Woo!
[Music]
Yeah.
[Applause]
[Music]
Heat. Heat. N.
Hey,
[Music]
ow.
Heat. Heat. N.
[Music]
Heat.
Hey,
hey,
hey.
[Music]
Oh yeah.
Hey.
[Music]
Oh yeah.
Oh
[Music]
my
god.
[Music]
Oh la.
Hey.
[Music]
Hey,
I'm home.
[Music]
Hey,
hey,
hey.
[Music]
Hey,
hey,
hey.
[Music]
Heat. Hey, Heat.
Hey, hey, hey.
Heat.
Hey, heat. Hey, heat.
on my way.
[Music]
Hey, hey,
hey,
hey, hey, hey,
[Music]
hey, hey,
hey, hey.
I
[Music]
I I
I
[Music]
Heat. Heat.
I feel
like I feel
Heat.
[Music]
Yeah,
Uh-huh.
[Music]
Ah,
hey.
[Music]
Hey,
hey, hey.
[Music]
Oh,
heat.
[Music]
[Applause]
Oh. Oh, starting with a whisper.
I know I find it hard to count down.
But I'll take way this time and night.
I've been there before a million times.
Cutting between the truth and the lies.
Can't hold me down for a minute long.
doesn't kill me.
Makes me stronger.
[Music]
Oh,
makes me stronger.
[Music]
Heat.
[Applause]
[Music]
Heat. Heat.
Fighting.
[Music]
Welcome ladies and gentlemen to LCK
2025. I'm Alice. I am joined by
Chronicler here for his first cast back
from MSI. Uh and we're also looking
absolutely glorious in our orange and
blue. Uh I'm feeling a little bit more
uh safety oriented than you are. Um not
quite as bright as you could be there,
Chronicler.
I for one do appreciate that. You know,
it's my final season at the Oscar and
you are wearing the Dutch national
collars. That's beautiful. You know,
that's friendship right there.
Yeah.
That's exactly why why we're in this.
It's the Dutch national national colors.
That's And I knew that that existed
prior to this conversation.
Absolutely. It really did. Um Yeah. Uh
so we've got a bit of a surprise for
you. Uh I know that your last cast was
T1 versus Gen G over at MSI. And so
we've decided to give you something
very, very different.
Oh. We've got T1 versus Gen, but it's a
home stand
here in Korea, which is very, very
exciting. As you can see here, we are
starting off with the legend group for
the first time this week. It's been Rise
Beginnings. Um, so far over the last
couple of days, but the undefeated Gen
are up against T1 and they've played a
lot of games against one another. I
believe in MSI it was 10 games in a row.
Uh, at least for Geng it was in a row.
Um, and then, you know, they went off to
EWC. They had some video games over
there as well. Didn't quite cross paths
the same amount of times, but uh I I
don't see Genji's winning streak
finishing here today. I would not be
shocked if it ends up being another
close yet so far moment as we have seen
many a time for Geng. I just want to
remind everyone the last time this team
lost um that that was that was in in
February by one game as well by the way
which I feel like we don't often talk
about but that was also by just one just
one as the 2025 SK Road show the T1 home
ground big match that we're going to
witness here between these two teams T1
I think in the minds of many of us right
now actually the second best team home
life have not looked that good in recent
form T1 the fact that they got to MSI
was, if we cast our minds back, a bit of
a surprise. The fact they got two games
away from winning against Geng twice
kind of mind-blowing.
Yeah. Well, I I mean, I think it's
debatable cuz I saw KT play yesterday
and I quite enjoyed what I was watching.
I'm not going to lie to you. That is a
debate for another day, though, as it is
T1 versus Gen here today. And as we can
see, Genji have been doing a lot of the
most recent winning, and that's because
they haven't lost to anyone at all. um
you know since the LCK cup and first
stand and stuff like that happened after
that it was all Geng all the time. Are
you ready Chroy and always Faker is the
response between these two 63 to
I still can't I I can't believe that
literally the only that that one win
decided who won MSI like that's that's
that's not real. How is that how is that
a thing? How is that the life we're
living where literally that single game
difference between these two mid laners
ended up deciding the MSI? I It's
mindboggling. Atlas, it's insane. It is
absolutely ridiculous. And then over at
EWC, of course, they didn't actually
meet one another and so we didn't really
uh see too much since that MSI final. It
was the same patch, though. This is the
first time we're seeing them on the new
one. And now some walkouts here.
Starting with T1 and starting on the top
side, it is Doran owner going to be
joining him there in the jungle. And I
am looking forward to seeing a
revitalized T1 here
as the mid lane goat walking in
coming after I think for his standards a
pretty lackluster spring but did
definitely step it up again at MSI which
was very needed. Kind of a reverse of
last year. Uh, Gumushi Carry out. We
have talked about these players. We've
talked about this team for so much. The
introduction of Doran with the fact that
they made their first MSI finals in a
very long time, plus the importance that
he had in getting them there. I think a
cool reminder of how this roster has
changed. Obviously the fourman core uh
four of the most insane consistent
highlevel finishes that we have seen out
of really any group of players uh
perhaps in the LCK only rivaled by the
team that they're about to face up
against because that top side is looking
mean as well and for T1 what a big win
it would be even though it is just just
a legend group right it's just a regular
season win
you remember Atlas cuz I'm pretty sure
if I remember correctly it was you Wolf
that casted that that first round Robin
the one where Chovi cuz that game three
the the Chovy Victor moment that did not
feel like a regular season game.
Oh no no no no. Casting that was
definitely not a regular season. That's
not how it works.
That felt like we were at a semi-final.
Well that was not that was not normal.
And to be honest you know the matchups
between these two teams didn't really
change as we went further through the
year as well. So, it is pretty
incredible um that that's what we're
getting as we do have
a pretty exciting day on our hands. We
saw that is an absolutely packed arena
there as well over in Inchan. Um super
duper cool to see so many people come
out and it reminds me of a quote that
Geng had which is talking about having
to play against crowds that aren't
necessarily for them. Well, they've got
another test on their hands. I'm pretty
sure it is the T1 home ground. So, of
course, this one is being put on by T1.
But even if it was a Genji home ground,
I would expect a lot of T1 fans to also
be there and be very loud.
That's just the reality really. And this
is something we keep going back to. It
doesn't matter where we are in the
world. Legitimately, we've we've cost
this team in every region worldwide,
they will always be crowd favorite.
There just isn't a way around it. Uh,
and for Geng, particularly for Chrovis,
he's obviously been here since 2022,
right? Who has basically faced off
against his team an infinite amount of
times,
they're just used to it. That's just
that's just the reality. That's just
life as it is for Gen.
And the reason he's only just beaten the
headto-head as well is that, you know,
Griffin was consistently losing in 2019.
2020 didn't see much better things. 2021
was a weird year. And you know, it's
it's a story of Chovi making his way
back into into godhood after what was
such an extraordinary debut with his
what 126 KDA or something like that he
had in his uh large amount of
undefeatedness uh that he started off
with. And we are going to move in to the
introductions for Geng here, our EWC
winners as well as our MSI back-to back
champions.
This is uh another test that they're
going to have to pass here. They did
manage to get through HLE pretty
comfortably earlier in the week right
after getting off a plane. I don't know
what to expect after they've had a
couple of good nights sleep.
Yeah, we've seen people kind of go the
opposite way where they're like,
actually the enemy of Gen is breaks,
right? Like if you look at some of their
some of their performances after not
playing for like a week or two, uh I I
don't want to lean into the memes too
much,
but this Geng team and particularly uh
Chovi, right? What I love every time we
get the Chi versus Faker is how much
these two players clearly respect each
other and how Faker has been pushed by
Chi to become a better laner, right? Cuz
that's something that he used to bring,
but when we go back to when Chovi really
rose to prominence, that was his biggest
strength. whereas Chovi is watching
Faker win a World Finals and he's like,
I need I need to be like him. I need to
be more clutch. So, I just love the back
and forth that we have between these
two. And that's always going to be the
core, right? Because let's be real, it's
the greatest of all time versus the
current best player in the world that
every thing that we talk about is just
going to kind of gravitate towards that.
Yep. It's just sort of how it is. And I
do want to like deviate from that
momentarily because I do think one of
the biggest reasons why Geng look as
incredibly good as they do is because
they got this random guy from Liv
sandbox and he's just super duper good
is absolutely amazing man. This guy has
just fit in with a team full of only
legends. It's I know it's the legend
group and blah blah blah, but these are
incredible players in their own right
that have built extraordinary legacies.
You know, the story of Keen finishing in
every single position, you know, before
he manages to get first. There's a story
of Ruler being world champion and then
taking forever to become a domestic
champion. We were talking about Troy for
a while. This is about Canyon trying to
rise back again to the prominence that
he found in 2020. Was toted as the best
jungler in the world, but then how does
he get back there? And then Duro, a guy
who just joined the league and then he
just hopped onto the team. He's like,
I'm going to be the new carrier. You
just watch.
Yeah. I
And so far,
literally the only moment where we felt
like it was actually going to be a big
issue was like what the first two
months.
We were we were starting in like April.
We're like, hold up, wait a minute. What
is happening? Yeah. And I think Duro
both in terms of gameplay uh but also
when it comes to some of the moments
that he had at MSI, I don't know if you
saw at the end where he just hold up the
hand and silenced the crap that you
you're not supposed to have that much
aura when you're the like the quote
unquote rookie on your team. Not
technically a rookie obviously did play
as you highlighted for a very short
amount of time,
but I think it also highlights what we
have seen from GenG in their ability.
They did this with the light as well as
we go back and yeah, it should come as
absolutely no surprise that Chovi is
leading in a lot of stats here.
Yeah. Um they haven't lost a series
since we started recording these stats.
So
um yeah, uh it's it's looking like he's
probably going to continue having pretty
good stats throughout the season because
we also haven't had a stat reset. It's
not like we've gone to the summer season
or anything like that even though it's
hot as heck outside. Um it is just sat
stats rolling through. So yeah, this is
um this is pretty unprecedented. Highest
DPM in the league. And the damage per
gold stats are really interesting here
because I think that's one of the
greatest stats for determining how much
uh you make use of the money that you're
given in every game. It's not just based
on how much you're winning, it's based
on how much use you get out of it. The
fact that these two have this the two
highest in the league really goes to
show why we always talk about Troy
versus Faker. But in in Chov's case,
it's actually even more insane cuz you
know how much gold he gets, right? Like
that that to me is what always gets me
with Chovi is that you know the leads he
builds, the leads that again cuz his
team just wins a lot. So being able to
still have that much damage even though
you are getting that much gold every
game I think is insane for Faker. I want
to reiterate I think that Faker has been
a demon in spring in 2023 in 2024. I
think this spring was actually
relatively muted. We were talking about
Zea. We were talking about BDD, not
about him. I think he did really step it
up when it comes to the impact that he
was able to find again, particularly at
MSI. Uh, but when it comes to going up
against Chovi, that is what Chovi has
been trying to incorporate, right? Like
that impact, what can he do? What are
the plays he can make? And how can he
impact the map?
And their final against anyone's legend
that we did see only a few days ago, it
was that game five that really I don't
know. It it I had that sort of moment
where I realized he's changed because
I'd watched him on DRX so many times,
pick TF
get so much gold and then just push top
lane and lose.
Yep.
That that did not happen this time
around. He got the gold. He did that
part, you know, 4,000 at a like what 000
score line or something like that ahead
of his opposition, but then won the
game. then was helping the rest of his
team, then was utilizing Destiny's to
make sure that everyone else was able to
get things done and and it really was an
eye openening moment as to the
development of this guy and the fact
that he's been able to transition
incredible individual play into being
able to win on the map as well.
And what I love Atlas is we've been
talking all this time about basically
just Faker and Chovy, a little bit of
Duro. We can have a
Yeah, we can have these sort of
about every single matchup. What about
the fact that Keen, who I think was the
tournament MVP when it comes to uh what
was it? MSI was, if I remember
correctly, the actual tournament MVP.
Yeah, VWC as well.
The fact that Ruler, who I think was
together with Duro, one of the slightly
weak spots,
that MSI performance was
it was crazy.
And the game five also in EWC as well
picks Zia and then just hard carries.
He's like, "Don't worry, guys. It's on
my shoulders now."
Which Guma did in game four against Al
at MSI as well together as Rakan.
There's too many parallels. We're
skipping the draft. We're just not going
to talk about it. Um, you guys can watch
as the pretty pictures come up on the
screen. Wait a minute. We're going to
sling narrative. That's what we're
doing.
We haven't even talked. You mentioned
it, but 2020 DRX. That was Parador and
Chovi.
Oh my goodness. The amount of uh Yeah, I
mean, a lot of these players have all
played with each other. Of course, Keen
has taken Doran's position and things
like this. It's all just a bit all over
the place. But we do have some bands.
Let's have a chat about those, I guess,
as the Tia, the Aurora, and the Gallo
all going to be taken away. You could
argue that they are all trophy bands as
well, although the Aurora ban is almost
definitely angled towards Keen. And what
is left up? Annie, Vi, um the PV that we
were talking about on Wednesday, uh Wolf
and I is um the VI, Varys, and the
Pantheon. And the V is still left up,
but the Annie is going to be the
selection here for Faker.
I was wondering whether they were going
to go for beam on Gwen cuz the Aurora
has been one of the prominent counter
picks. This is also a highlight that
that I think the Viprow has slowly
started drop. I wouldn't be surprised if
Owner still picks it up here. He's an
incredible VI. It is really good
together with the Annie specifically,
but to me, we have seen the VI slowly
start to follow and Wukong is something
you pick into VI, right? because of the
ability to counteract a lot of what she
does. The clone is really annoying to
deal with. Again, wouldn't be surprised
if device still gets picked up here. And
what we also continue to see is that T1
is heavily prioritizing getting a
comfortable matchup for Faker. They've
been doing this a lot, bending a lot of
trophy champions and then picking
something that Faker's victory and blind
can be any. I imagine if we go to like a
game two, game three, we're going to see
the Well, we're going to go to game two,
but if we go to game three, we're going
to see the Victor as well. something
that they've been prioritizing for
exactly the same reason as a VI would go
well with these two champions. AD Fred
Zinszou could be another I I would have
also liked Trundle just because I love
Trundle Rumble. I know you can't see any
tanks on the other side, right? You
often try to pick it into tanks, but
Trundle's just been good.
It's just good.
I'm with you as this would have twofold
pressure here for Chovi. would be very
good into the lane match up against
Annie obviously having a lot of range.
I would have thought that Diana makes a
lot more sense but
I mean I would have loved that. I think
actually Diana is one of those champions
where we might start seeing her in
certain matchups. Uh just at any point,
right?
I think as soon as Kenan hits the rift,
that's when
Oh god, don't remind. What was that? Was
this Was this like his Gwen counter pick
and it was a disaster? He got solo bolo.
It was his Gwen countered pick. That's
what it was. It was a little bit
different.
Yeah, it's it's when you exchange the R
for the D and you really do struggle.
This is both a lane number pick for
Chroy, but it also picks away from
Faker, right? The Faker is one of the
players that still really likes the
Oriana, gravitates towards it very
often.
Yep.
So, you are able to take that away and
also it combines really well with the
Wukong filler. That's a no-brainer. We
have double AP solo lanes combined with
a heavy AD threat.
Yep. I'm seeing or is going to be very
upset. Uh because with double AP we're
not going to be getting a Ziggs. Not
this time around.
Yeah, Naidder. No one should be picking
Zigs here in this first game.
I don't think that's what's going to
happen. I think center is going to be
locked in by someone though unless it is
going to be banned away.
My guess would be yeah R for center here
if it isn't banned for Genji and then
they give counter pick to Duro. Genji
have liked just picking like Re. Uh I
think Real is also a good pickway cuz
Real Rumble and Real Vi obviously are
really big threats. You can just slam Re
or Alistar here on four and then give
the counter pick over to
uh to Duro. There is also the threat of
a Jin which I think that Gouma in
particular is going to be looking
towards. Both players have liked it but
for T1 it obviously doubles up because
Jyn is very self-sufficient in lane and
gives carry the ability to impact the
map.
There is the Alistar ban which feels
like they are fishing for a real here
like they want Jen to pick RA right
especially with an Alistister ban which
normally we see picked into the rail a
decent amount
and we also really like on the side of
T1 so it kind of fits if it is going to
be left up. I think the center is still
probably um the highest priority
champion that's sort of left up as far
as the roles that they're looking for,
but we'll see what ruler does decide to
go with as we are ticking down. It's a
Jin instead.
Feels like denial um rather than picking
for Ruler. They will be able to take
that one away from Gushi.
I' I've been I've been happily convinced
by Ruler's Jin. I also think that this
is the type of composition where it does
work well. You don't have a lot of
safety from your uh from your team so
far. It is eco
combined with the Oh my god, Duro.
Okay, I mean, if Duro's just going to
like sit here in like the the T1 home
ground and just aura farm everyone by
playing carrier's skin,
oh my goodness, that would be too much.
That would be going too far, my friend.
And
the the the funniest part about this is
if you told me if you took the name
plates away, I would have thought that
that Geng draft was a T1 draft. And this
is something that as we I think play
more and more Fearless, we're going to
see more and more of is teams just
trying to work on two levels cuz I think
this is a very good draft from Gen,
right? You have good lane pressure. I
think Bard works really well into
particularly the Rumble, the Annie. I
think those champions can really
struggle, even the Nico into the Bard.
But then add to that that you're also
picking away Gumayushi's Jin, right,
which has been one of his pick comp. You
pick away the Oriana.
For T1 though, I think that there is
this type of composition that just
really plays heavily around early
scraps. That's what they love. This is a
very chaotic team and I like that they
lean into it draft in the first game.
Yep. It's going to work pretty well, I
could imagine, for the beginnings of the
game. It's just whether it's going to
work well enough against uh Genji, who
are pretty good at just staying stable
and then playing for the team fights
later on. We've also seen that Oriana
can lack a bit of damage depending on
what the build is going to be. I think
my favorite was from Shanks a little bit
more recently, which was like shadow
flames and all sorts of mega damage
builds and items. And that sounds really
fun. Let's get into it.
I was waiting for some fan chance, but
we didn't get any fan chance. Do we miss
them?
cuz I'm I'm hearing chatter.
There's certainly some chanting going.
There we go.
[Music]
Okay.
That's a lot of T1.
Okay. Let's just not commentate. We can
just let the crowd do it.
No T1 crowds. This isn't going to stop
anytime soon either.
Yeah, that's what I'm thinking. I'm
like, hang on. How how long are we
supposed to hold?
Also, Duro is not using carrier's skin,
which is I think a little bit of a
bother.
That's okay. Chi could have also done
the same thing. He elected not to.
I wouldn't be surprised.
I want I hope that Ruler used ghost
skin, though.
The ghost jin is actually dope. That is
actually my favorite Jin skin. And it is
mostly because of Ghost. Let's be real.
He's just such a lovely. He's just so
sweet.
And I like just the, you know, the Greek
god theming of that skin line. I think
it's just cool.
And this is also uh the first time that
Geng can get revenge uh sorry, the T1
can get revenge for GenG putting T1's
broken key in their trophy at EWC. Even
though they never faced off against one
another, they did the same thing to
Halife Esports as well. It was uh the
first time that that had happened and we
were trying to work out whether it's BM
or not. And I don't think that that was
the case. I know that it was Ruler and
Dura that were standing up there trying
to figure out what to do and that's just
what they decided to do. And I just
think it's kind of funny. So now we'll
see what T1 think about it in this early
game as the aggression is going to begin
hopefully shortly. We have had some
relatively late uh first blood.
It does give you and me the opportunity
to catch up.
It's true. It has been a while.
It has been a long time, Atlas,
cuz we always joke, you know, how how uh
it's always you and me wherever we go.
And then it wasn't. And it really
bothered me. I I I missed you a lot.
Yeah, I I was uh I was a bit sad not to
make it to Vancouver. Never been to uh
to Canada before, but we're glad to be
back. And now we've got a lot of time.
Also skipped out on you, so I we're both
here. That's what matters as uh I think
looking at the early draft setups here,
this is two compositions that do really
look to push the issue. As soon as we
get to level six, right when we get the
ultimates available for the Wukong, the
VI, the Yiani, and the Rumble, that's
when I do expect there to be a
considerable amount of action. But on
the particularly for Wukong, I don't
really think they're going to be looking
too much. We do have some summoner
trades here early on.
Yeah, Carrier actually being read by a
book. read like a book a little bit
towards his bottom side. Sometime
sometimes those those shape spplitters
can let you get away with some stuff.
Not this time around.
But it is sort of like it's double range
match up towards the bottom side of the
map. It's level six scaling junglers as
you mentioned before. Gwen Rumble is a
lot more even than it was in the past.
At least that's sort of how it feels.
And Oriana Annie, need we say more? This
is like season one.
Exhaust for Keane I do think. Yeah, he
did ping. So he did spot does know that
owner is there and this is a preix
Wukong so I don't know how much he can
really do maybe if the binding hit but
doesn't look like that's going to be the
case and both junglers going to be
trying to get a base in and yeah I think
particularly after we saw the continuous
nerfs to Rumble uh he still has a lot of
friend lane we saw some solo kills
recent yesterday
but particular with the exhaust unless
you get ganked you should be able to
just as Ke is doing here maintain a nice
amount of pressure. Ke did go for
conqueror by the way. We've still seen a
decent mix between that and the
crosswash
traded as Goomer is just going to flash
away.
Ooh, flash and barrier and he'll use as
well. So some positive trade here. Duro
playing aggressive on the bard.
Yeah, there are two corkies here and if
there's two corkies it's going to make
the cleanse not very useful. That's my
assessment. still very even when it
comes to the summoner spells. In fact,
three corkies. Never mind. It's
completely out of control here for T1.
As you can see, carrier taking a bit of
damage
by Ruler who is standing his ground. Got
the Brad moving away. There is a Wukong
making his way in and a VI lurking in
the area as well. We'll see whether
there is actually going to be any action
as the health trade certainly favoring
Ruler for the moment.
Yeah, I think both junglers just showing
up trying to
immediate cleanse making use of that one
shot. Carrier turns back but it is going
to be the deadly flourish avoided and
Gumushi carrier going to look for a
little bit of a back angle.
That would have been big if that hits.
Never mind
the pre six dive.
Yeah, holding on to it here as Gumushi
Nim Strike going to come on through. And
it's actually Duro that takes the kill
and the teleport is going to be in a
little bit late here by Doran does have
the equalizer available though. But they
just take a magical journey to safety as
Tibis gets a little bit angry. But so
does the orb. And now Chro is looking to
chase it up. Look at the flash forward.
And there is the flash in to follow.
Owner locks down the kill onto Chovi.
And it may have just all been a bait.
Beautiful bait there. Oh, can you Oh,
there it is. Okay, never mind. It's
going to be answered. And Faker did
indeed go down. I thought that actually
Faker had made it out, but he was off
screen and I just saw the fact that Ona
came in for the kill. So actually going
to be a big old trade up here for Geng.
If Canyon doesn't find that kill would
have been really big there for T1 able
to get both Chroy's flash which does
mean that particularly with level six
available for Vice soon would have been
huge. First though going back to this it
really is testament to the 2v2 prowess
of Duro and Ruler that even when they
are playing cleanse into this barrier
lane they're still able to maintain as
much pressure to set up for a dive. Pre
six womb dives just aren't that good.
And then here Chovi thinks he has an
angle on Faker. I assume the shield just
barely is enough as yet there's dead
again.
That's that's the cost of that flash. So
Chomi playing aggressive and getting
punished two times in a row now.
Yeah, that was a solo kill from Fo.
No, no, no. It was I think uh both Owner
and Carrier. Carrier definitely flashed
for it. Owner was shown up the assist. I
don't know. Maybe I don't know if he was
actually involved. I should see
he didn't get an assist or at least
No, I guess he didn't. I thought I saw
him in the kill.
Might have been around.
Oh, I It was Carrier pretending to be
That's definitely what happened.
Yeah, we're going to check it out one
more time. Yes, and indeed Carrier is
here going to make his way over. There's
also an equalizer. So, it's Doran.
That's uh who the other person was.
Oh, it's Doran. There you go. Uh but
nicely done by Carrier. Really good
punish. Uh really good punish by the
side of T1 to make use of the fact that
the Tro has that flash right like that
aggressive flash. Uh I think a little
over eager when you're Oriana even
though the solo kill which you didn't
get again was Canyon that secure that
would have been nice. You are Oriana
into Nico by an end. So
that summon is pretty valuable. Tib is
going to come back again and command
protect not really going to be saving
Chovi here. is going to be skirting
around. Keen here towards his bottom
side. Needs to be a little careful. That
health bar is getting toasted a little
by Doran as Tim is going to come on over
and stand as T1 will be able to take
down these grubs. And they've taken the
first dragon as well. So, this will be
the second objective that they're able
to lock down if they can indeed do so.
Owner making his way out. And that will
be two grubs going over to T1 and
another objective secured for them as
far as feats of strength are concerned.
One more kill, one more objective. They
will be able to upgrade some shoes. The
equalizer goes down, but the exhaust is
there from Keen, who's snipping around
the rip. Does have his needles out as
well, but Faker is making his way down.
And Keen has now just realized that he's
likely dead. Wants to be able to trade
this one for the kill against Doran.
Let's see whether he can actually get
there as Never mind. Faker just comes on
over, stuns him up, and will just walk
underneath the turret, hoping to deny an
assist to Doran or something like that
in case, you know, damage came in a
little late, but wasn't to be the case.
Ruler on the hunt. Don't think he's
going to find him. Looks like Doran with
a safe back. Not going to be found by
this Jin. Ruler not wanting to just
throw out his ultimate and risk just
wasting it. And that is a nice set of
counter punches here now from T1. I do
want to reiterate that I do think that
with this style of composition, they're
the ones that need to keep this pace
high. If you end up just playing frontto
back team fights, eventually I think
you're going to reach the point where
Genji is going to be really hard to deal
with because their targets will get
harder to burst down. Uh it does look
like Chovi is going for a uh more tanky
build which
makes sense given the comp might still
be dead though. He is uh his flash is
enough as Tempered Fate is going to buy
him a little bit of time um but
otherwise not too much. It does take him
a little while longer. Pop Blossom is
going to be invested. Roller comes on
down though and Tibis is angry but it's
still going to be T1 that are running
away from the bottom lane of Gen G. They
got their prize and once again I mean 03
on this Oriana. We've seen like better
score lines on an Oriana be a little bit
useless and so this is exactly the T1
game plan trying to take Chroy out of
this as much as possible and it's
working.
I really like the punish there is so
much CC and so much damage available on
the team between the Annie Vi and Eco
and they're just really consistently
leaning into it. It's not even like
Chobi is that far of his lane, right?
like he is just basically standing like
just beyond the wall.
Yep.
Uh that uh marks between the river and
the jungle as you can see here. Not like
he's that far up the lane, but it's just
a really nice timing here from Owner.
And even if Oner doesn't find him, like
in the flash, I think Carrier will
always murder him. Uh regardless of what
happens, attempted
uh saved by Jor doesn't quite hit the
mark. if he can fight people instead of
just maybe that's enough but not going
to be the case and then Carrier has to
do his best as he will be very happy to
do so for that kill.
Yeah, I guess as well but shock wave's
going to come down towards his bottom
side as Joby I think is a little angry.
They get the cyclone as well that is
going to guarantee that the Annie goes
down as Dor you got to stop this man he
is just meep slapping everyone to death
and I think some of the kills would be
better on a Wukong or an Oriana. really
would cuz he's not even if he was
electrocute, you know, like give me that
rapid fire cannon.
I mean, he could still build a rap. I
was talking about this just
he should he shouldn't pivot. He he's
got his redemption done, which is good
for early fights. Chovi did finish his
roa, so that's something. But I have not
been the biggest fan of the ROA. I feel
like the item after the nerfs just
doesn't really hit the same impact. No,
my read is that Chovi, he has a ton of
damage in his team and he's also going
to be just very far behind in this game.
I say that it's 130 gold
which uh he has been farming up a storm
as often is the case. So despite all the
attention that's paid,
it is still only 130 gold
which is kind of crazy.
Yeah, sort of ridiculous. That is going
to be feed of strength as well over to
T1. I'm pretty sure yes it is. as that
uh last remaining objective was taken.
They take down the dragon. So T1
upgrading some shoes pretty nicely and
it's a cloud soul. Oh baby, you love to
see it. Always T1. They're always so
good at getting the cloud souls. Some
needle work down here towards bottom
side and Faker has just decided that he
wants to get out and he will do so. But
looking a little worse for wear as him
and Tibers head towards top side. It is
like a kind of cool two for one special,
isn't it? When you're Annie, you get to
teleport your bear up there at the same
time.
If Keen had an item, he would have just
died. That was a little dicey, but
wasn't a little.
Will be able to make it out anyway.
Oh dear, that could be 50 gold over to
Choby as well. Maybe um playing Annie
into Chobi himself is actually a bad
idea cuz this puts an extra minion on
the map for him.
I think this movement Yeah, the movement
by Ruler kind of gives away that owner's
like, "Uh, can I take that?" Right,
guys. All right. Well, Duo and Canyon
are in here. They're going to get the
cyclone out as Ona will get the alt in.
Doran is following as Quen's in the mix
and they're looking for the Rumble as
well. Magical journey going to be taken.
On will get taken down, but it's a
double pop blossom. Keen is going to go
down and Canyon nowhere to run. Duro the
same situation. He's going to have to
really find some magic here.
Yeah, that is going to be the old faint
flame splitter spitter. And down goes
the bar. Toby's farming. Ruler's
farming, but the rest of the team is
dead.
Yeah, Ruler walked up, ulted, got his
kill, and I was like, "Ah, okay, I'm no
longer needed here." And
it's it's so cool because just that
movement from Ruler, I think, gave away.
So, Owner knows he's going into multiple
people here. And they're timing it with
the arrival of Nico while also making
sure that Ruler can't actually join the
fight. And then with the open door,
they're able to at least get that kill.
But when all is said and done, this is
obviously a very favorable trade. Will
be three kills, 2-1. And this is offset
a little bit by the fact that Chobi is
just in a lane unattended by himself,
which is why when we look at the gold
lead, we're going to see that basically
sticking around the same mark.
And also, we did just watch him kill
Tibers as well. So that's another 50 in
his back pocket. That's
You are really
I mean,
you're locked in on the Tippers gold. I
mean, it is just a lot of gold, man.
It's It's worth the same amount as a
Nexus.
Well, I feel like with Nexus, there's
other circumstances that make the Nexus
really valuable.
No, no, no. 50 gold that is worth.
Well, no. I I know that it has that, but
that's not why people aspire to take
down a nexus. I would say
that's not my point, though.
Okay.
I'm just talking about the monetary
value of a Nexus is the same as pivots.
I And you know what? That's true. You
are correct. I I I have no further
argument, your honor. Uh that's all I
got. Um yeah, so that is a large reason
why uh Genji are still doing decently
well as far as gold, but you can feel
that the tempo around this map is not in
their favor. Right, T1 are still taking
the things that they want. There's been
no objectives really picked up for Gen
throughout this entire game. And that is
going to continue as here towards the
bottom side of the map. What if we try
to kill Thor again? Well, he's just
going to al the wave. The cannon is
going to come through with another melee
and we're going to see whether we can
kill him underneath this turret. Another
cyclone does come in. Decoy going to
help take him out there as the tempered
fate will deactivate the turret. That
will allow everyone to get out of here
as T1. Yeah, they're going to throw down
the Rift Herald and they're going to
look for even more. A sacrifice of just
a rumble for this outer turret is going
to feel pretty good as now Keen dashing
after Faker here. The flash does come
out and now Faker is definitely dead.
That flash was never saving him ever.
And now you got a Rift Herald making her
way up towards the top side. Shelly
Shel's merry jaunt as we can see here.
But I don't know whether he wants to
charge the turret because he probably
would die. Shel is just going to wear
wear herself out and head back to the
void.
This game's a bit of a mess out there.
It's weird, man.
It's fun. I'm having a good time.
I mean, it just feels like T1 have done
so many things and then I look at the
top of the screen and I'm like, yes,
they've got two dragons, but it's seven
to seven and Genji has a gold lead. Like
why do they have a gold lead?
Yeah, I So it's partially the farm. It's
partially the ability to they get a good
amount of plates. And when it comes to
kills, it ended up being I think
relatively I think it's 7 to seven right
now. So nice dive here. The fact that
Dory uses his uh ultimate there does
mean that the mid lane turret falls. I
think maybe otherwise he could have
barely made it. All right, here's
another little catch. As we can see,
Keen was in the mist for a while, but
the equalizer is going to come down.
That's another kill going over to
Gumushi. Did take a fair bit of damage,
but not quite enough as now Doran in a
little bit of trouble. But maybe Ruler
is as well, but finally does get that
last shot
into the Rumble. Yeah, Ruler has al and
they don't have a Rumble, so maybe this
is going to be a dragon that T1 feel
like they can give up. Just one cloud
isn't end of the world.
They don't really want to risk it, I
don't think.
Looking at the alts, they only have
Faker's old available. Oh, they've got
Kushi's old as well.
Yeah, that Okay, well,
I missed you, Chronic.
That is true. Yeah, you haven't tilted
me. Wow. I I I lost my Atlas resistance.
Everything gets to me.
It's all too easy.
Yeah, it's not fun for you.
Just need to get your practice up.
It'll be fine. Uh I do think that
maybe look for Cheeky. Not going to do
it even with the vision. I think that's
that's fair. Uh they don't really need
to go for this. Would have been good for
T1 if they had gotten it. And I think
the redemption actually ended up being
pretty big in that fight, right? The
fact that Duro has that available
because if we look, Keem stays alive
here for a lot longer than I was
initially expecting. It's him opting
into this, by the way. Yep. Uh just
fully voluntarily, but because he stays
alive for so long, the rest of T1 can't
help with taking down Ruler. And then
Chi finds a nice ultimate to bring him
back. Ruler finds W. Suddenly, Doran
goes down and a lot of were used in T by
T1 in the previous fight. And I think
they are more reliant on their ultimates
especially when Ruler and Doro still are
there. So Drake's going to go over to GG
as Chovi. Is it a trap? Yeah, they're
going in. Who's trapping who? As the
shock wave is fantastic to deny Faker's
approach and now owner is in a little
bit of trouble, but he's continuing to
go in. This guy has no fear at all as
the rockets do start raining down and
Gumushi will say cease fire everyone.
They will acquies at least for now. Keen
and Doran continuing to just one v one
here towards the bottom side and Gushi
will come back towards the mid lane
because Ruler is continuing to shove
that one out
as are we going to go for it as Chovi is
backing
who is there it is canyon comes on over
and that is two dead Chi just knew I
guess Genji had all the information and
T1 caught napping as we've got a little
bit of a dive here as the equal
that is not a dive that you could take
beautifully played here by Doran But on
the top side, it's a mess.
And not even vintage Doran is enough to
halt the acceleration of gold for Genji.
I really thought that they knew.
Wait, unless Gumushi is down here just
killing Ruler.
Thanks for the chocolate.
And he's able to get himself out. Does
have of course the ghost blade.
Oh, I I want to go back to that. I
thought that they spotted them. Like I
actually thought that they spotted him
uh spotted them going into the brush
right there cuz I think for a split
second we saw the play from Canyon. They
clearly did it but that wouldn't have
happened. Goes in with stealth. He's
able to get the kill. Chovi selling this
very well is what allows them to
going on the edge of vision and then
backing like that. That was very sneaky.
Uh allows him to get the and then here
Keen has been playing very fast and
loose this game. really how I like
actually shout out to Doran, right? So
he uh
a lot of work was actually dodged as
well.
So dodges he rocket belts forward which
dodges the W. Then he dodges the second
shot which would have slowed him and
maybe gotten another shot and then he
also is able to as you highlight dodge
the needle work while simultaneously
getting his off take down which is nice
and which you see a little bump up.
Yeah, a little bit of a dorm blip.
Yeah, that's that's a dorm blip. Uh but
then on the other side of the map,
Canyon has been he's been gaming Atlas.
Yeah, he's he's definitely been gaming.
Uh 61 and three on the Wukong. And we
saw yesterday um it doesn't take Geng to
make to make Wukong look broken like uh
Wukong when he gets ahead. Was it uh who
was it that was playing uh playing
Wukong yesterday? I want to say it might
have been
is a big it just looked broken. It just
looked really ridiculous the amount of
damage that he was able to do. Now is
going to get started up as Geng looking
for their second objective of the game.
Oh, that's a late contest.
Oh, they're looking for the angle here
as Doran does have his equalizer back
off cool down. This will be difficult
for them to lock down as the equalizer
does come in and it will be secured here
by Geng. Good smite from Canyon.
Although there was no real contest as
far as that front is concerned because
the buy was nowhere in the area.
Genji will just uh secure the highway
robbery and is a big deal buff man. like
this this guy. It's no longer just like
you know the pedal situation and stuff
like that. You just get a whole bunch
more.
It's a big deal as you highlight. It
also I think sets up nicely because that
teleport being invested by Doran means
that Keen can now get TO push out that
top wave and then make his way over
towards the contest on the drake which
would give Genji another opportunity.
And despite everything that happened in
the early game and the best attempts to
shut down, Chobi is currently sitting on
a 2K.
Yeah. Um I I didn't want to bring that
up.
Well, we have to.
It's confusing.
So, I think it's a continued like
obviously the farm cuz it's almost 50
farm at this point. That that is a big
amount of gold. He's got I think two
turrets. Definitely got uh definitely
got the top side. I think it was there
for bot as well.
Uh let's say let's say three to four
tibers. So, that's 200 gold right there.
I hope I hope Yundo's back there
somewhere counting the amount of tivers
that were taken.
The space is going to ensure that you
know how many tak
what it takes it takes six tibbers to
make a kill.
If he's killed six tippers then he's
actually a one three and seven Oriana.
Very true. Atlas
just quick
needs to win this fight. He need to get
a top on Ruler or Chovi. Well, Keen is
running away, but I don't know whether
he's necessarily the target that they
want to be going on. Can be slippery,
although it has worked in the past. Now,
Dur could be in trouble, but he's also
not the target they're looking for. The
equalizer is weird to say the least.
And T1 now without that big tool. Bonita
works coming out there. The pop is going
to connect on a new shot under four
people. Oh no, five. My god, the
cyclone. And they all explode. It is
over as Genji, they'll take a
celebratory dragon. And oh god, T1, that
is not where you wanted to be.
That's a bad movie right there, baby.
That's what that was. That was a fiveman
shockwave.
I was like, surely it's not five. My
brain just refused to believe that that
was five people standing in perfect
position to be blended.
In in theory, it makes sense. It's like
Gwen doesn't have an escape. Ke has been
Keen has been playing like a psychopath.
If we burst him down, we can maybe play
the game. And I do think T1 need to play
for these picks.
The equalizer being used early, maybe a
little scared, but then the whole
sequence of the fiveman ultimate into
the Duro ultimate and then
into the just wandering over
whizzes them up, you know, puts them
into the food processor.
Uh, we got to see this again as Keem
goes in. It actually is
Oh my god,
Durham. It's a point blank.
And then just the flash cyclone. No way
to react. They're all just in the sky as
soon as they come out of being golden.
And they are whisked up. Oh my goodness.
Well, if there is any doubt about Genji
being in winning position in this game
before, it is gone now as that is a
guarantee. 8,000 gold now. the lead at
24 and 1/2 minutes.
So, this uh provides me with a great
opportunity to ask Atlas.
Yes.
How you've been?
I've been pretty good.
Yeah.
Yeah. Not too bad.
It's Korean summer, you know. It's a
lot.
Yeah, that's uh it's not great. Faker is
dead. Um and T Who did it go to? Canyon.
Canyon. Unless it was trophy. They were
they were sharing some
the flank.
Okay, there is a flank.
Chronicler is not wrong.
I just don't know whether you want to
flank five people as four people. I
don't think
uh in fact that's a nice possible
finding. If only there was another shock
wave there, Troy, as that would have
been an easy one on two, but instead
So, back to green summer. It's it's
rough.
It is. It is real rough. We've got a
really nice air conditioner, though. So,
that is uh that has been put through its
paces.
That is the most important.
Yeah. And so, that's definitely good,
especially with my wife pregnant at
home.
I've been eating your uh your cold
noodles.
Cold noodle. Oh, I haven't had many on
that much. That's actually something
that I should be uh picking up here.
Yeah, we're going to check out the
replay
and there were people Faker was alone.
He was dead.
One Faker and four Geng members.
Didn't go so well.
And despite the start, this Annie has
really been uh after I think having both
great early impact in the lane as well
as in the side lanes able to find some
plays even towards Keen. uh not being
allowed to really play the game.
There's a flash in. That's going to be
another cosmic binding. Doran taking
some time being CCed and will get caught
by the very edge of that tempered fate.
I've seen other ones of those miss as
Keen is going to snip him up. It is now
going to be Keen versus the bottom lane,
but the pop loss going to do nothing
against the stasis that he brings out.
So that means that owner is going to die
as well as everyone is zoned away. And
ladies and gentlemen, this game is over.
It is it is just not it's not really
there's a 4,000 gold lead for the monkey
um as we can see there and not even that
outer turret is going to be secured as
Genji are going to look for the Baron.
Information is given over as T1 are
looking for a miracle here and that is
precisely what they're going to need.
Well, that can definitely bully them up
there like Chi needs to walk all the way
over. They need to hurry up though.
You see definitely Kane is on a flank
angle as Carrier could be in a little
bit of trouble here as Duro going to be
cleansing himself. The deadly flourish
comes down. There are the curt there's
the curtain call as Canyon gets out of
the pit. This baron is so
extraordinarily low. It's down to 1,100
and it's going to be secured by Gumushi.
He's in the back of the pit and just
gets sliced up like a ham. And it's
going to be Ruler that takes that kill.
Now Carrier wanting to keep at least
another one of these baronss alive as
Canyon comes boop. And down goes the VI.
That was actually an eco.
Does it again. If the game state was
even remotely close, that would have
been huge. Uh it it doesn't really
change the
equation. It still helps the the gumi
narrative though.
It it is he can put that one on the list
as well. So what I want to highlight
here, I actually like this call from T1
cuz you're in a desperate situation,
right? And you tpd to bot and then they
started Nash, which means that Faker
knew he could TP to mid and pressure
them off the Baron. I think they were a
little slow. They probably could have uh
gotten a little bit more done.
Ruby went gold, then Doran went gold,
and then Doran went dead.
I just don't think it really matters for
the game cuz even with the Rebel Baron
power play, it's it's 500 gold. It's
probably going to be maybe a thousand if
they're lucky by the end of it. Maybe it
just stays around this, but they are not
going to be able to contest the drake. I
think it might be a negative.
Um could be. Yeah,
is that's that's my sum summation of how
it's going to look. This carrier is
going to limp away from that one.
He's five level. How is we haven't
really talked about the levels yet. How
is ruler level 16? Um,
it's a really good question.
And then and then owner is is 14 and so
is
one heck of a of a buff.
It is. What is it? It's so it's 39
pedals for Geng. And we got to keep our
eye on the Yeah. Where where's the I
can't see the pedal counter. Oh, do you
have to look at the character?
No, I I looked at the character.
I like the pedal counter that we had.
Equalizer is used here towards the top
side. And then yeah, this was the chobby
golden Doran golden.
Yeah, you got to flip it, right? I like
Doran being that far up when you don't
have control of your jungle. Obviously,
most likely backfires. But I think at
this point, if you're T1 and you're
like, ah, we're looking at next game.
Losing on blue side though, bit of a
rough one. And again, a lot of good
champions have already been taken away
by Genji.
It's a very good point. One thing that
we did learn though is that even though
Genji have already qualified for Worlds
as of their last match,
which is
they are not looking to slow down um at
any point in time. They could take a
vacation if they felt like it and they
would still be there for the world
championship as they have made playoffs
of the LCK already as Chobby is going to
throw out his ultimate but only onto
Owner and then just runs away. He has
phase rush and is going to get pop
blossom. They're going to see whether
they can take him down, but he goes
golden. The tempered fate to make people
even more golden as finally is going to
get taken out, but unfortunately the
trade I think is going to be a little
too great. That being said, killing
Choby probably feels great. Um, and
that's the best they're going to get
because their nexus is about to explode.
Hey, they got six stacks off of the
Madax as well.
Oh, that is a really good point. Um,
Faker is it's curtains does manage to
almost take down Canyon here. That was
very close as Carrier is likely going to
get booped. That is a decent little
captain Jack there from Ruler, but
unable to quite kill him. And so Carrier
will be able to watch on as his nexus
goes down. But T1 will drop this one.
Genji looking poised to hit that number
28.
Two main characters for me in that one.
Uh, on one hand, the monkey. Uh, I've
been talking a lot about monkeys for
obvious reasons.
Monkey. Yeah, but big monkey performance
there uh from Canyon. The other one is
Duro. The This is something we keep
going back to with this player
just locking in a champion and more and
more champions that he's added to his
champion pool. That game five pike from
MSI I will not forget.
It's not something that he's known for.
It's something his opponent is known
for. And his Bart performance was crazy
in this game. Was able to make a huge
impact. Really lean into the creativity
that Bard allows you to have as well. I
I just think that that play in the river
was one of the greatest that we've seen
ever. And of course, Chobi finding the
shock wave was the biggest one.
But
it's how it comes together.
Yeah. And the followup, the fact that
the Tempered Fate was there to make sure
that Canyon was set up for
just absolutely exquisite. And you can
see, yeah, it was already drifting
towards Gen. And that cliff you can see
there, that is um
that's a fiveman. That's that little red
A there.
Yeah,
cuz we knew before and cuz that's
highlighted. I think that Genji was
always going to have T1 on a timer. I
think their 5v5 is just insane with this
composition. I just didn't expect it to
happen like an item and a half in.
No, I didn't either. Really impressive
stuff here from Geng. They've been
impressive for a very long time. T1
though, they have been stalwart. Let's
see whether they can sort things out,
get back on the horse, and bring us
three games because T like Genji, they
often go the distance in their series.
So hopefully they're generous here for
the LCK Road Show, the T1 home ground,
they give us a full three game. We have
short go for a short break when we get
back. The space going to break that one
down.
Heat.
[Music]
[Applause]
Heat.
[Music]
Okay. Oh,
rubber.
Okay.
[Music]
[Applause]
Wow.
I don't get it.
[Music]
Hey.
Hey. Hey.
[Music]
W.
I feel again.
I am.
[Music]
Hello and welcome to the space. We are
here after game number one of Genji up
against T1 and that one was kind of even
for the early game, but eventually
Chov's shockwave found them all and the
game kind of just ended from there. I'm
Valdez. We do have Wol and Wadid joining
us today. How do you guys feel about
that game number one? It was a pretty
close game at the beginning, right?
Faker had a great laning phase. A lot of
resources were given to him. He baited
uh them into that that play in the mid
lane. Was able to get a kill there. The
Annie looked like it was going to get
online and the team composition here for
T1 from ahead is so hard for Genji to
play into, but they made a few mistakes
after the early game and Genji just ran
away with it. This kind of has been a
trend for so many teams that nearly stop
Genji's streak but aren't quite able to.
Yeah. Uh we just want to mainly focus
about the Anie because now it's
considered as one of the best pick in
the mid lane. Uh the record is 50 not
considering this game. Uh it was first
uh lose on the Annie, but uh it was not
the Annie's fault uh because Annie is
one of the strong game power spike pick
because that's what all it matters in
this meta cuz you want to stack all
drakes and any is just really strong
until uh three items. The three item
power spike is just insane. And also
it's so easy to set up with the fight
with any because it's just target CC and
there's not many counter plays against
any W flash. So that's why uh T1 could
snowball the early game, but they just
messed up around the the first highlight
because they just didn't fight with any
and it's OP, but what's the point if you
don't fight with it?
Yeah, they took the skirmish the wrong
way. They took it the wrong way. And we
can take a look at some of the early
highlights. Let's take a look at
highlight number one. Actually, 12
minutes in, we had this fight in the
jungle of T1 that owner seemed to know
about and went head first into ends up
being a win in the end for Gen. They
don't have any setup here and Owner
knows this as you say Valdez and just
because you know doesn't necessarily
mean it's the right play. Don't forget
also that during this play even though
it ends up being a trade here for T1
where they do end up picking up a double
for GMA. Joy is also free pushing on the
top side and Vaker is just simply not
here. So this is where a lot of the
tempo is actually lost for T1 in this
game despite the Corki getting two kills
there. Genji gets so much space. They
get so much control over the map. Yeah,
even though they uh chain Gento the mid
lane, I feel like Canyon was always
ahead in tempo. I think just because of
the bolt lane matchup, I feel like Corki
Nico should have priority cuz Vi was
covering in the early game uh flows, but
I feel like them messing up the B boat
play was kind of uh bad news for Vi cuz
he was not able to get the tempo back
against Ukong. And I think that causes a
lot of issues in the map control here.
Yeah, it absolutely did. And uh not 3
minutes later, 15 minutes in for
highlight 2 here. The bot dive did come
through for Gen G with just added insult
to injury here in this early game.
This one is the most egregious one for
me because you know the game state right
like Carrie is here trying to cover but
gets cut off. Look where Canyon is. He's
like doing topside scuttle or something
and ends up going mid and trying to make
a play there. Just completely gone,
right? They end up getting the the
successful dive there taking Doran out
and then making the play top side
getting a solo kill. Canon's not
involved in either play and Genji went
on both sides of the map as Faker gets
soloed by Keen and Ruler's just chilling
like he doesn't have a outer in mid but
he's so far back that the play Canyon
looks for there in mid just doesn't work
out and it's just better play it's a
jungle uh gap here in in this first game
in owner right for those
yeah sorry canyon is the one making a
successful player is the one who's you
know on the top side and then trying to
make the play in mid well then we had
the highlights to rule them all which
was one of the best highlights maybe all
year we're going to get. This was
highlight number three where Chovi's
shockwave finds them all quite literally
as everybody just grouped up for it and
he knocked them down.
Yeah, I feel like uh Genji was just well
spread around. That's why uh they were
kind of it was really hard to find the
the angle for the team fight for T1. So
that's why they kind of hard forced the
fight here. But I feel like uh just
Genji in general, they just know where
to position themselves and I I I think
just in general uh they just had the
better plan in the team fight and the
better plan makes better plays here.
Yeah, I mean that was one of those
skirmishes. Obviously the fight that
Valdez was talking about was the big
shock wave with the Bard ultimate
layered on top and then the Wukong
ultimate, right? This composition works
incredibly well when you have map
control. We don't have the highlight
visually to show you guys, but if you
guys go look back at that play, Karia
gets a engage, right, just like he did
in that play, and it baits T1 in to a
really rough spot, but they don't know
where everyone's standing, right? They
don't have full vision. And it with
comps like this, I think vision and pryo
is way more important than gold. You
look at the gold graph in this game, for
most of the game, it's relatively close,
but Genji had so much control that the
team fights were so hard to play. And
Genji continue with their streak here.
They're going to get the first game.
Will they continue with another series
win? Let's find out going into game
number two. Back to the casters right
now.
Thank you very much, gentlemen. Yes. Uh
that highlight was actually deemed too
brutal to be shown once again. Once was
definitely enough.
It's too much.
Y
we already played it once live and then
once in the replay.
That was enough, I think.
Yeah, we're definitely not going to see
that on uh
the Mad Movie like for the next like 15
years. Uh yeah, there's I think the Mad
Movies might actually just continue um
as well. We'll just have that one in
every Mad Movie from now on. Uh is how
it's going to go. I'm looking forward to
the score esports um putting out. No,
it's not. It's It was against Faker,
wasn't it? So, they probably won't make
a video about that one.
You're on fire today. You're not just
starting fights. I'm not I'm not
starting fights. I'm just I'm just
observing a trend, okay? There's no
there's no beef. I've worked with the
score many times. Plus, are you familiar
with the concept of rage baiting?
And this is a rhetorical question
because
I have
obviously I don't have any idea what
you're talking about.
On the experiencing end of your rage
baiting for the last 4 and 1/2 years, so
I know that you do
for a fact. I feel like you're getting
with every passing year, you're adding
more tools to your arsenal. You know,
I like to try. You know, you got to you
got to add to the repertoire over the
years. It's it's how it goes. But this
is of course the T1 home ground at 2025
LCK road show and T1 needs to win a game
to give us value.
Come on.
That's all we need, right?
I want to we want to we want a game
free, right?
And it's very red in the stadium. So I
put this to you. Maybe it's time to
choose red side because maybe what Geng
thought was that everyone there because
it was so red was cheering for them
because they were on the red side.
What do you think? That's my theory.
Do you know what we didn't get? We
didn't get account.
Actually, I have a actually we didn't.
Yeah. Very upsetting. I have a very Do
you How good do you think noise
cancelling headphones are?
Not great.
Okay. Well, in that case, I don't think
that Genji is thinking.
Well, no, no, no. So, not I think noise
cancelling headphones are fantastic and
they've definitely improved throughout
the years. They're not good enough for
that for an arena.
You can see on your screen.
Well, no, that's my point. So, they will
know cuz every time team one does
something, I assume there will be loud
yelling. Yes, I imagine that there will
be a fair bit.
I hope we get free games of loud yelling
because I love that. That's what we do.
Exactly. We just got to do some more
loud yelling. Okay, we are going to dive
into this draft here. As you can see,
it's fearless. So, we're not going to be
seeing any more of these shock waves,
finding them all. Instead, it will be
once again banned on Tia. Last time
around, it was Tia, Aurora, and Gallo
taken away. And on the side of Genji,
they took away the Pantheon, the Varys,
and the Azir. I assume they're likely to
continue uh down this trend as the Azir
definitely needs to be banned given the
fact that the Tia has been taken away.
But instead, it's going to be a Zenzou.
So, the Aurora up and available
if they would like to take it. And of
course, if they wanted to play things
like the Rumble, things like the Gwen,
that's why you ban the Aurora, and now
feels a little bit less necessary.
Still do think that Aurora is just in a
good uh place right now if you have the
execution. I do I don't think it's uh
really a type of champion that you can
just plug and play into any comp. I
think it also requires funnly enough I
think it requires good execution, but if
you do, I do feel like the champion has
very little counterplay.
It's one of those champions where the
things you can do with it if you're good
feel
because of the displacement on many of
her abilities allowing her to always be
out of way as
I already wrote in Azia but instead it's
Javin.
So they're going to B1 Air and then Chi
going to like what's like slam Victor.
Oh it's it's a Y game. I can feel it.
Oh Suani Yon. Yeah, it feels it feels
like it's down those lines
that I think those are the two avenues.
We're either going to see like Akali,
Silus, or Yona, or we're going to see
Victor. Um I
I hope it's not Victor.
I hope it's not Victor. I really don't
think that that matchup is any anywhere
near as good as people have seemingly
thought it is. We are obviously
People have been trying to like that
snake oil has been on sale for so long.
You know, people keep buying it out.
I know. And and we every time we every
time we we mention, oh, you got to be
careful because you'll get you if you
don't have flesh, you'll just get to
die.
It's like your people and those tulips,
you know, it's the value is only there
if the people say it's there, you know,
and then you create a bubble and
economics crash and it's just a
disaster. And you'd think that history
would have learned, but it didn't. Okay.
Which is what happened in Japan.
That's why we have a sear versus victor
in 2025.
That's what I'm saying.
Yeah. Very very very upsetting. Um,
you're the one. You're the one wearing
orange. This is all just out. That's why
I have the Netherlands on the mind.
Oh, Zyra.
I do love me. Oh, I do love me some Guma
carrier Zyra. That is that is good
stuff. I do think it's obviously a hard
match up in lane. There is a lot of
pressure that will be applied by the
Lucian Braum. That being said, I mean,
this T1 core that they've put together
now can be augmented by so many
different things, right? Like you could
throw whatever kind of potato you want
on the top side of the map, especially
with the jungle already behind
aren't going to be coming out from the
side of Geng. They're probably going to
have to away.
And in fact, it is going to be the first
one.
I'm going to say Trundle Poppy. I think
those are the two bands. I think the
puppy also goes really well with the
Azir. T1 is really good at using it even
though they can't flex it. I think it's
also good into the Scarnner. So, I would
really like for that to be the takeaway.
Yep.
Now, I don't think T1 should ban
midlaners here cuz I don't actually
think it really matters what Chovi
picks. I think that last game also
showcased that trying to target Chovi is
maybe not the way to go cuz I it didn't
work at all and it was a lot of
resources invested and it was obviously
not really bothered.
The Aurora is going to get taken away as
mention I think Aurora is just top tier
pick right now. She is just good.
And I wonder whether you know the lack
of Sichuani that we're seeing on the
side of Genji will deter Chovi from the
Yona angle and will make it so that T1
doesn't necessarily have to ban that
thing away as the knock turn is going to
be the other band. So that Poppy you
were talking about,
okay,
is still going to be there and playing
Lucian into Poppy just doesn't feel very
good. Outside of that, I guess you're
not too worried. Although stand beside
Braum is going to be a little bit uh
more difficult.
We'll see what tier one do decide to go
with their final ban.
Will it be something like a Yona? They
wouldn't be representing very much magic
damage at all on the side of Genji. So
likely that that is not going to be a
look and it will instead be the Hay
taken a way. I actually like that. I
think playing Zia into Hi is just a very
miserable experience.
Victor, as mentioned, I think has a lot
of innate weaknesses that just won't
make you super happy to lock it in.
other things that outrange Z. We're
talking like mid Zigs. We're talking uh
I think it's Acid in game.
I could I could see that. I think you do
have to wait till five though. Keen
Sante just slam it.
Or we just play TF.
Oh.
Uh he is fresh off a nerf uh on this
patch, but it wasn't exactly, you know,
backbreaking. And I find it kind of
crazy, right? cuz I feel like TF is one
of these champions that's just never
going to be that good in solo queue
anymore just because as soon as you're
good at it in pro, it's like ridiculous.
So, the fact that it even got nerfed is
just kind of nuts.
I'm pretty sure he was also in the zero
win club.
He was in the zero win club until game
five EWC final.
Yeah, I know. And then he did kind of
and then everyone figured out why he was
being
I I want to I was at MSI. I should
remember this, but I feel like either
Chroy or Faker did pick it up at some
point and did really well with it, but
it was like one like basically the
champion was like one in I think Kalista
was winless and then
TF maybe had one played by T1 and Geng
at MSI.
That would make sense.
Both of them. I don't know whether it
was uh
successful or not
that successful or anything like it was
pulled.
I know the sentiment was that uh people
didn't like it.
Jace
Jace Okay. And some range. I like that.
one of my least favorite Sajuani
compositions. Although at least now does
work. Um, but otherwise we're going to
hope for some hammer form here from
the Jace. And yeah, we're not
representing a lot of damage on the side
of Genji.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. I've
fallen for this trap before. The the Oh,
Genji doesn't have that much damage.
This is where you're allowed to say it.
You're allowed to say it now in the
draft. Okay, cuz
and then when the damage graphs come up,
you're like, "Ah, well, you know, I
guess uh Casante is actually a damage."
So, let's let's The T1 draft I think is
very straightforward. This is an amazing
team fighting draft. You have decent
amount of pressure towards the top side
of the map. I think that what you need
to be careful for is early on. I don't
think your like uh early skirmishes are
quite as strong cuz you have Braum and
Lucian which are crazy good and then you
have the TF, right? So, I do think you
need to be careful about how you
navigate the early game. can really
easily fall behind if you take a couple
of bad skirmishes. When it comes to 5v5
though, this comp is absolutely
devastating. Has great range, has great
damage spread, has a lot of playmaker
potential, has good engage, has good it
has everything.
Yeah, self- peel as well for Gushi is
fantastic. Although when rapid fire
comes in for TF being a Zia just feels
terrible.
This comp for Genji, if it was any other
team, I would think it sucks.
Yeah,
I would just be like, I don't think you
have damage. I think these champions
just they can be okay, but I feel like
we're really lacking.
Do you know what the the best part is?
Exhibit A is the entirety of MSI,
except when it's Genji.
Exactly. Exactly right. Um so yeah, I'm
I'm also not sold. I would agree with
you. I think that uh Chroy's Twist of
Fate is built well and truly different
and has evolved over time. This was our
example earlier on in the day for a
reason. And we'll see whether we're
going to look silly with pie on our face
after T1 bring us to a third game or
whether it's Genji just continuing the
uh trend towards 28 in a row.
There was yelling earlier.
Yeah, I just thought that maybe this
time around we'd get there, but we just
didn't get there. So,
it's okay. It's okay. We still had the
yelling. It might have been that we had
them like earlier on or something like
that. Or maybe there's like a time time
difference scenario.
I'm not entirely sure.
It's fine either way. I don't need fan
chance. All right.
I actually uh I made a post about this
as well during MSI. So there are for me
say that you the classic scenario like
aliens are invading and we need we need
a we need a setup that wins us a 5v5
league game against the aliens,
right? And there were two duos that I
named.
So it's kind of like the
base. Yeah. Yeah. Basically like who
would you want when your when your life
is on the line when everything comes
down to it. One of the combos was Guma
on Za carry on cuz I've I've seen them
do trulant
with Kenyon Nidley.
That's a pretty good one. Um now we
don't have the Nidi so I'm a little
worried for Genji. It's really what I
was kind of heading towards.
Yeah. I I didn't quite know where you
were going, but you did get somewhere.
Um the whole alien invasion thing really
threw me.
Have you never Have you never seen that?
It's like a very common
Space Jam. Yes.
Well, no, but like the sentiment of
everything is on the line, who do you
ask to, you know, if I'm so like in Game
of Thrones where like uh Tyrion asks for
um for a second comes in
if I if I was arguing about League of
Legends minutia, I would pick as my
champion. And I know I, you know, like
in that way.
Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep.
That that's kind of what I'm
what I'm leaning towards. If I needed
someone that would make an argument for
why Blast Con suck with a Brenda fellas
right there.
Yep. I do think that Faker being on Azir
is also a pretty good one.
That's maybe that's all you'd need.
And honestly, T1 has a large selection
of things that they're pretty used to
playing. Um, Onus Suani has been up or
down as Canyon is going to pop into this
top lane to pay Doran a visit. See
whether they do get a flash and they do.
So Doran is going to make his way out,
but does have to use a pretty important
summoner spell. Now Kane going to be
feeling much better in that lane.
Although he wasn't feeling great earlier
on. Bit of a drive by here by Owner as
he moves towards the top side. Has
cleared out his entire bottom side. And
it is going to be now up to Canyon to
head towards his bot side jungle. See if
Kane is able to use that.
The early level's going to be really
rough. Post six, you obviously have a
lot more kill threat, so should be
looking better afterwards. Canyon
actually interesting popping here. So,
full topside player into attempt to gank
towards top. Doesn't actually get the
wall slam. That could have been the
difference maker between actually
getting a kill, but without that not
going to be the case. Still gets the
flash and isn't really that far behind.
Is about like a camp behind, I think,
when all is said and done. Yep. Although
as I'm looking isn't doesn't even look
like that's really the case. Owner also
showing mid earlier on as we do have
Canyon now done with his Gromp. And as
expected, Thor and Ruler should have
cryo in his laning phase for uh the
foreseeable future unless we see anyone
on the Genji bot side mess up. There are
a lot of spell books as well. Want to
highlight that. So we have the supports
as expected. Then we have TF as well as
Owner as oh Faker.
Yeah, Canyon going to pop on over but
doesn't quite get his claws into the
pigeon.
So Faker will be able to back away.
Owner secures the crab. Crab answered on
the bottom side. And Canyon actually
waiting a little bit before he takes his
blue buff. You can see it is still up.
So only going to be popping over now
looking for a little bit of an entry
towards Chovi. We'll be able to find an
angle. We'll see whether they can
actually get a flash, but Canyon's going
to move on over. And now they get the
gold card onto the Siguani just to make
sure that uh these red dots can continue
to be consumed by Chovi stacking that
deck over and over again. As I do love
that as soon as Chovi won that game on
the Twisted Fate, everyone learns all of
this intricate stuff about TF just
because he was making so much money. The
fact that now they understand that
loaded dice is actually loaded and
they're like, "Why does he keep getting
six?" That's because that's kind of how
the champion is supposed to work.
Look at that face and tell me that that
doesn't look like a man that you would
not want to play in a fair card game.
Cuz there won't be a fair card game,
Atlas.
Yeah, it's Channing Tatum. Absolutely.
You didn't watch uh the most recent
Deadpool and Wolverine movie?
I have he he played um what's his face?
Never mind. Got a bit of an engage here
towards the bottom side of the map.
Ruler dashing on in. But carrier gets
himself out of there. We do have the
feathers pulled back, but no one's going
to get rooted. So I believe this will be
a stalemate. Do get the concussive blows
onto owner who takes a fair bit of
damage but everyone on Geng is looking a
little worse for wear. I think now it's
time to pull this one back as okay never
mind. We are coming in for another
engage. Canyon looking for a bit of an
angle there. Throws a rock around but
otherwise it is not too much.
Good amount of action there towards the
bot side of the map. Going to be
favorable for Geng. The summoner trades
actually going to benefit them as they
only invested the heal where T1 had to
invest flashes for both GMA and Carrier.
Yeah, kind of crazy that the flash
exchange was that bad for T1 as Toby
throws out a gold card in mid.
I think the the big thing was that Gmba
tried to get the recall and build,
right? Like if he gets the recall, that
mean they kill ruler, but he uses flash,
wasn't forced, was a voluntary and did
end up costing. And if you had have got
RE's flash for it, which is often what
you get going for those plays, it could
have worked out. As Flash does come on
through, Choby utilizing his as well.
Feels a little bit less punishing when
you can exchange that for a new summoner
spell. The teleport comes in from Duro
making his way back to lane. Feels like
it's a more action-packed early game,
but we've had less kills. It's kind of
interesting.
It's been Canyon. Canyon actually been
one of the biggest criticisms we've had
for him for a long time is that he is
just not that active as Oh, Keen.
Yeah, owner going to get that flash.
Nice. And Doran's just about to come
back off cool down as well. So a kind of
big deal as the Jace will have even a
flash advantage on top of the fact that
he is having a real good time in lane.
So Canyon's been very active with the
biggest piece of criticism for Kang
obviously often is that isn't that
active, but he's been matched by Owner,
right? Owner was there in bot to counter
the gank timing. Owner now forces to
flash towards top side. Also has been
hovering around mid. I I we are seeing a
bit of a problem developing though,
which is that as you highlight like TF
should always be ahead. Probably
shouldn't be two kills worth of gold uh
7 minutes in. That is a little bit
ridiculous.
Yeah.
Um he's just uh having a good time.
Does have his
Yeah, I don't I don't think you're
killing here. the amount of times we saw
Keenh. Okay, he's gone all out though as
now the destiny coming towards the top
side and yeah, the Sichuani was here but
she can't save him from that. That is
first blood going over to the Casante
and now life is way better. Yeah, Canyon
in position towards his bottom side.
They do have vision. They know exactly
where he is.
Well, there's cleanse and heal as well.
Yeah,
see whether the Grim can keep alive now.
Faker's roaming as They're like, "No,
no, no, no, no, no, no."
Yeah, not worth it. Uh, Trophy has a rod
of ages at 7 minutes, 8 minutes.
That's not
Um, so he'll have that one stacked up.
It's going to be low value though, guys.
Uh, because of course the later levels,
the more valuable ones to get and he'll
have it fully stacked before he gets to
those later levels. That was first
blood.
You're you're a glass half full kind of
guy. Kind of love it
for T1. That was a glass half full for
T1. And that was sarcasm because Genji
are pretty happy with the fact that he
picks up a full item.
The one the one big lead that they had
was towards the top side of the map. And
that kill on key
is a big deal.
You know how you were saying it's two uh
kills worth of gold.
Yeah. It's it's almost free.
Yeah.
So that's the thing we don't really need
to we'll we'll we'll circle back and
we'll have a bit more of a chat about
further down the line.
It's always what what do you actually
get out of the lead, right? like
yeah,
but as you highlight starting to stack
your rowa early I think is really
valuable.
Just having a full item in general
compared to Faker who's only sitting on
components is a big deal. The grubs were
spread two to one. So one for Genji, two
for T1. Yep. And also like for Twisted
Fate, you just kind of want to get to
your rapid fire cannon and your lich
banes and things like this as quickly as
possible. I feel like his build adds so
much utility to his kit along the way.
And so the acceleration in gold really
going to be very helpful there.
Something we've been talking about for
millennia is what it kind of feels like.
If he's been virtually unchanged, right,
for the longest time.
We do have Canyon just continuously
trying, but maybe gets a maybe it's old.
There's the Impale almost catches in max
range, but Faker a little bit faster
than Canyon was expecting.
Faker still at his old as well, so I
think Canyon knew like if he flashes
doesn't really do anything. He just
wastes his flash. not going to do that.
And we do need to reiterate T1's comp
scales
monstrously well. The only particularly
into team fight.
Yeah, the the only part that doesn't
scale super well is obviously with Jace
and like I think even in Jace's case,
Jace to me is just one of those
champions now that just kind of always
is good. Like I I
going to get exhausted here as he does
cleanse it. Carrier looks for the charm,
but he gets the flash instead. And
honestly, I think T1 are going to be
pretty happy about that. But that is two
summoner spells for the price of none.
Yeah, big mistake there from Ruler cuz
Duro wasn't around. So he had to play a
little bit more safe. Did not do so. We
do have Canyon maybe looking for a play
towards bot side. Goomba has his old but
I think there really is too big of an
angle here.
Yeah, there's a little bit of a knock up
on Canyon, but he's immune to damage is
what it looks like. He's got two belts,
so his pants are well and truly held up.
Maybe he's like one is the pen and then
the other is like over the chest like
one of the cool belts. I mean like a
technical
with this skin. You don't even have
legs. So I don't know what the pants are
doing. But he does have two belts for
them.
So it's double cross, you know, like
across the chest. And he just has like a
bunch of
Oh no, he's got two belts because you
need two belts around the caterpillar
track things that he's got.
Oh, different kind of belt. Oh, yep.
It's I was just thinking about the wrong
belt.
I I I'm sorry I didn't back you up.
Actually, he can have two more belts cuz
he also has the things on his arms. All
right. So, we need to build more belts.
Um, Canyon needs to make sure that he
gets a gets a gets a Warmog on the way.
I also Yeah. Well, I also have seen a
good amount of Twitter discourse about
like actually the optimal You might not
like it, but peak tank performance is
just building giant belts.
Well, then it it also makes sense
because he needs so many belts cuz he's
a machine.
Yep.
It's glorious. Well, Destiny is um not
exactly kind to Doran here towards the
top side of the map as going all out.
Not sure if he's going all in and Doran
is real dead. That is a kill going over
to the Twisted Fate. Um, and we we're
talking about a kill worth of gold.
Well, he has that now as Flash is going
to be invested here by Duro to get
himself out of the way of the Emperor's
Divide, but he's still moving forward.
Ruler lit on fire here as Ona comes on
over with a summoner spell that he
didn't have at the beginning of the
game.
Love that. Owner with the aura ignite.
You love to see it as Troas now parked
himself on the top side of the map and
he's going to look to take that one
down. And that should give T1 a bit of
an angle towards this dragon. Bit of a
check-in when it comes to feats of
strength and how we're doing there. If
T1 do manage to take down this dragon,
then they'll only need another objective
to be able to lock down that portion as
Genji one kill away from the feats of
warfare.
And Chobi is getting to work on this
turret to the point where we might need
to be talking about first turret blood
as well. I don't know whether he's going
to take it on this push cuz that is
going to be a Keech dragon. King finding
a little queue and is going to be eating
a bunch of CC and feeling happy about it
as
not again. Not again. Not again. Not
again.
He just got back.
He doesn't want the dying spree. Not a
dying spree as that's a bit of a
driveby. Doesn't quite work here for
Canyon as Chovi does find a blue card.
Sure about that one as Doran's going to
be able to take down the scanner. And
it's a disaster here for Geng as T1 even
out the kills and well and truly strike
back. carry up the hero that Doran
needed.
Making sure that his top laner stays
alive after these continued dives. And
now all of a sudden T1 is winning on
multiple sides of the map. They're able
to push in and bot fully keen off the
turret as Chovi.
Yeah, this is a big deal if they can
lock down this kill. And they got three
people here. He wants to deal with the
minions that are in position as he
flashes away from his turret. And that
is going to mean that he's dead. Cute
little gold card towards the end there,
but not going to be able to get too
much. He still has a massive gold lead,
but he's now not on the map. And Genji
kind of falling apart at the scenes. We
were talking about the feats of warfare
that Genji was so close to getting. T1
just claimed it. And now they just need
to get another dragon, a herald,
something like that, they'll be sitting
pretty bit sloppy there for Genji cuz
they could have called this off. I think
the moment they spot that Raan.
Yeah. But instead, if Kenyan just
flashes out instead of trying to prime
with the ultimate, I think they just get
out instead and they're fine. But they
try to actually make it work. Timely
arrival from Guma to catch there as
well. And then I like that T1 also, they
know where everyone is on the map,
right? They know that Duro and Keen are
bot. They just killed Scarnner as well
as the Lucian. So they can just dive
Chobi there and T1 on an even game
state. I'll take them anytime. Every
time. The amount of damage this team has
is incredible. And I I we have seen
Genji play this exact composition in
late game. And I think it can be done.
It's very poke heavy, right? You just
gold card, do some poke, back off.
Yeah. And you can play it in a 1 131
things like that. More of a full one. I
guess
there are ways, but by default, if
you're T1 and you get to two items, you
get to free items, you're going to be
feeling amazing. You're going to have
intense amounts of damage. You're going
to have, I think, as long as you
actually stick together, not a lot of
weak spots, not a lot of people that are
easily targeted, right? There's a lot of
mobility, there's a lot of beefiness.
Really, only Doran can be found. And
between Owner and Carrie, I don't think
they're going to let his their body go
down that easily.
Just have to see whether Genji can find
some of that magic or whether this is
indeed going to be that threeame series
that I think we all want.
Would like that, especially most of
Inchan. um as they are all there in the
stadium.
Let's just see as Gumushi taking a lot
of damage there. And in fact, the
culling comes on out here from Ruler.
Owner going to be blocking that one, but
Gumushi is out of this fight now. Does
have to eat the honey fruit. Chia's old.
Got to be a little careful.
Yeah. Uh probably doesn't want to use it
because I think Chovi prefer just to be
parked in lane. Does actually throw out
the destiny. Hasn't gated around just
yet as the gold card does come on
through. But that is a big cool down
that they now take as he makes his way
back towards the rest of his team. Yushi
does have half of his health bar back up
once again, but Canyon has position now
on this Rift Herald. It looks like Geng
might be the ones to claim that one as
Ruler parked in mid is going to put on
that extra pressure. Are they actually
going to get it off that? That's crazy.
Kind of ridiculous.
Uh I think T1 is still going to look for
the contest. And look, Faker making his
way over.
Yeah, let's see whether the pigeon can
find the angle as the glacial prison
doesn't quite get there as now Chovy
gets the gold card onto Faker. And now
for the rest of the fight, Canyon going
down. extraordinarily low. There's the
jungler out of it. Emperor's Divide not
really finding it, but it pushes them
out of the pit as Keane. He's gone all
out, but he is in fact all out. Double
knock up there from Carrier as well.
Looking fantastic. Rule the front
lining. Doesn't want to as he flashes to
get out of the way. And that is Faker on
the board with a kill on Duro that he
was looking for before. And Choby not
going to get hit by that grand entrance,
but I still think he's in a bit of
trouble here as Ruler wanting to try and
catch them off guard as another gold
card is locked in. Wild cards actually
hitting all of them there as somehow
it's Faker that managed to just take
down Ruler. Chroy will survive and T1
limp away.
But T1 going to be happy with that one.
Herold found fight one. Mid lane turret
sieged. Possible setup towards Drake as
well. Now the gold blade firmly in their
favor and a 402 Z as well. Quick blades
now completed. Kumishi, he's pretty
ridiculously good on this champion. And
let's have a look at it once again as
this was an awkward fight. You know, it
was on all sorts of different fronts,
but T1 play it masterfully.
The big thing for me is that Faker zones
out together with Goomba at the start.
Three of the members of Geng. And like
despite some true keen Sante heroics, he
can't actually 1v9, right? That's not a
thing that you can do. So, he does get
taken down eventually by GMA, by Doran.
So the setup of the fight is really nice
for T1 and if Genji can't actually blow
up a member individually or poke away.
We do see that comp struggle a little
bit as Ruler and Chovi try to clutch
this fight out. But the flash forward
from Guma not afraid finds the kill.
That's now another drake going over to
T1 and I think thus far we are looking
good
although Dor might be caught.
This is a really awkward position here
as Canyon walks over the ward. They get
the information here with the destiny as
there is the glacial fissure and oh the
emperor's divide by faker is glorious as
they lock down chovi. They'll also take
the scanner as well as kumushi in a
little bit of trouble here as Keen
manages to get one back but it's only on
to Doran and T1 are now chasing down the
remaining stragglers of Genji and they
do it so so well with this composition.
There is the culling. It doesn't really
do too much of anything at all as the
perafrost not going to connect onto Duro
there, but he has to flash to get out of
the way and they'll trade Doran for a
whole bunch more here as T1 move to 10
and four and JG is tenacious but T1 he's
getting the better end of them anyway.
Faker having big impact on this Azir
consistently finding the plays and
despite the gold lead which by the way
is dwindling.
Yeah and that gold lead for Chroy is now
down to 700. That's more than haveved.
It's kind of ridiculous.
It is the dwindling gold lead.
Oh, that's the gold lead.
Well, there was a lot of dwindling gold
leads to Atlas. Um, as we as we
highlighted, it's very nicely done here.
There's no flash for Chobi, so he just
ends up dying there. Canyon, even if he
hits more people, I don't think it
really does anything. Cute there that he
gets the wall slam on the Doran.
That is funny. And then here there's the
attempt, but I actually think this old
from Keen doesn't quite hit the mark. I
think he probably was looking to drag
him over the wall like into the pit and
play from there.
Gets his feather storm off cool down
right there,
right at the wrong time. And but also
the fact that he basically drags Desire
towards his team, right?
Uh not what he was looking for. Also
good there from Guma. I think that might
have been just allowing uh what allowed
him to reposition in a way that
made that play work. And I think right
now things are looking really good for a
game number three Atlas T1. The only
thing they need to ensure is don't throw
out a card. I think that that's that's
really it. You have an incredibly
scaling composition. Be careful about
the side lanes. Genji do still have a
lot of burst on single members. If they
can zone someone off, beacon sees what
T1. They're death balling and I think
they should. Yeah, it's working. Carrier
does move into this tri brush. They get
control vision in the area. The other is
just gone. Just going down and Genji no
real right to head over there. Vision is
paramount and they have none of it and
so Genji just going to settle with an
outer turret in mid.
Kuman carry out the Zion Raan.
The team fighting of D2 has been
incredible.
Look for this as Ona comes on over. They
clear out the wave. Concussive blows and
nothing really happens here as that was
a cleanse of the air from Chovi.
Come on, bro. You got to trust Duro.
Trust your buddy. Dura would never would
never let that hit you.
I mean, the hit box of the glacial
prison is a bit funky. Maybe that was
atlas. It's about trust. If you ever
tell me to catch that skill shot for
you,
Yeah, exactly.
I would I would trust you blind, I
probably die because of it, but it'd be
worth it.
And I tell you, you should have claimed.
Anyway, T1 going to be able to secure
their blue buff and now look to put more
pressure on the map. And it's so hard
now as Genji's composition to play the
game because look at Chovy. He is
running away from the minion wave. Uh
that is precisely not what you want to
be doing as the Twisted Fate. You want
to continue that pressure as much as
possible. And if you do have control of
the map, then you can utilize it. In
this case, he absolutely cannot.
It's just rough. Now you're getting
perma slowed by the Azir. There are
three targets you need to deal with cuz
all of them have enough damage to carry
a team fight. There is great front line,
great engage. this T1 composition. I
think we saw in the early game what
could go wrong. Some of the picks kind
of highlighted how Genji would like to
play, but here I think we're going to
need to see both a crazy Jenji team
fight and I think it comes down to does
Gmba live? If Gmba gets taken out
somehow by the Keen Sante or Chi finds a
crazy flank, maybe that can be
something, but realistically T1 should
be able to get themselves the sole point
here. And is the soul the biggest deal?
Not really. But for Genji's comp, trying
to actually chew for some of extra uh
damage resistance is still nice. There's
that RFC, but I don't know if it's going
to be enough. Trying to get himself out
of here. Does manage to dash away. Holds
onto the flash for the moment. 50% of
his health is now missing.
It's a tough one as T1 just continue
this relentless pressure. Joby has found
a lane, but look at this. The poke on
Ruler is just kind of gigantic and the
rest of T1 just continuing to push
forward. They'll take down this inner
turret very comfortably with four
members and Canyon just not quite here
in time to try and alleviate anything as
Keen comes on over and is trying to
defend against Faker's push but it is
unrelenting. Does take a lot of damage
here from the Keen Sante as the Empress
Divide is going to have to be employed.
That means that T1 do not have that if
there is going to be a bit of a team
fight. The glacial prison also was
thrown out earlier on as carrier looks
for a bit of an angle here. Gets the
charm onto Chovi.
So T1 not really hard committing as it's
a fight for a Gromp guys. Um there's the
destiny and okay Toby thinks that this
is maybe an angle. Shifting sands does
get Faker out of there and remember this
is three items onto Choby now. Maybe
it's an opportunity but you can see the
culling just kind of hitting the air and
now T1 they can back away if they'd like
to. Would they like a team fight? That
is our question. But without the Empress
Divide perhaps they do not want it.
Well Cheni is slow playing this. do have
Doran probably looking for a base and
immediately TPing back. There's a good
amount of flank angles behind them.
Yeah, there is a mega cone here as well
for Troy if you'd like to utilize it.
Oh, Doran. Yeah, there is the teleport
in as Doran diving on top of Kane here
as Joby holding on to this gold card for
such a long time. Carrier comes on over
and there is the all out. It is going to
be the secure on the dragon with that
unsealed spell book from Duro as
Canyon's just going to drive his way out
as best he can. Down goes Doran as Geni,
they slow down Carrier as well. And I
don't think he's long for this world as
the Ardan Blaze will be able to tag him.
So, he's not going to be executing
himself just yet. And so, Genji able to
deny the soul and will also find
themselves I could you call it a fight?
I guess you could call it a fight.
I'm kind of in awe that that worked. I I
guess it's the power of No Emperor's
Divide for a while.
So, there's a lot of layers to it.
There's the Oh, Trophy might be dead. So
there's the power of no emperor thereby.
There is also T1. We keep talking about
hook at their fighters that isn't a
frontto back scenario where you have
owner and carrier standing for this is a
skirmish like this is a broken up messy
fight and GNG are simultaneously forcing
T1 to respond to dragon cuz if T1 fully
commit to either side I think they have
a large angle to win the fight even
without the ultimate but instead Chovi
and Keen are two between Dor and a car
they're going to win that right like
between the TF and the Keen Sante that's
no biggie and then on the other
If it was any other Casante, that would
have been a very difficult fight.
Oh, I I I I think that that might have
been rough. But
maybe not Dundon.
Don't remind me, bro. I I don't want to.
That's like a whole another
conversation. I I I I don't I He's in
the LC now. You know, he's it which is
nice.
He's riding, you know.
Well, I uh don't Let's not Let's not
talk about all reliable, okay? It's too
much. But he did teach us that Grump is
important as Geng startup Nash.
Yeah. This is what they learned from T1.
And the just start up the baron if you
finding an angle or did T1 find a Chobi?
Chobi kind of knew that this was what
was happening. He doesn't have an arm
guard so he's just dead. And now the
quickness goes all over the rest of
Geng. Can they find it? No, they cannot.
The Emperor's Divide throws them into
the mix. And now Ona trying to dash his
way out. Ruler is doing a decent job,
but Gumushi just getting on in there. My
god, he slaughterers them. It's a triple
kill for the Z. and T1 say well I guess
we'll take a Baron.
Uh maybe if you have flash and ZAS
Chovy. Oh Kane's going to die isn't he?
Ah I've seen these before. Jonah strong.
I know what's coming.
Hey no but he got he got the raptor.
Actually I don't even like Doran doesn't
have a whole lot of health. Um so
if it was just Doran and he didn't know
that it was just Doran.
He has a he has a lot of whis it would
have been fine. Uh
my only read is like I I actually I
don't know like cuz you know where
everyone is.
Yeah. It's not even like ET not you know
where everyone is. Chobi just goes too
deep. The response from and this is the
front to back. Look at this. We have
Guma and Faker doing damage. On the
front and a beautiful from him and then
Ruler actually does take down Kara is
trying to make and then Guma just
flashes in. uh does a really good job.
Gets all the damage out.
I think Faker's disappointed that uh
Choby died so early because it was a
fiveman shock wave in game one, but
there were only four alive to hit with
the Emperor's Divide in game two.
Y
Oh, it's completely unfair. Um it would
have been five five if Chovi hadn't have
just sort of
gated his way into death. Okay,
so we'll give them an even on that
front.
It's just it's classic Chobi, you know,
he's just calibrating how to make more
plays. That was that one is going in the
data set is not it.
Yeah, it was not quite it.
That was that was not I I do think it
was already a Hillary, right? Starting
the Baron in the first place trying to
look for that turn, but
he can make the play now. He's got his
arm guard.
Well, the game is done now. So I I I I
think the game was already in a rough
spot. That play was, don't get me wrong,
that play was bad. I think that the fact
that they started up Nash kind of shows
that Jen also knows that they're a
little cooked.
Are getting that sick cleanse. Yeah,
this game is looking mighty over and I
love that Atlas. That's That's good cuz
that means
the series ain't over
which which I love that we have gotten
max games for Geng1 in what the last
How many has it been cuz it was the two
and
so was both out of MSI they didn't face
and ros MSI round I think round robin
two was a two I think round robin one
was incredible but round robin two I
remember being a bit of a let down
yeah it wasn't it wasn't super hard not
this one Atlas
not this time around as we move into our
first ever round three as we get a zoom
in on the gold card being collected by
the bird that was flapping away. So,
that's not going to eventuate in
anything at all. Bounties now up and
available here if Genji can ever get out
of their base. But, I just don't know
whether that's ever happening. 20
seconds on this dragon would be soul
point for either team.
So, they don't have to play for the next
RA cuz they got the last one, which is
nice thanks to Duro Smite. But
maybe they will anyway.
Well, I don't I hope they don't cuz
they're also playing. But to what end is
what I ask you, Atlas? because the dead
nexus
well do you really want this game to go
like what are you playing for there's
not normally in these type of situations
they're like
I mean that's a that's a much deeper
question than you may think because
team's already qualified for worlds so
what are they playing for chronic
to keep the streak alive
yeah but I they they've been in
interviews and they're like yeah we
don't really care we just want to play
well
which I I tend to believe
I mean these are competitors if they had
the mindset of I guess we take a holiday
now then they wouldn't be the player.
They wouldn't be they wouldn't be on the
streak. Yeah.
Um there's also that statement is then
always followed followed up by we just
want to do well at worlds which
that's everyone.
Yep.
That's that's how it goes.
It is something that they haven't quite
managed to achieve just yet.
Need a heal marry here. Maybe a
multi-man from Canyon. Otherwise, we go
in the game free.
Oh, there's the destiny to come in there
as they found Canyon on the flank. He
only gets Ona with the ulti as now
Gumishi is in a little bit of trouble,
but he's got the feather storm. He's
buying so much time and the Emperor's
Divide to get him out of there as well.
Ruler is the one that's down so low as
they trade 80 carries as now Keane dives
in, but he cannot pick anyone up. And
it's Doran finding his revenge. He'll
also get cleansed. Everything is fine.
And now Chrovy and Duro versus the world
as the teleport to get Chroy out of
there will be interrupted by Ona as
Doran says, "Yeah, we are going to a
game three." And I'm going to take us
there by destroying these nexus turrets.
And he's getting some revenge after
being bullied earlier on. These health
bars aren't going down as fast as they
really wanted to as Chobby flashes out
of the Grand Entrance. And we're just
going to zoom in here on Doran booping
down this nexus with his hammer. gets
the gun out there as well just to show
that it can transform. That was real
cute. There's a demonstration of that 50
gold that I was talking about. That is
very, very important to bring us to game
three.
[Music]
T1 team fighting will bring us to a game
number three, a Genji composition that
had us going, I don't know about that,
but it's Geng. and then turned out
they have made comps like that work in
the past but against everything they
gave to T1 that's the real problem and
this is a conversation that uh was had
on the desk yesterday as well sometimes
you look at your composition you're like
yeah
I love that composition
and then you look over to the other one
you're like ah that one's better
that one was better and uh in this case
I think the execution from team one was
also great they did have to navigate the
early again we saw a slight lead uh
eventuate there, but particularly
carryon, right? I think his turning
blade towards the top side ended up
being really big for Genji uh or for
rather for T1 to turn this area around
and for Genji to kind of stop losing
that or start losing that momentum
because you can see I think that dive is
right where that little gold lead
evaporates
and then you had the big team fight and
then the game really became a struggle
from that point on. We won't talk about
that weird dragon scenario and all that
sort of stuff that happened afterwards.
It was fun.
It was a bit of a blip,
but it was distraction.
It was and it didn't really mean too
much. So T1, they will even it out. We
will go to three. Time for us to take a
short break. When we get back, the space
going to break that one down. Then we'll
have the deciding game between T1 and
Geng. Will it be T1 that breaks the
streak at the T1 home ground? Find out
after this.
[Music]
Heat
up here.
[Music]
Get
ready.
What did you
[Applause]
do again? Let's go.
[Music]
How about
this? for
[Music]
Now I'm gay.
Heat. Heat.
[Music]
Heat. Hey, Heat.
Hey,
hey, hey.
hey,
hey.
[Music]
Hey, hey,
hey.
[Music]
Oh,
I want Heat. Heat. N.
[Music]
I feel
[Applause]
you.
[Music]
Hello and welcome back to the space. I
can say proudly that we do have a series
on our hands now as T1 was able to take
game number two away from Gen G. Gen
with a pretty interesting draft. Didn't
quite work out for them after that top
dive and T1 was able to take the game
from there. are pretty interesting
stuff. Guys, what do you think about
that game?
I really want to talk about the draft
because while Geng are an incredibly
strong team and they can make almost
anything work, uh they had a very
similar draft to this at the EWC finals
in game five, right? But I think they
may have forgotten that they got a duo
kill on Hope and Kyle early in that game
and Ruler was super accelerated because
in order to win this game, you need your
Lucian to be ahead. You need to have map
control the entire time because you just
otherwise don't have damage. Sure, TF
can gold card somebody, but if you can't
kill them, it doesn't really matter. And
I think T1's comp was just way stronger
and way safer.
I mean, the thing is, you already saw
Azir on the first pick, and you picked
Brown Scanner into it. That's the worst
idea you can have against Azir. And also
as you mentioned TF covered on the top
side so they could actually save Sante
from like diving from Jay but they have
Azir and Z on the other side. So it
doesn't matter for T1 cuz they have all
scaling lanes or all three lanes but
also they have enough damage against
Scanner and Braum. So I feel like just
in general Jenji had just wrong plan
against that comp.
Yeah, definitely did feel that way. you
know, if they got more ahead and some of
their early game plays worked out, maybe
they get enough of a lead where they get
that snowball rolling. Kind of what you
were talking about with the dual kill
over at EWC, but it wasn't meant to be.
Let's take a look at the first highlight
here, which was 16 minutes in. T1 did
take a big fight win at the Herald. This
is when things can become very
disastrous for a composition like this
for Genji when you lose control early,
right? Even though the ultimate from
Owner completely whiffs, they have no
control. And look at Faker able to peel,
keep three members of Genji away while
also just kind of kiting back here.
Sure, he has to flash ultimately, but
fights like this where Ker gets the
knockups and Genji actually don't have
damage. Where's the damage? Still not
seeing any damage. T1 clean these up.
Yeah, it's really easy for Genji to set
up the fight with the tons of CCs like
Scanner, TF, and Braum. But yeah, the
damage is missing while T1 is just
melting the front line with Zia and
Azir. uh just no damage so you can't do
anything. It's crazy that Jenji made
these fights look so close still. Like
this team is so incredibly practiced
with these types of compositions.
They're really really comfortable with
them. Even though no one is winning with
TF right now, it's basically only Chobi.
It is very impressive that that looked
as close as it was and Chobi was almost
even able to get that exit kill there.
But ultimately, don't play on hard mode
against T1. This team's really good.
Yeah, T1 I think was very good at
punishing in this game number two. Let's
take a look at the fight just 2 minutes
later. Uh 18 minutes in for highlight
number two, which was essentially the
nail in the coffin in our minds. This
comp just got too far behind.
Yeah, I feel like Jenji already knew
that they cannot even outscale T1's team
comp. So that's why they tried to cut
off on the side lane, but T1 is the one
who got the full control on the river
side. So the backup wise is always
easier for the the pressure side and you
cannot really kill Zia on the on the
other side as well. So it was really uh
clean play by Ker and Guma as well. So I
mean just in general they had no choice.
Yeah, I think you're 100% right with it.
Like Genji I feel in this moment 100%
also aware this is not a strong play.
This is not a strong position. The
chances of this succeeding are
incredibly low, but they're like maybe
Keen outplays it. Maybe T1 mess it up.
Maybe we actually find a way back in
this game. Let's try to make a proactive
play here because if we just sit back
and let the Azir become huge, we just
lose the game anyways. So, that was kind
of the last stand. And it's crazy that
it's at 18 minutes in the game, Jeni
know this one's likely over. Now, there
were some shenanigans that happened
after that. Ji almost got back in, but
in theory, like at this point, T1 should
never have lost control. I just want to
tell that T1 the key for T1 is
stabilizing the laning phase. Uh the
game one solo kill happened on the b
side and I think that's snowball for
Genji really hard. So I feel like for
the third game as well they need to find
some way to just stabilize the laning
phase and just get into the team fight
sequence where T1 is really strong on
that part.
Yeah. Well, we actually do have a close
series now as it is one to one. Still a
lot of uh picks left as it's only game
three of Fearless. Let's go back to the
casters Atlas and Chronicler for the
call.
Exactly right Valdez. We're still
looking forward to game number four that
is going to be coming up. That's when
Fearless is really going to get
exciting. Mainly because that's when Bro
and DRX start playing. You know what I'm
saying? As thankfully, we get a little
bit of a look in on Sun, Clad, Templar,
and Pony who are manning the Korean desk
when it comes to the cast, which is
super cool.
Really, the only thing that gets me with
as cool as this arena is Yeah. is we
here at Low Park are just in and and you
know what really the funniest thing to
me is that our voices echo
which never happens.
Normally there's chatter, you know,
there's fans, there's all that all
that's fine. We have at least have a a
proxy for that. But I can just hear you
yelling and I can just hear it like
Yeah. bouncing off the walls and it's
like I'm yelling to no one. Yeah. It's
like find some mole.
It's it's an odd It's an odd sort of
position. It's funny, but we do know
that there's a giant crowd of people
going absolutely bananas, so I'm not
complaining.
And we can hear it. And now it is the
deciding match. Genji, they could make
it to 28 series in a row. Uh, from the
very beginning of this LCK season until
now, uh, no matter whether it is an
international competition or here
domestically, they have not lost a
series. They have lost many games though
because they've been to five against so
so many over the last few series. here
all the way to the the distance of game
three in this best of three. The first
match up here in the legend group
between GenG and T1 and thankfully we
get the T1 home ground for it as well.
Now LCK road show these road shows man
it's so cool that we just some regular
season games it's just an absolute
banger and there are so many people here
to witness it as well. It is just
awesome stuff. Always glad to see the
passion of the fans. Also always the
best part of the internationals, right?
Seeing fans from around the world just
go crazy for their teams.
And it's also very funny to me that uh
Brennan lives in Inchan and had to drive
here
here in
for a game that was happening in Inchan.
Yeah. Although, as he's said many many
times, Inchan is a gigantic place. And
so, actually, it's probably just as far
to drive to the home the home ground
than it would be to drive to work. And
in fact, it's probably faster to drive
to work is what he'd tell me. I imagine
he hasn't said it just yet. That reminds
me of in 2022 when I was in Busousan
with my parents two weeks before MSI and
then MSI the broadcast was in Berlin and
then like we flew from from Soul to
Berlin.
It's uh it doesn't feel very right. I
It was funny though.
I once flew to Berlin for 2 days to
commentate a tournament in Iceland. That
that also happened.
That didn't feel real. It was it was a
very strange uh thing cuz there was no
one in the other the LAC arena as well.
Well, yeah. You left before the jet lag
kicked in.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. And I I I was just
never jetlagged throughout that entire
experience cuz it wasn't in Germany long
enough. It was like a fever dream.
Exactly. Which is funny because one of
my favorite memories of Atlas is him
arriving in New York for 2022 and being
like, we we met up, right? I at that
point I'd already been to LA and he just
shows up. He's like, "Ma, this is like I
think the evening off you coming in."
You're like, "I'm actually feeling
great. I don't think I'm going to be
jetlagged at all." I'm like, "I'm glad
you're here, Max. I I I'm glad you're
doing well."
And then he gave me the story about
Raz's birthday party, which was
absolutely
And then obviously the conclusion of
that story is that Atlas was in fact not
well and did really get boomed by
Jetlack for like the next three days.
Yeah. And also Raz had a real issue with
a with a bill at a
classic Raz. That's a real serious Raz
situation. Oh man,
I love Raz.
Me too. Okay, we got some bands coming
in here as Nocturn and Tier are both
going to be taken away. This will be the
first time that Genji have been on the
blue side so far and they're going to
continue down the route of banning the
J4, which is an interesting one. Um, and
in fact, it's only bans towards owner
here on the blue side. So, a bit of
respect given to the T1 jungler who has
been playing very, very well of late.
He's just so good, man. Owner. He's just
he's just he's just good.
Ah, the Maokai ban.
Oh, that's that's
I love this is why Fearless is so good
because these bands come out and then
you have to do the like the reverse
puzzle to work out why the Maokai is now
the champion that's being banned.
It might be because they're afraid like
Maokai Yon. That's a that's a classic
combo.
They've scrimmed too many LEC teams
recently. Yeah, I mean we saw a lot of
what was it like Maokai Yon Varys.
Yeah.
We are B1.
So then I think these three bands make a
lot of sense because Senna doesn't like
in the playing in any of them.
Yep.
And Senna is obviously a very good pick
right now.
And you also get the opportunity
to uh two three pick Trundle tank which
is really strong.
Zixs Camille.
Oh Zix Camille sounds fun. In fact,
Ziggs just sounds like a really good
pick into the center and then you can
just craft a comp around it. If you pick
Rise, you're probably less likely to
pick Ziggs,
which is sad, but that's okay.
You're going to get like Rise versus uh
what, like Gallo? Chovy Gallo. I I would
sign up for that.
Ooh. And then you could uh I mean, that
is another opportunity for a relatively
low damage composition. But when you
have a Senna, she does hit that critical
mass where you can protect her and do a
heck of a lot of damage.
What does owner's pick going into?
He's smiling a lot, Chronicle. I'm
worried about that. Oh, instead it's
just going to be his classic, the
Zenzou. Maybe uh they're just wondering
like why did you ban all these junglers
and leave up my favorite one and that is
because Trungle has a really good match
up into the Zenzou. So maybe that's what
Canyon was angling for. Yeah, there
there's a there's a bunch of reasons,
right? Like Owner is the best Zenz out
in the LCK, I think, by a pretty
substantial margin. He's crazy good on
the pick. His team fighting in
particular, I think, is what really sets
him apart. Uh, but it is a pick that has
a much harder time getting at the center
reliably than any of the other three
picks that were banned. So, I do think
giving that over makes a decent amount
of sense. This also makes the draft
possibly a little awkward for T1 cuz if
they don't pick a support counter pick
here, there's going to be some bands
going towards that I do imagine. And
now, will K can I think for Keny you
don't really need to pick her? I would
like a Chroy pick unless they're going
to run a pirate test of Trundle which is
good into poverty as well as the Zenzo.
So, I do think it it's warranted. It's
also not blind Trundle, which Canyon
fans of all ages have. Uh,
oh god.
Do you remember that game that got
disappeared?
Oh, game five in the world finals.
No, no, no, no, no. The the game where
he played Trundle and the game
disappeared.
We had to remake the entire game and the
entire draft.
He got like free kills in like the first
straight up ran the early game. It was
the best game that he had all year
because it was like 2023 or two or
something like that.
I think it was free cuz I think two that
were still consistently good.
I think it was free.
Yeah, I think it sounds like
the struggle bus really started
severe struggle bus scenario as that's a
Gragas.
Is that Gragas support?
It feels like Gragas.
It's it's obviously a flex, right? I
think most likely this is carry and it
will this will go towards the bot side
of the map. But it also does mean that
obviously as we all know Dorne is an
amazing Gragas player so they can flex
it as there is indeed that Gallo ban
should not come as a surprise. Nope.
Uh see what uh the next answer is going
to be.
Gallio Victor I don't think you're
really too worried about Casopia pulling
out or Chovi pulling out like a Casio. I
also don't think Casio is that good.
We've seen this counter pick be
attempted a bunch of times but I think
the pick needs a lot of setup to really
work. Caitlin going to be taken away.
So, we're going to be digging into the
80 carry champion pools quite far.
Caitlyn Jinx, maybe. I think a Jinx band
would make a lot of sense because that's
the last champion that Gumushi is well
and truly known for that will be left up
and available. Also, I I always look at
picks that really outrange the Sana cuz
I think that's her only true weakness is
early on if she doesn't get the stack
because you just outrange your in space.
Yeah, cuz you can deal with aggressive
lanes, right? You do have still have a
decent amount of sustain. Want to mind
the Jinx banners. The Aurora also going
to get taken away from Chov. It's the
Poppy instead.
Interesting.
Which I guess their read is that this is
a top lane Grager. So just a blind for
Doran.
Well, Smoulder is hovered. Oh, okay.
Felio.
Oh, it's not going to be the Jinx this
time around. And instead, we are taken
200 years into this draft.
I'm glad. I really hope Aphelios is like
back to state. I like the champion a
lot.
We'll see how this one plays out.
We get to talk about severe and grabs
and stuff again. That's kind of fun.
Also, you do have the ability to very
early on bully the lane, right? He's not
what I was thinking of, but does have a
good amount of range as
Let's do it.
Okay, we do need some.
It's just like Victor.
Ah, Aurelian Soul.
could actually be an we know that loves
to lock this pick,
but the Casio that you were talking
about
is a consideration. This is something
that he actually played a fair bit back
in the Griffin days.
It is a short range comp. I think this
makes the most Yeah,
it feels less good.
It's boring,
but it's it's probably
I do I do also think like into the comp
that T1 has, it is actually really good.
Yeah,
just being able to force them to do
something or you just poke them down.
It's also a good late game insurance
policy together with the Senna. feels
less good picking something like a uh re
here, but the nautilus is potentially a
possibility if they want engage, but
instead it's Thresh. Oh man, we haven't
seen this for ages. This is something
that gumishi carrier used to be great at
in the past.
It's the 2022 era, right?
It really is. That was spring 2022.
That was a pretty good year for T1. If
you just don't look at the game five
between them and DRX
or the game five between them and RNG.
Yeah.
But otherwise, great. Brilliant year.
Brilliant year. Um, in fact, they went
undefeated, I'm pretty sure, in spring.
Like, that was the last time any team
that was the first time any team went
undefeated in in a in a split.
Yeah, I I I I think that their
performance in that split also was
crazy. That one it was to me there was a
lot of subbing, right? Like I think that
was a little actually the year after I
think they were way crazier with the
double AD carry meta, but this was what
they made their name on, right? Like
this is as you highlight when GMA
started after his debut in uh in 2021.
This is where they really made a name
for themselves with this specific combo.
That said, I'm looking at this Genji
comp. We have Chovi on an insane damage
threat with laning pressure. We have
Keen on Renekton. We have Kenyon with a
counter matchup and then we have Ruler
on Senna.
Yeah, it's um this is going to be a
little bit less of the Genji doesn't
have enough damage and more of maybe
Genji has too much damage. which we'll
just have to see as T1 still certainly a
lot of opportunities to make plays, find
team fights, and get things done. I
don't think this is by any means a draft
gap. Let's jump onto the rift for game
three.
Yeah, I I needed to give them a chance,
right? I need to give him a chance.
Might be happening for a while.
And also, I had it like ringing in my
ears. I don't think this is a draft gap,
but if I was to be honest,
many unsung
is good for T1.
No,
but honesty often isn't what you should
do as a commentator. You know,
sometimes it's got to be about, you
know, making sure that you have the
right amount of hype on both sides.
What we really want as a commentator is
that afterwards you go, you know, and
then you get called bias from, if you
get biased from both sides, that way,
you know, you smashed it.
Yeah. Right. But that's always what
you're looking for.
Or you've uh you've pingponged too hard.
That's the other way.
You know, like you've just gone a little
bit too hard in both directions.
No, but if you go too hard in both
directions, it it
it does mean you're not biased. You just
might be not that great at your job.
That's all I'm saying.
Well, now you're adding new insecurity
for me. That's so mean.
That's okay. It's okay. You've only got
a few months left.
You can figure it out.
Oh my god. Atlas,
I'm going to run.
Come on, man.
I really did. I really I do think that
now that we've gotten to summer, I feel
like the the the jokes are going to keep
getting ramped up and we're not.
We have not even nearly began yet.
No, no, it's going to be good.
There's a cute little play there as Dur
doing that thing where you press the one
button that you have for like 20 seconds
and then uh and then you just go back to
the brush.
Yeah, Senna does actually have a quite a
strong level one. Uh does offset by the
fact that Alistar's level one is not
good. And then for Gman carrier, looking
at the sums, we do have ghost. So team
fight focus there.
Pretty cool law match up as well cuz we
got Senna versus Thresh.
It is. It would be really cool if like
Carrier could use the lantern on Senna
offensively
and she just gets sucked in.
Oh, that' be great.
Yeah. And like she's just not in the
game for the rest of the game. Maybe
Riot should put that in as carrier not
going to quite find anything here as he
picks the gap. The flash does come in,
but Carrier does manage to flash away.
Not exactly the play that we've wanted
to see there. Did pick the gap quite
nicely. So, that is six points if he's
in Australia playing football.
Uh outside of that, um it's just not
going to be too much. Big whips is going
to not be the end of the world when it
comes to summoners. But it does mean
that Genji and Duro
any trading they can do is good for them
as long as they don't get dove because
again Senna is relying on finding these
trades and just continuously scrapping
to actually get off to a good stack
start. So any auto right second auto
that GMA can get any Q it is just going
to make a big difference as we get later
into the game. So Kerat going for that
play and not all working out. Not going
to have too big of an immediate impact.
But those are the moments that Genji is
going to make good use of as uh the only
matchup that I think truly is just
really nice for T1 is top because the
the Renekton pickup to me doesn't make
that much sense cuz Gragas actually
particularly with Grass is one of the OG
Renekton quoteunquote counters. You
don't really counter Renekton but but
one of the champions together with like
the or that just doesn't really care,
right? you sustain through, you can
always disengage from him. He doesn't
really get to frame you the way he does
with a lot of other picks. So that is a
bit of a questionable one is they are
very aware of this.
Not going to be looking to take any of
the bait. Will also spot owner here.
Yeah, that ward is getting so much value
here for Genji as Faker is also going to
be roaming down but just to get a little
ward and the back is going to come on
through. So Genji don't know that owner
has gone back home. That might give T1 a
little bit of an angle, but instead
they're going to look for a back timer.
I wonder whether this is going to be a
bit of a lane swap. Could potentially be
as here is Doran enjoying the counter
show. I don't carrier cancelled or well,
you do need Yeah, early levels are up,
right? You do
kidding. It was just um
I mean Keen having a good time.
I do think that back when it really was
a counter was when the Gragas passive
was a lot stronger than it is now. We
did obviously see that get nerfed.
Yeah. Uh I forgot when it was like I
want to say like a year year ago maybe
maybe a little bit shorter but did get
because the sustain was obviously very
oppressive as the lane swap does come
through. Looks like the TPS are or the
TP is just going to come through here
from Doran to make his way towards this
lane and then I imagine Keen is going to
try and like get the shove him. I don't
know if GMA Yeah, GMA is not letting
him.
Yeah, it does have Grabbit and Primed as
well. So
but can make his way back. Wave state is
a bit awkward for Ruler here because
again Goomba did uh get the freeze but
he did take a decent amount of damage so
we'll see. Yeah, a little bit of a
freeze on both sides actually. The
cannon does come on in and the cannon
doesn't survive on Genji's side of the
map. So that bottom lane is at least
going to be pushing taking some death
rays here. Does miss that Q but I don't
think the Rise is too worried about
what's going on.
It doesn't have TP anymore though. So
like this damage does actually stick.
Chov Chovi also has gone for comet which
is interesting. We've mostly seen ARY in
these type of setups as
H. That looked a bit weird. I don't know
what was going on.
I think it's hex flash and then
okay always frightens me a little bit
but that was a hex flash.
Yeah, but before that he was just in the
hex flash animation just kind of
Yeah. You're just partying
zoning around. Yeah. Partying party
fresh. And honestly, when you take
Hexplash, if you haven't just used it,
it's available and you're not just using
it, then a mistake.
I don't know enough about fresh skins,
but like imagine surprise party fiddle
sticks, but it's fresh. Like his lantern
is a piata.
Oh my god.
And when you click it,
like candy comes up. That
That's pretty That sounds good, right?
And actually, you could have like the
thresh uh the hook like the death
sentence also like when it hits a
champion like confetti comes out. No,
no, no. It's a kazoo. You know, like the
the birthday like a
Yeah. Yeah. Like the sound that the
crows storm makes as Carrier going to
throw a lantern over to Ona and the wind
becomes lightning and not much else. But
uh they do get the heal. So there is at
least that as Canyon's over here eating
some shellfish
and he'll take a dragon as well in
rebute.
That's all right. Fishi going grab a
white gun. Carrier throws another death
sentence a little bit. Waywood just does
the rage ignite, but Owner is there.
This is setting up for a bit of a dive
as they will now.
Yeah, Faker in amongst it. Teleport is
going to come down from Keen, but I
believe that one was interrupted.
Another one as never mind not actually
going to come on through there. And they
do manage to get that first kill. Faker
locking down first blood as Owner is
able to flash away as well. And even
Doran will survive as the Dominus did
come on through there as Canyon takes
about 15 years, but he will be able to
take down this dragon. And they do, you
know, stick around in lanes. There's
going to be a wave missed in mid, but a
double kill in the top lane and this
whole wave dying. A great start for T1.
Big win for T1. It's the use of Rise,
his ability to impact the side lane
there. It's Faker just like he did on
Denny in game one teleporting up able to
take the kill and Doran also canceling
that TP if Keen shows up to that play. I
don't think it's going to go nearly as
well.
Yeah, it's a big one
and understanding that that's where he
was going to be as well. Really glad
that Jonas Strong had the pan down as
we're going to check out the replay one
more time.
And Ruler stepping up. I don't think it
would have made a difference if he
didn't with four man. I think this dive
can just always work. And then here
the attempt from Keem and Dor. Oh, the
double. That was beautiful. No way.
Keem was ever going to be able to find
it there. Filter available. Could
probably outplay his dive, but instead
owner doesn't even die. He would have
taken the death. Would have been no
problem at all, but he's clean with it.
Yep. They also take two uh two turret
plates as well.
Yep.
And Gushi now with that Moonlight Vigil
moves up, spots his control ward. That
does give Jen G bit of a heads up here
as Canyon just kind of ignoring
everything else that's happening on the
map. He is a PVE player at this point in
time as Doran and Keen just partying
here towards bottom side. Some grubs
being taken a hook going to go wide
and Gumushi does have red white. That is
a scary opportunity here as slice out
here from Keen. Doran without very much
mana and will get ruthlessly preded
which I don't think is a great verb but
it's fine. You know there's a new
Predator movie that's coming out. The
trailer looked good. Yeah, it looked
kind of interesting.
You know, I've never seen any of the
Predator movies.
Really?
Should I? Are they good?
Yeah, you definitely good good action
movies.
Carl Weathers, man. Oh, it's the iconic
like uh the the shake the hold arms.
Oh, no. I've I've seen I I don't need
you talking about I've seen clips and
like I
Yeah. Yeah.
Biosmos. I've watched a lot of movies,
but then you get to see it in context if
you actually watch them.
That sounds fun.
It's all right. Carrier going to find
one. does get the cleanse out from Ruler
this time around and there's the flash
out as well. Running out of summoner
spells here as gravit going to hold duro
in place.
Not a dive. Moonlight vigil will connect
and owner's coming in. I've seen this
play before but uh Faker is not going to
be able to move over the pillar pillar
as Canyon looking to try and get himself
out of here and in fact not going to
take the risk. Didn't want to get
charged audaciously or even prisoned
runically.
Okay, now you're now you're stretching
it out.
I'm really trying. started with I'm
predatoring ruthlessly, but now we're
we're
That started a fun conversation that
involved car weathers, though. That's
kind of
Oh, it was a win.
I felt like it was positive. That just
went way too far.
Let's Let's be real. As fun as
internationals are, it's fun to just
yap.
Yeah. All right. Canyon comes on over
and looks to take a bite out of Faker.
Does manage to do that, but isn't going
to be able to kill him.
Sorry. Walk back to back to Yapp.
Okay. Now you're Now you're crossing a
line. Okay, come on.
He did do that though.
He did do that.
It's kind of like Wario, you know, where
he has the, you know, dislocated jaw
thing.
Didn't Wario do that? What What was the
What game was that even in
aware? I don't think I don't want to get
started about Donkey Kong Bonanza cuz
like I feel like that's going to be the
whole the whole conversation for and we
we have a game to cast.
I haven't played it yet, but I do know
it is good, man.
Do you know what's the best thing about
it? Dunkey is making like consistent
videos about had like it's like been one
a day for the last like 5 days. It's so
good.
Just give me more donkey content. That's
all I need.
Just one about an ice bridge.
Oh, it is playing around an ice bridge.
I I'm going to spoil everything, man. We
need to We need to find a different
Okay. Yeah, Ruler could be in a little
bit of trouble here as the death
sentence is going to get thrown out in a
random direction. Just trying to pick an
angle there.
You know how sometimes you've downloaded
your opponent and every hook hits? Yeah,
rule is downloaded.
Carrier does not have any connection,
bro. He is he his data is not working.
His Wi-Fi is sluggish and we don't know
why.
Yeah, that was a I I don't even know
what that like
there was obviously a level of like
thinking thinking thinking. It wasn't
just like an error. It was I just don't
know what the possible positive outcome
could have been.
Just keep predicting. Yeah.
Yeah.
So, this game to me is kind of a repeat
of game number two.
Oh, there it is. That's Alistister
though.
Yeah. So he's going to get a pulverize
off. There is a teleport in though as
the Gragas is coming down. Moonlight
Vigil will do a damage and the Gragas is
here guys. Howdy Gragas.
Howdy Doran. It's going to be
still. Yeah, there's no they they can
definitely pressure here but can they
get the turret before the Trundle and
Renekton
get it?
They don't have white guns. I think that
actually matters a lot. There is another
minion wave that is coming up and this
one's going to take a little while as
Arcane Storm in the mid lane is going to
be pushing Faker around. I think it is
going to be first turret going over to
T1 though.
Oh, okay. Yeah, with white guns
definitely going to be able to get that
crescendum over and Kumushi with a bunch
of extra money and he'll deny the cannon
as well.
Oh god, he's going to be up like what
like one and a one point 1.5.
Yeah,
feels pretty good. Kane also extending
his advantage as Duro will be able to
get he doesn't even need vision because
they can see Faker on that ward but
nothing they can do about it. Control
ward goes over just to make sure. So
that is going to be the dragon secured
here for T1. It's going to be an
infernal soul here for game three. And
the gold ahead for T1 about 800 but it's
not a massive lead. This is feeling like
a much less like oh this is kind of
doomed for a lot of extraneous reasons
this time around. This is some honest
League of Legends we've got for us here.
This This is And both teams can look at
their com outskilled. So, you know what
that means, Atlas? We're in the long
haul.
Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep.
Can we get an elder? Two elders. Maybe
T1 can break their record of their
longest game ever. What do you reckon?
93 minutes.
You know that's never happening.
Yeah, it's so sad.
Oh, wow. Carrier's figured it out now.
The lantern doesn't quite work. And the
the
Have you seen the joke edits of like
where like where like someone like
tepee's into a brush and then like
flashes out and it's like oh it's the
ghost of that's how these players are
looking.
Yeah. I feel like we're just not good
enough to understand what carrier is
trying to do. So I just I just
I refuse.
This is this is they're going to get
this turret as well. like we we've been
meaning a lot but T1 actually have done
an exceptional job of something we've
criticized a lot of team for
specifically with the Selios especially
with these white guns. So one of the
things we always talk about with Zigs
one of the things that infuriates
I mean it's a Caitlin and Jinx thing as
well and they've done this with GMA so
many times on these picks
and it's why we see the gold lead
actually starting to ready balloon
they're very happy to just siege away.
Well, here's a Dominus here for Keen as
he looks to try and defend, but he's not
just standing around. Wants to be able
to dodge some of the CC. The play does
come back though, so he can't dodge all
all of it even if the hook does go wide.
Still Canyon is going to be able to eat
this turret.
So, the gold lead remains manageable.
Yeah, it's not the end of the world for
Genji, but I do like T1 being this
proactive with pushing and again playing
around the pushing strength of
particularly the Zenza as well as the
Ailos. There's also the added benefit of
when you play fresh and you are ahead on
tempo, even if you don't actually hit
the hooks, which so far has been a bit
of a problem, just being on the map
making moves, forcing people off turrets
is already a big win.
Yeah.
So T1 able to use that nicely. Now we do
look to the other side and we see that
Ruler is I think a little behind. I
think really when you when you're
feeling really good in the center,
you're going to hit 60 souls at about 20
minutes. I think the average in MSI was
like 51 at 20. I think he's more on
track for that. He's going a really
weird build though because I was I was
talking to a and you're supposed to
build essence first.
No, no, no, no, no. Atlas, I know I I
know you don't actually.
He can still make up for it by building
runon second, right?
I'm not ready to talk about DK. Okay, we
can talk about Donkey Kong. No, I want
to talk about D plus K. I wasn't I was
off that day. That wasn't real.
Oh, it definitely was. I saw you in
chat.
Yeah, I remember cuz you said juke juke
and that made me sad. was already a
juke. Okay, that's all right. Carrier
with the flash play. On looking to go on
in as well, but the Arcane Storm wants
to take down the one more tick will do
it, but it's not going to connect as now
the cask will deliver Canyon to his
death potential. He did have to
subjugate there. And oh my god, Ona
survives the headbutt to get Kumushi out
of here, but he is an absolute
demolition machine. And Genji, they
might be staring down the barrel of
their first loss of the season.
Keane trying to look for a counter pick.
The hook hits in. He does manage to at
least get carry. He's flashing in
looking for even more. The turret's
helping him out at the same time, but
Ona is also going to be able to get a
cute little charge. And that will help
take down the croc. This guy's in. It is
built different, ladies and gentlemen.
And that whole time Kumushi was just
slaughtering them. 303 now on the
Aalios. Yeah, we're going to need a few
hundred more years.
There was Carrier surviving there. But
for me, as you highlight, I want
everyone to look at Owner in this fight.
Carrier starts it off, but the fight
initially isn't actually that good.
Carrie almost goes down. If that if he
goes down and that becomes a big chaos
storm could have been the arc in could
have been different than that, but then
here owner goes in with just the
slightest bit of health. Takes down
Ruler, which is the essential damage
necessary. And then Doran
being a frontliner that we have seen in
him be for so many teams including Geng
by the way.
Oh yeah,
got them two titles and then Keen here.
This is really funny as uh Owner just
with barely any health left gets the
point blank charge and tanks the turret
and tanks a the turret shot afterwards
as well. Yep. 4 and 1/2k gold lead now
and I think this drake or Genji are
going to contest. I don't know if they
really can. There's the hex flash hook
onto Duro. Not too much more to happen
after that, but there's a glorious cast
onto Chobi. Does get the gravity field
down as now Duro does get a pulverized,
but Faker is making his way in. And Ono
just finding it. Ruler goes down yet
again. The entire bottom lane has been
removed and Faker will just take a bit
of a journey underneath the turret.
Might have been a bridge a little too
far as Carrier looks for another cute
little play. needs a few extra links in
that chain though if he wants to get
that one. As owner going in one more
time, it's the most balanced Trundle has
looked all week as the hook this time.
He's going to connect. It lands onto
Chobi Kuma's going to grab that kill.
And Carrier, I mean, I don't know how it
worked, but it absolutely worked. He had
some of the most crazy hooks ever, but
he lands them when he needs to. And the
inner is going to then go down. T1, they
are so far ahead. This is all just about
knocking down these turrets and securing
the first victory against Gen for any
team since the LCK season started.
Since February,
we are free season. It was winter.
Spring has come and gone. We're in the
heat of summer and T1 at their home grab
might actually be able to do what no
team has done in so
so many months. Oh, that uh there's a
ward right there, too. We're going to
check this one out one more time.
Starting with Carrier finding the little
but Doran's just like these casks, man.
It's working out. There's not enough
damage available. And even with Carrier
hooking a minion, owner sees the space
to go in. Ruler again doesn't get to
play the video game. And then here,
watch this lantern. Faker looks like he
might go down. Keen even tries to get on
top of him. Doesn't quite work. Denowner
applies pressure to Canyon here. the T1
these staggered approaches this
continued pressure as there is the
download onto Chi just in time.
Yeah, he knew that one. Him and Chi,
they go way back. So going to be able to
lock him down. And now Genji staring
down the barrel of 6,000 gold.
That is Goomba sitting on a 3.2k gold
lead.
Two items on the Aalios
and Genji. Yeah, in theory this comp,
they're part of it that scale well, but
is going to be behind on souls not going
to be able to really farm them up. Chovi
is again going for a build that is going
to take a long time to you're talking
like fourth item at this point. Looks
like he's going to go what Leandre
second.
Yeah, I think this is going to be a next
series uh Road of Ages before that's
going to be very useful. And I have
watched Genji uh I think this was the
first test of five between them at MSI
crawl back from a big deficit. Was a
very different drop was a very different
setup. This T1 palm just the it skills
well like the 5v5s will remain good.
There are obviously parts of Genji that
are going to become a problem eventually
like the range on Chovi the damage on
Ruler and his stacking but I don't think
that we're really going to reach that
point. And the problem is is like I'm
looking at these junglers as well and I
can count and that's making things look
a little bit worrying here for Geng
because there is shoes and then two
items for owner and there is shoes and
one triangular fan here for Canyon and
it's not really looking great.
This is just a T1 that are well and
truly powered up. We're talking about
like item spikes that are just perfect
for this stage of the game as well with
this composition as a hook is just going
to sail on by. Death going to come on
through there as well as Chi will be
able to at least sidestep the cask, but
owner is looking to make his way in.
Another hook is going to be fantastic
here as Chi's already got that flash on.
In comes the moonlight vigil and down
goes Geng. There's at least a couple of
kills back here as they do manage to
trade with the help of the turret. But
T1 are so far ahead. They don't really
mind that Doran and Carrier go down. The
damage is still here.
There's still a walking turret in the
form of GMA.
Doesn't get to play.
He's an upgraded turret.
Yeah, cuz he also kills other turrets in
a matter of seconds.
Well, red, white, don't fight. Well,
that is not what T1 are thinking.
They've got a green gun now. So, the
extra range here for Gumushi. Are we
like looking at like a deep flank
bolstered by TP? No, he's just farming
raptors.
Yeah, we're looking at raptors. That's
where we're looking.
All right, he did get him.
Yeah, he did manage to lock that one
down. Nailed it. Didn't doesn't have
subjugate, so does need to be a little
careful.
Doesn't quite find the angle.
Only saving grace for Geng is that soul
isn't that imminent. That's it. Uh maybe
you can get to a third item as we take a
look here for Troy. Nice movement. Nice
side steps initially, but then still
gets tagged and then that hook from
Carrier.
Black is out. Still gets hooked.
Yeah, might not have the uh again uh the
earlier hooks down, but these hooks on
Trophy actually end up winning the
fights cuz Trophy doesn't get more
rotations off and the flashes you
highlight is a really big deal. The fact
he doesn't have that available means
that both Doran, even Owner and Carrier
have way better angles. Ruler still not
at 60. By the way, Duro, I I swear he's
trying, guys. Do not look at that
combination of summoners. It's fine.
Yeah.
Oh,
so Genji like I'm trying to think of
angles for them to somehow bring us to a
competitive game three. We need probably
Canyon the steel or they let this one go
and
well actually there are three rounds um
at this particular end of the year as
Ruler is just going to get engaged on.
Does have to flash and there's another
cast this time. No avoiding that. And
that is Faker grabbing a bunch of extra
gold.
Yep. Sometimes you ruler and you're a
little bit too pushed up. This was the
first pick center as well, guys. Really
taking a bit of a face plant here on the
side of Genji. Kind of torn apart by
T1's answer.
And going into this, I actually felt
like Genji's composition looked good.
It is. But the way that T1 have played
this, the way they moved Kumishi around
the map and turned him into this
slaughter machine has been just
beautiful. He'll take the lantern ride
to get himself out of there. We also
just haven't seen that much success for
Thresh. Even when Carrier tried to play
it the last couple of times, it hasn't
really been all that inspiring. This is
working out a bunch better even after a
couple of flubs earlier on. And now
you're also looking at a scenario where
how do you actually engage onto T1 if
you're Geng because there is there is
Carrier who is a walking lantern bot has
fle as um
Canyon Canyon is Canyon is dead. He
might not be down. He
does have a lot of speed.
He is dead. Um
so is this dragon he it'll it'll run.
It'll make him work for it. But
yeah. Um well
Malov gaming there as he does Doran just
going to boot himself away to try and
avoid that again play before.
Oh it's the fake out and Faker then
Faker out.
That was okay I'm I'm
that was weird. Um
there was a there's a dead troll. The
dead troll dead dragon soul point now
for T1. Don't know whether that is all
that relevant cuz the game could just be
over in 4 and 1/2 minutes. Yeah, it's
just a beautiful snowballing from T1,
right? It it and it really comes down to
that one dive in top.
Oh dear. Ruler is just dead. Cut the
video. Cut the video. Cut the video.
You need to watch it. It's a little bit
worrying here as at least Keane does
have a Dominus. Faker is going to take a
lantern ride to get out. Scot-free from
that one. And Chi comes on over, but he
comes on over a whole lot later than he
needed to. And Arcane Storm is down
underneath this turret. He does go
golden as that is a dead Gragas maybe.
No, they are in fact too far ahead
ladies and gentlemen.
The wallets Atlas.
Yeah, that was the pianoized wallet
right on the noggin of Chovi and T1 will
be able to push these super minions in
for the first time in a deciding game of
a series this season. Gen are looking to
go down. We'll see. There is a pillar of
filth there just to delay it. I was
about to start the monologue, but I
guess we'll have to hold off.
What? What? What hit ruler? Why is he
Did he get hit by like blue gun?
Um I swear he just respawned
and he was at like maybe uh rice bounds.
He is 0 five and zero.
Oh yeah, he's also level I I I there's a
lot. I'm just wondering what
specifically like looked at him. I think
someone may have breathed in his
vicinity on the T1 side of things is uh
I think what happened and his health bar
vanished. We Why are we getting a replay
as Ono was just he is just here. He was
just ready. You know what? Getting two
flashes that's war. I'm not even I'm not
even
um shouldn't have happened.
Well, T1 are just going to deny this is
Keen. Okay.
Um
Atlas, this this whole situation.
Yes.
It just reminds me of when you were
like, "Mal, I'm fine." And then you were
not fine.
That's what I'm looking at right now.
It's the jetlike scenario. Yes. Uh well,
the uh Victor is just going to get taken
down as T1 just catch two teleports that
come in delivering members of Geng to
their doom.
They're doing it, Atlas.
They are definitely doing it. They're
just going to wander down. Baron is
unnecessary as Ruler is going to be
discovered by Ona once again. This time
the snare comes in, but now he's just
going to hunt him down to the ends of
the earth. And that is maybe going to
Infinity in this game because T1 will
end it and end Geng's streak. 27 is all
they will get as T1 in their home
ground. Will be able to take down Geng
for the first time this season.
What a win here for T1.
And it's vintage. It is 2022 again. We
are watching Faker impact the sidelines
and we are watching Aelios fresh. And
and you know Carrier, you just to shake
off the rust little early on as I got to
I got to vote for
you P. Uh
I feel like this is just a I'm I'm I'm
I'm being met with skepticism. Uh
it's up to you.
Okay. Who Who do you got? Well,
oh, gotcha.
No, I I I I just always think it's Doran
when he plays Gragas.
It's always Doran when he plays Gragas
to me. Although, uh I think there's
quite a few decent choices here.
It might be It might be Kuma.
Yeah. The one thing to me that really
stands out in my mind is that moment
Jarvin was banned.
I think Genji lost the series.
Yeah, you're you're really you're you're
not on board with the Jarvin there. I
think
No, I think you ban Azia every single
time. You never give that pick away.
I think it's uh like Azir was buffed and
he was perma banned against every LCK
team prior to the buffs.
Yeah, I just don't think it's I don't
think it's legal and I think that sort
of really threw Gen uh off immediately
afterwards. I'm just happy to see Jen or
T1 rather play classic T1 right as I'm
sure the crowd went absolutely wild
after that one
as the
league that Genji has has highlighted
they are already qualified for worlds um
is not something that is going to be
taken down in a single victory but given
how many close series these two have had
over the last couple of months I think
it's very warranted as Doran got to love
him the Gragas ends up paying huge
dividends again. And I I'm right there
with you. Uh when it comes to those
casks, man doesn't doesn't miss.
Honestly, I think that he almost played
a perfect game uh in that last one. The
interrupt on the teleport as well where
he was casking midair and managed to
land the body slam as well, picking all
of the angles that Keen could be. Of
course, if he had have missed, he would
have looked ridiculous because he would
then have zero CC and just have to watch
him teleport away. But still, he nailed
it. knew exactly where he was going to
be, what the options were, and executed
on that play. And that really was what
started that snowball rolling. And Genji
never found their way back into the
game.
It was also uh actually a pretty good
rise game from Faker cuz I think that in
game number two, it was to me a lot more
about the draft and just the team as a
whole. But I think in this game three,
he was the one that actually set up
multiple of these dives. uh him and
owner I think for me were really what
kind of started the snowball and it's as
you highlighted T1 have been able to
play around that specific setup be it a
felios with white guns be it Jinx be a
Caitlin about a million times this is a
moment that I'm sure Jenji is going to
review an infinite amount of times
because that is where the game became
hard and this is probably where the game
was lost. Yep, this was kind of over at
this point as carrier even managing to
survive with his little lantern shield
towards the end there. But that cask,
man. Oh, give my boy the pom.
I re I actually don't know who it's
going to be. Like I I'm I'm trying to
cuz I could see an argument for
I think Sups and Chisik are going to go
with GMA.
Okay. And I think that the true sants
like Jonas Strong for example will go
for Doran. And I think the people that
only half watch will probably go for
owner because he's always a good vote.
And uh and the rest will go for carrier
because it's hilarious.
Cuz you you just call me out like that.
Wait, who did you vote for?
Oh, you know who I voted for.
I have no idea.
Everyone everyone
and actually like the majority of the
votes are going to go for
cuz his uh fourman uh was pretty nice on
the Azir. My recency bias is coming in
with my uh I think Doran should get it,
but also it's just you. It's Doran, man.
He's just so lovable. I know. And he's
and he's Gragas, man. It's always so
good.
And every time he plays Gragas, I always
want justice for Doran missing out on
MVP when Pace got it that time and he
didn't deserve it.
Okay, well, let's let's not open back.
My favorite part is look at the little
mascot in the player camps. That's just
like as the crowd is going wild, the
mass, yeah, we're doing it. Look at it.
It's adorable.
It's very cute. And we also get it
behind Faker and Goomer as well. Like we
get double mascots.
You can even see a little bit there in
owner.
Yeah, that's true.
[Music]
Given the side eye as Duro does manage
to get a little bit of revenge towards
the end here.
How poetic that it's T1 that ends it
after Genji denied them both the upper
bracket finals as well as the finals of
MSI.
Yeah. And I don't know how Genji are
ever going to recover. Are they even
going to make it to Worlds?
The answer is yes, everyone, because
they qualified two days ago. That's the
joke.
Atlas, I really need to rebuild my uh my
Atlas palace. I I I I'm not
You did like that was all that was
building for the story that we had to
get to and you just left me hanging.
It's Carrier that picks it up. Okay,
that's a that I mean that's a that's an
option.
He was on the team. I do starting the
second half. Uh his his fresh was really
good. Uh and I think the the Ra
performance was solid as highlight. I
think him on uh him, Guma and Keria or
him him and Gmba on Zia Rakan are always
really good. Uh that's not I really
thought in hindsight that was going to
be either GMA or Faker.
Yeah. And I I thought like I thought
this game
it's just legit. Every player gets
votes.
I imagine it's probably going to be a
little bit all over the place. Um the
fact that it was carry that picks it up
was very very funny because some of
those hooks earlier on in the game were
just very strange. But the bait in the
mid lane absolutely fantastic and did
manage to like catch
up, you know, like the he was doing the
dance.
Yeah, he did definitely make some sick
plays and the Rakan was pretty
game-winning in the prior game and maybe
we're just too used to seeing it at this
point in time to really give him enough
credit for that situation. So, an
absolutely fantastic performance here
from T1 and crazy that the streak ends
here of all places. I was a little bit
early on my prediction of the streak
ending. Um, and instead I am speed
running to meet Don in the predictions
as I went like zero for two day one.
He got a big win though. He got the
bros.
Yeah, he got the bros and he got the T1
today.
So, it is a threes.
It's a good w good week for Dion. Yeah,
I actually think that maybe we're even.
Maybe we're even at this point in time.
I don't I don't care. It's predictions.
And I'm often like I'm a middle of the
pack kind of guy
and so as long as I can get up off the
As long as you don't want to you just
don't want to get comic science.
Yeah, I took some risks this week and uh
did not pay off and sometimes that's
fine. It is now time for us to head over
to the interview though. Take it away.
Thank you very much guys. This is dear
for the POM interview translation for
the 2025 LCK road show at T1 home
ground.
We are joined by Kia on the side of T1
who just shut down Genji's 27 series
winning streak.
Congratulations.
The genius monster has received the POM
today.
You took such a valuable and incredible
victory at the LCK road show. We can
feel all the energy from your fans. How
does it feel to defeat the previously
undefeated Jen Gi?
You know, we were playing in front of
all the fans that were supporting us
and I feel like
us winning must have made our fans
really happy. So, I'm just really glad
that we're able to live up to their
expectations and pay back their support.
Today was a rematch of the MSI finals.
And because of how close the MSI matches
were, you must have taken extra measures
to prepare for today, you know, because
the patch had not changed much since
MSI. I think we really just focused on
what we had been preparing for and we
tried to fix all the areas that we had
to work on, all the reasons that we lost
from the times that we were facing Jenji
in the finals or in the MSI.
So, what kind of feedback was there
after game one?
You know, even in game one, we were
actually doing pretty well. And due to
our own mistakes, it actually went down
that way, but we knew that the biggest
area of improvement was really on
ourselves and our place. And we tried to
make that and fix that as soon as we
can.
And in game two, the enemy left Azir
open and it felt like they were steering
you into picking him. So, what was the
discussion like during the draft?
I think we were actually just trying to
go ahead and ban some of the champions
that they were uh pretty good at and I
think that's why they ended up leaving
the open and that's why we ended up
having to pick him in the end
and so we saw your affiliates thresh
what made you pick him you know this was
something that we were thinking of even
back in MSI and we just didn't have a
chance to lock them in and today we just
saw an angle that we just could not
pass.
And I feel like we were able to really
play it out the way we planned
everything. So, I'm just really glad
that we're able to execute everything so
well
and yeah, you got such a great early
momentum
and you shut down the enemy's scaling.
So, creating such a big gap, did you
expect to win with your game plan?
you know, with the Falas, I felt like
we're either going to win big or lose
big,
but I'm just really happy that it played
out our way.
[Music]
And today's victory
might just be thanks to all the fans
cheering from every direction on the
stage.
Wow, they are just deafening. So any
word for the fans who came all the way
to Yangjong do to support you know ever
since EWC I think we weren't feeling
very great not the best condition and I
think I'm uh few of us are suffering
from a cold but because of all the
energy that our fans sent us I think we
even forgot that we weren't feeling well
and I was able to focus on the game so
thank you
and two days from now you will play nong
redforce
right where you are
any mindset going into that match
because of all the fans that will
attend. You know, I'm just going to have
to make sure that we win
and this is the start of your round
three. So, what are your goals?
You know, we really wanted to take it
home for either MSI or EWC and we were
unsuccessful. So, I want to make sure
that we win it all in the LCK this time
around.
And please give it up for T1 and Kia.
And that's the end of the interview with
Keria. Back to the space. Thank you.
[Music]
Thank you, dear, as always, for that
awesome translation. Great to hear from
Kia in front of that gigantic crowd at
the Inspire Arena. Great stuff from him.
And uh yeah, T1 actually did it. They
broke the streak. Crazy stuff. And
Jinzy, their streak will end there,
unfortunately for them at 27. Not going
to catch up to their previous streak of
29, which was last year. Thoughts on
this, guys? I mean, it had to happen
eventually, right? Jen D's drafts were
really greedy in this series. And while
they often weren't punished in the past,
they get punished by T1 here, especially
in game two. I think that was the bigger
uh discrepancy we had in draft than what
happened in game three. Uh where
ultimately it was a really cool Aelio's
Thresh angle. We'll talk a little bit
more about later.
Yeah, I mean it was really brave idea to
pick Thresh in game three. I mean, they
just lost in MSI finals at game five. uh
Duro just picked a pike randomly against
uh Kerat, but this time around Kerat did
some kind of revenge against that. And I
think this kind of draft idea is always
bringing up uh such a great opportunity
in BO3 or BO5.
Yeah, absolutely. And uh you might think
that hey, Genji were the big favorites
today. Obviously, everybody would have
predicted them, right? Wrong. Actually,
one person did go ahead and predict T1
and that one person was Deon. Um gangly.
How did he know?
Interestingly though, I noticed Don was
actually at the home ground. He was
actually there and he was sitting on the
Genji side.
Yeah, what did he mean by that? Why does
he do this where he tells everyone he
wants Bro to win and then predicts
against them? Uh, Dgon, we're going to
have to have a little chat uh when
you're back here in Soul tomorrow.
So, is he is he happy inspire Arena at
the Genji side?
Yeah. I wonder how the Genji fans they
sing with right now feel when they see
this come up on the screen.
Yeah, he's probably locking his cell
phone screen real quick right now.
Always watching the stream. He's like,
"Whoa, no,
no, I didn't."
He got the PR right, but at what cost?
You know, let's hope he gets home safe
tonight. Uh guys, we do have the POM as
well. Let's take a look at the votes and
see where they did go as it was a 6 out
of 13. And uh as the casters were
talking about, very much kind of split
up all over the place here. Even some
votes for mid, which is pretty
interesting. Um Figer did have a good
Azir game. So I guess there's that.
I really like the Guma votes because he
was extremely consistent throughout the
series. But for me, the recon plays we
saw from Carrier really solidified their
win uh in game two. Also, some of what
Guma was able to follow up on. But the
Thresh, yes, he missed some hooks.
Doesn't matter. the the draft pick, the
mastery of Thresh that this guy has
allows them to draft this Aphelio setup
here and they played it so well into
this melee setup here for the side of
Genji. The Thresh was so key. Yeah. And
especially when you think about the team
comp, you have to play against Pillar
and you have to somehow have like play
against Victor as well, which is like
outrange for Thresh, but he just flashed
into Victor and somehow reached to
Victor. I think that was the main part
of the this game on the mid turret that
carrier landed the engage and the both
hook as well. I I think it's just really
brave enough to just pick a game three
fresh when thresh is not the main mana
pick in the support lane.
Yep. No game five pike this time. Never
let this man have Shinjo ever again says
Chronicler. Um I feel like we've said
that about Owner with a decent amount of
champs at this point. Shinjo was
definitely one of them. Vi was another
one of them. In the very beginning of
the season, we were like, "How does he
keep getting it every time?" And they
just kept giving it to him. And even
though it has fallen in priority
slightly, it's still an S tier jungle
pick that he absolutely obliterated.
Genji with there in the mid game of this
one.
I mean, I I feel like every game is just
different. You know, the meta changes
every single time. And here comes
Rakhan. And you all know what Rakhan has
really bad win rate, but Carrier always
makes it different. Kas Rakhan is
different level.
Yeah, it was really good. uh played
alongside of the
Here comes Zia says Prince. So I guess
they kind of
they coordinated it all.
Imagine that.
All right. Just like Zia and Raond do.
Yeah, those guys were able to do it on
the desk. What? You guys didn't really
coordinate.
We just talked about the trash.
Yeah, we we talk to each other. We
already have that synergy built in.
All right.
Putting a bell on the tiger's neck.
Check.
Well, there you go. Is there some kind
of reference there that I'm
If a cat has a bell, you know where it
is at all times, right?
Yeah.
Maybe referencing the vision game from
No, no, no. Jenji's Jenji is the uh the
the tiger.
The tiger, but like if you know if you
put a bell on a cat, they usually do it
so you know where the cat is at all
times. Maybe that was like a vision
thing. So, this is what I was thinking.
It's a Korean saying it's like the
impossible
has been done or something like that.
Like cuz putting a bell on a tiger's
neck is like really difficult, I guess.
Anyway, uh let's talk about the draft
cuz we really wanted to talk about the
draft. Uh the Aelios Thresh obviously a
big uh difference maker in this one.
So, I was yelling at the TV for the
Thresh. A lot of people were thinking
this Grogas was going to be in the
support role. Aelios is so strong right
now. I I really really think that
especially with the crit builds we have
right now um that we're going to see
more Aelios. It's been hovered a lot. We
saw it at W EWC hovered. I was like,
please play the Aelio. It's just so
good. But when your enemy doesn't have
really consistent engage, you've got the
pillar, maybe Renekton can close that
gap. The Senna will outrange doesn't
necessarily matter cuz the Trundle and
Renekton, if they don't get on top of
the Selius who has a Thresh to back him
up, you just don't kill him and then he
does way more damage than anyone on
Genji can do.
Yeah. I mean, this is the reason why I
really hate the Senna Alysa together cuz
I feel like you have no pressure in lane
at all. So normally Senna uh I think
they set up with the notless or time Ken
so you can have better lane but I feel
like with Alissa you can do nothing much
on the lane. So and I think I think
getting a lane priority on the bot lane
it's just so much important in this meta
and I think that happened on the top
side dive as well. So it was still
really brave enough to pick Aelius and
Thresh cuz it's not in the meta and I
think uh it was just a game-winning
draft on the game three by T1.
Yeah, absolutely. It's not every day
where we say, "Hey, the draft had a huge
impact on this game." But it really does
feel like in this one it absolutely did.
So that's a good shout there. Uh guys,
wanted to clear something up as well.
Earlier we uh aired a Annie stat that
was actually incorrect. Uh this is the
correct stat here. It's actually 3 and
one now after the Faker loss earlier.
Similar idea. We had five and zero. It
was actually three and zero. Annie still
same.
Still the first loss of the uh the
season here or the round.
It doesn't matter. They broke the
record. So ultimately like the still the
still the same concept does uh apply
there. So just a correction. We're not
trying to bring up um the old wound of
game one again. They still won the
series after all. Let's take a look at
the standings here as guess what guys,
Genji, they actually can bleed and T1 is
the team to do it. This kind of makes
sense when you think about it, but we
were all thinking that it's just going
to be random like Nin is just going to
like take a win over them at some point.
At this point, T1's form is way better
than Han life esports. So the fact that
T1's able to get this really incredible
win over Genji cuz you get the triple
round robin in this group you can get
two more opportunities to beat Genji but
your more realistic wins are like KT
Nongim maybe Hanife Esports currently
though really big for T1 they absolutely
can take that second place spot away and
I think it's kind of bad news for Genji
because like everyone was kind of
confused why they open at zero and why
they're playing this team comp against
T1. So I feel like they have to find
some way about the dre but well on T1
side it's such a good news that you kind
of have a little revenge against the
Genji and I think this what matters when
it comes to LCK final uh uh playoffs cuz
the record like keeps going on and I
think T1 finally found find their way to
build around their synergy between the
players.
Yeah, the form is great of T1. The
drafting was great here. Uh it feels
like in all three games T1 had a better
read than Genji did. So absolutely big
deserved win and that's the way it does
go sometimes. Guys, we got the next
matchup. It is the Bros up against TRX.
The Rise group coming up next. You
thought T1 versus Genji was good? Just
wait and see until bro faces off against
TRX. Banger alert here at the LCK. Stay
tuned. We'll be right back.
[Music]
Hey. Hey. Hey.
Heat. Heat.
[Music]
Heat.
These
[Music]
health bars are so low. Diabo dancing
around this fight and manages to take
out all of them.
[Applause]
[Music]
What doesn't kill me
makes me stronger.
[Music]
Heat. Heat.
[Applause]
[Music]
Hey,
hey, hey.
[Music]
Oh yeah.
Oh,
[Music]
I am.
Hey
[Music]
la.
Yeah. Oh
yeah.
[Music]
Heat.
Hey.
[Music]
Hey,
hey,
[Music]
[Applause]
hey.
[Music]
Hey,
hey, hey.
[Music]
Hey,
hey, hey.
Don't.
[Music]
Heat. Heat. Heat. Heat.
[Applause]
[Music]
Starting with a whisper.
I know I find it hard to lose. Counting
down hours,
but I'll take way this time and night.
I've been there before a million times.
Cutting between the truth and the lies.
Can't hold me down for a minute longer.
What doesn't kill me
makes me stronger.
[Music]
Oh,
that makes me stronger.
[Music]
Heat.
[Applause]
[Music]
Okay, buddy.
fighting.
[Music]
Welcome back, ladies and gentlemen, to
LCK 2025. I'm Atlas, joined by
Chronicle, and we're ready to get into
the main event for today. It was really
great seeing Geng and T1 warming
everyone up as the what are they the
support act for DRX bro that are about
that's about to happen now. I have no
idea what to expect. All I know is we're
going to learn things
and we're going to be entertained.
That's all I know. And that's every
great thing that you watch has both of
those things.
I really do think that there is so much
value in appreciating all facets of
anything. And when it comes to the LCK,
you can't call yourself a real LCK fan
if all you watch is T1 Geng. I'm sorry.
You have to earn it by enjoying with us.
A nice free gamer between DRS.
How did How did you make enjoying sound
so much like enduring? How did you do
that? That was very, very, very clever
of you, Chronicler, because you
definitely said enjoying, but that's not
the word that I heard as there is a
closet bro antie in there somewhere.
I did predict them. I did predict him
here today.
Well, I mean, there'd be a reason for
that, and that is because DRX are our
second least winning team that we have
here in the LCK. Somehow DNF managed to
win two games, but it still says they're
on a seven loss streak um after their
performance uh yesterday. And Bro, fresh
off a win up against DK, a team here in
the LCK. They did lose the tiebreaker,
but that wasn't actually included in
their streak. So technically, Bro
managed to break that streak and now are
looking to make it a perfect week. They
can pick up a victory against DRX here.
Let's have a look. DRX though on a
fivematch winning streak against the
Bros. When have these sorts of records
ever really meant anything when it comes
to the Bros though? That's my question.
Wow. Uh Atlas just breaking the fourth
wall there. I I don't think it matters.
I am the conviction that today's going
to be a free gamer. I think it'll be
very close because even though bro
looked as good as they did, my boy
Crocco popped off closer showing that
he's really having a great year thus
far. I I just don't know what it means
cuz Bro could do that and then
immediately go back to not doing
anything and getting blown up by this
man Teddy in the starting lineup after
90 days which uh with his victory being
a lot longer ago.
Not that much longer ago actually. It's
like 24 days.
Yeah, that's that's that's that's a lot.
That's a month.
Yeah, I guess but I mean 90 days is
longer than that.
That's true.
You know, I'd say in like you know it
just doesn't seem that long. Anyway,
both teams going to make their way out
into L Park here as we are back here
now. We were um previously in Inchan and
we have now made our way back to L Park
and I guess everyone did know that we
were already here waiting. But
thankfully we have now got people in the
crowd here at L Park. So it's not that
weird echoey yelling around and stuff
like that while everyone's having fun
elsewhere including Don who skipped out
on a bro match to head down to a home
home ground match for for T1
chronically. How do you feel about that?
I'm honest. I'm a known bro antie, you
know, and and and that's okay. Although
like the opposite bro antie though, we
don't really like that.
Well, let's be real. I ever since Crocco
joined, I have been having a bit of a
crisis of big battles cuz I love that
man.
You are the leader of the Crocco fan
club. But this
after all these years,
this must be a very difficult one
because you're also a leader of the
sponge fan club as well. Yeah, I have
this issue a lot um as I do kind of just
get attached to players and then am in
inner turmoil when they face off.
We'll see. DRX, they really are a team
that I think very often
wins or falls with Sponge's performance.
Yep.
Um he's just he's just Sponge. Sometimes
he's great, sometimes he's not. But the
big difference with Bro is that I think
as good as Kroko has been really kind of
convincing all of us cuz we were all
skeptical when Hanukkah was subbed out,
Krokco was announced as a sign. Even me
obviously
especially made no sense at all.
You were way you and Wolf were way ahead
of me. I think I I was obviously cuz I
have a soft spot for Kroko. I was a
little bit more willing but even I
thought that given what Hback showed his
heist, I don't know if it was warranted.
It has been. Crocco has transformed his
team, but much more important, I think
that bro have other threats as well.
We've seen Hype finally lean into what
he used to do in challengers. We've seen
Morgan with I think the biggest
Cho'Gath, the widest cho I have seen in
a long time. And then we have Closer,
who right now, and I think by a large
margin, is the best mid laner they have
in the Rise group. I don't I don't think
anyone come really comes close.
Nope. It's a little bit of a shame if
you're a Showmaker fan, but that is just
the fact of it, unfortunately.
I'm right here.
Yep. Yeah, don't worry. I am too and
we're both sort of hurting um after that
last one. Still Bros going from strength
to strength and we'll see whether they
can find an angle here up against DRX
because it's still looking like the Bros
are going to be safe here in the Rise
group right now from their position
where they're sitting. But DRX are
pretty close to them, right? Like they
are the threat that's coming from the
bottom of the standings. Uh DNF not
likely to overtake with their one
victory that they have picked up so far.
And so Bros wanting to create some
distance between themselves and DRX.
It's kind of important here.
It's actually interesting cuz the two of
the Bros wins in series were DK. Like
all one they also two zero DK which
actually ended up costing DK the in
hindsight if they had 2-1 they wouldn't
have had the tiebreaker. Exactly. It was
it was a crazy set of circumstances. Uh
but bro have really struggled taking on
Eastern teams. That's actually the most
interesting part. And their consistency
was something that actually Duke, who
obviously now is their uh new head coach
commented on. He's like, "Guys, I think
that the peaks that we hit are actually
really respectable, but the floor when
we play bad, it is really rough. And my
goal, as we see him right there, is to
ensure that we don't hit those lows. I
just want to crank up at average level
cuz we know the highs are there, but
we've also seen Bro go from looking good
to just not doing anything three games
in a row and just kind of losing."
Yeah. And if they can get rid of those
lows, I think they could be very well in
contention for the first place spot
right with TK in a complete free fall
right now, but has to start here with a
dominant victory. Yep. We'll see whether
the Bros can make it a perfect week here
or whether it's going to be DRX coming
out with a bang with a bit of a newish
roster in comparison to what we've been
seeing from them prior. Right. Um Teddy
making his way back. I'm not sure what
to feel often times. I like I'm a huge
Teddy fan, but I just don't think that
he's necessarily had those same uh level
of performances that we've seen in the
past, right? Like back on the Glory Jin
Air days or, you know, on that 2019 SKT
roster that looked so incredibly good um
at least, you know, domestically that
year. Uh it's just has kind of been
shades of his former self is good old
Teddy. And we'll see whether he can buck
that trend, turn that one around, have a
bit of a renaissance here.
But so far we've got the Nico and the
Gwen taken away. Pantheon is going to be
the answering ban as the Azir is also
going to hit the deck. Um probably less
likely that we see Tia focus I guess as
often times it is a bit of like we're
fishing for an Azia first pick type ban
but Vi is still up. Varys is still up.
These are the important ones.
Looking at the Varys, looking at the
Rumble as well has been a main stay for
such a long time. We'll get Morgan Yoro,
you know, one of the one of our our
resident actual Yoro players.
The first one to win on it
so far this season with the new
iteration of the Yoro. Zenzou still open
as well. I think that we saw in the last
game what kind of power pick that can
still be.
Might just be the vibe, but I mean we
have seen that like a lot of teams
pretty happy to pick whatever into it,
take the Wukong away, things like that.
We have seen find a lot of success. So
maybe that priority is going to fall
down. Taking a lot of time to think
about it as the Tia ban will still come
through. Not wanting to give that one
over to Closer. I think a little bit
understandable when it is closer that
you're facing off against Tia has been
fantastic so far in 2025, but he does
have a lot of other picks that he can
certainly go towards. We'll see what the
first pick is actually going to be here.
Aurora still up as well.
I think that's going to be B1, but is a
definitely a power pick and it does
really fit with Closer's play style as
well. There are things like Lucian that
we've seen a lot of teams prioritizing
pretty highly, but instead it will be
the Annie like we saw in our first game
of our previous series. That one will be
locked in with Vi left up and available
as well. So, we could interestingly have
a very similar draft uh to what we saw
from T1 coming out of the Bros. Let's
see what DRX are going to answer this
with. Rumble is up. That's rich. I mean,
need I say more? Could just be
I don't think you do. I think the Rumble
would make a ton of sense here.
Well, Wukong.
Yeah, that's it's a it's a decent combo.
We also see this uh Wukong Priority
definitely one of the best junglers of
the patch. Also has a good match up into
Divi, which again, we talked about this
exact thing. Yeah,
not 2 hours ago.
This draft has happened before. It It
really has. Uh it's going to be the
Aurora takeaway instead though, which
Oh, bit of Rumble Denial as well. Means
that Morgan won't be able to lock that
one away safely.
I'm not going to lie. I think if you're
Morgan into Rich, I don't I think Aurora
top has a pretty high barrier of
execution. I know that matchup is rough,
but we'll see. Rich has uh found ways to
surprise me before.
Yeah, it doesn't really feel like a rich
champion. Uh I think you might be
alluding to his champion pool situation.
Yeah.
Uh Z going to be the option instead of
something like a VI. I do like this a
lot more. The setup that you have gets
the Zin in there. stack that knock up
while the uh stun is coming on through
from the Annie. I like it a lot. And the
Alistister is actually going to be the
choice here for Polo who had a bit of a
stinker in game one against DK and then
came back and smashed them. Look looked
absolutely fantastic in the next two
games of that series. We'll see whether
he can find that form earlier on. This
is a pivotal pick and a very big one
that Okay, bro can certainly take
advantage of as a Poppy is being
considered. This is a favorite for
Sponge in the past, but he's already
playing a Wukong. So, this would be for
Andal there towards the bottom side of
the map.
Yeah, unless they were going to get
waved with it and flex at the top. We
have seen that Poppy top in some
matchups. Keen has pulled that one out a
few times. True.
Don't think that's likely though.
Probably just going to be on this. So,
no AD carry have been picked yet.
Something we're going to look towards as
well as top. Now, DRX can obviously
keep that top lane match up for R5,
which I would love. Just pick an AD
carry here on four. You can go a lot of
different directions. Jin to me always
makes sense because you want to not be
anywhere near the Annie or the Zenzo and
you have a lot of damage in the rest of
your comp already. So I think it is
something you can definitely get away
with.
Siver going to be taken away here from
hype. C we saw rising to some popularity
over the last couple of weeks on the
previous patch and the Oriana going to
be taken away from Yahoo as that would
be a pretty scary top side. Although a
lot of magic damage. Jahu with a lot of
options as far as what he wants to play.
Teddy was of course a bit of a Ziggs
guy.
It's also interesting cuz like this
Oriana ban is they're kind of still
hedging their bets, right, as to where
this Aurora is actually going to go.
Y because we don't know for a fact it's
going to go one way or another. I
definitely do think it's one of the
match ups you can play into Annie
because you have uh ways to actually
trade with her even if you do get into a
range and you have a ton of safety
already outside of uh flash bears. I
think you do have uh a lot of ways to
make plays there. Mr. Senna taken away
as well. Do you want to know something
fun? Hit me. The first letter of all of
the names that DRX have banned spells
Pats,
which is kind of cute.
Oh, okay. With a double S. But
with a double S.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. So Pat, it's still
Pats.
But is Pats even a name? No. Pats as in
Oh, it's a pet with a doggo.
Ah.
Pato. That That's with an eo, not an a,
right?
What? No, pet. That That would be You
can pet a dog, but you can also pat a
dog.
Oh, you're right. Yeah.
In a When I was growing up, we didn't do
like we didn't say, "Can I pet the dog?"
We'd always only say, "Can I pat the
dog?"
So, I didn't really understand what pet
meant as a verb cuz a pet is your pet.
Yeah. No, I'm I'm also quickly quickly
losing the plot. Um, but I do I am happy
you pointed it out cuz I would have not
have known it otherwise.
There we go. Now everyone knows and now
we're completely off track. The miss cuz
we knew this is what we were saying.
They're picking a carry on four.
Yeah.
And then they're going to counter pick
for Rich, which is going to be Atrox cuz
it's Ridge.
That's my guess.
There's a Scion for Morgan. That's why
I'm saying we're going to need some big
damage here from Hype. Let's see what it
is going to be. Pol's taking his time
figuring out what are we going to be
playing into this Corki.
Corki has a lot of safety as well into
what the amount of dive that is
available. Now, there is still the
potential for this to not be a rich pick
and just put the Aurora at the top, but
Ambessa kind of conceding the early
lane, but having even more dive and with
this comp, I think that makes sense.
Yep. Extra tool to lock people down as
well for the Nefold.
And she has been a pretty good pick into
Zion that we've seen develop over the
last little while. So, an understandable
choice there. But of course, Morgan very
happy to just be a bit of a potato,
weather the storm, and then take control
in team fight. Scion and Alistister
together are going to be able to create
so much space here on the map for the
bros. And then Annie, Tibbers, and Corky
can get to work.
I I just can't get over the image of
Morgan the potato. Good.
I mean, he's just he's the it's the
potato train, you know? you just fly
into a team fight, hop off the rails,
and run a muck.
I think both drafts have things to look
forward to. I think the DRX draft, my
main qual with it is that the burden of
execution is a lot higher. I don't think
it's quite that easy to play. I think
you need to be very in sync with all
your team because you need to make sure
you hit the CC. This is uh this is
actually the newest evolution in fan
signs that I haven't this like I haven't
seen this before. the Levi opening up
the
That's great. And I assume it's cuz he's
a sponge, so he cleans as Levi does in
that
that play. That That's good stuff.
And and that that that's attack on
Titans, isn't it?
It is. I see. I know. An amin.
Okay. I know you're just saying this to
infury me and it's working. Good job.
You're welcome. All right. It's time to
get to some actual fan chance. Let's go.
[Music]
[Applause]
I'm really glad that uh Chad appreciates
Ammon.
That one I'm never going to stop using
for the rest of my life. Feels good.
You know, that's a that's a rapper as
well.
Really?
Yeah.
Isn't that Eminem?
No.
Oh,
he's good.
Well, there you go.
Yeah, that's a new one. Speaking of
rappers, you know that guy that um uses
samples from all of the Ocarina of Time.
No, but that sounds very cool.
And then remixes them with like famous
um
rap songs.
No, but that sounds very cool.
It's It's called um Ocarina of Rhyme.
It's on YouTube.
Sounds really good. I
The one with the Goron City theme is
just the best.
I will look it up when I get home if I
don't forget,
which which I will. So, please send it
to me. No,
definitely send it.
I would appreciate that. Can you like do
you know the like do you remember the
song in like Goran village? Do you want
to sing it a little bit just in case
people don't remember?
No, I do not want to do that. Uh for
many reasons.
Do you want me to try?
I'm very happy to listen.
It is a very it's a very uncomfortable
take take it away at
well it's bro and brew. We got we got
you got 15 minutes.
Something you can do in a bro and brew
that.
We don't we don't we're not in any rush.
Everyone know everyone's that that's
here right now knows this as well.
Yeah. Okay. That's a good point. It's
the one that goes like
that one, you know?
Yeah. I
I feel like I didn't do it justice. It's
been a while since I've uh lie to when
it comes to a time. Mine is a
you you know the one
that one.
Yeah. But I don't want to do too much.
I'm I'm you know I want to I guess it's
fine. We can hum. I think we got we got
plenty of uh plenty of humming in our
future if this series is going to go the
way we expected to. As you mentioned
prior, you can see some full clearing
going on between our two junglers.
Closer and Yahoo are just hanging out.
It's probably the best we've seen an
Annie do in the early levels against a
Aurora,
as I say it.
Um I I was wondering about this. So, cuz
if I remember correctly, but I wanted
your check on this as well. The
inventors of the term bro and brew were
Brendan Feld and and Wolf. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. They were the Bro and Brew.
The Bro and Brew and Yeah. the
originators. Yeah.
Um cuz I I I don't know. I got in a
conversation with someone about this
recently. I'm like I'm 99% sure it was
the two of them.
It was.
And I'm glad to be have that. I It's
important that we keep track of the lore
of the LCK.
Yeah. You got to work out where the
origins are.
Yeah. Well, we can't just
as just let that go. I'm sorry closer
for mention mentioning anything about
this lane being fun because it has
discontinued to be fun. Did manage to
find at least a little bit back there.
That was actually a pretty good uh No,
no, no, no. It's still awful for Closer
having a terrible time.
Don't worry for I got your back.
Hopping on throughout the Let's be real
here.
Oh yeah, that's true. I mean
is the What's the What's the tech
situation by the way?
The Britex. I mean I got mine in and we
do have a Oh, here we go. Got another
highlighted one talking about scrambling
some eggs and stuff and there's barrel.
Watch too much barrel. Yeah, that's uh
honestly
that's what that that may have broken
our brain. That's why I'm singing gor on
city theme. But honestly, Ocarina of
Rhyme, look it up. It's amazing. It's
incredible.
And that one I think it's ASOP.
Oh, I didn't tell you my favorite. Uh
actually, you would love this.
So, at MSI, I had a fan come up to me
and he was like, "Hey, so uh you know,
I'm sure you get me me and Draco were
casting." He was like, "I'm sure you get
asked this a lot, but can you sign
something?" Like, "Yeah, no problem." I
was like, "It might be a little weird."
I'm like, "I don't know what's going to
happen."
Uhhuh.
And he pulls out
a Carly Ray Jeepson album.
He pulls out a motion atlas and then
obviously I I took a picture with him
cuz my guy, I need a picture with you.
That's amazing.
That is absolutely Sorry, I signed it.
And then he also had a really cool fight
stick that Draco Si signed as well. It
was just like it was
that is rad.
No, it was awesome.
That's like bringing the right things to
the party as gets knocked up momentarily
and it's an even trade.
Oh,
this is
minutes at left.
This do be a bro and brew don't it?
Very very nice. Organ is going to go
home for a moment. Yes.
Your your your beverage of choice. Are
you still part cuz I remember uh the tea
you make me I I still think of falling.
I want to say it was Australian
breakfast.
It was no Melbourne breakfast.
Melbourne. Oh, even better.
It's very nice.
It was It was good.
That's a That's a T2 if uh any uh any
Australians, they would know.
Can Can is it only an Australian
exclusive?
It's an Australian brand, but I think
you can get it kind of everywhere.
Probably can. I got a few bags left.
Oh my god. I had to look into that. That
sounds wonderful. Don't you worry about
that one. They also sell a lot of like
really nice like mugs and stuff like
that.
I'm good in the mugs, but I definitely
do want more of the tea.
Yeah, it's good. Good stuff.
It would be great. Now, imagine us
I know we could actually brew and brew
with brewing some tea
as almost did the thing.
Almost almost action there.
Yeah.
Pre 10 minutes.
My bro versus TRX not happening. Um, two
teleports did get used. Wait, three of
them. I tell a lie. as Morgan did use
his to get back down towards the bottom
side.
Interesting.
As the lane swap has begun,
started here by the bros. Level six, the
train will be unleashed.
Not yet.
Choo choo.
Obviously, um because we need time. Do
you know what I did?
Tell me. I watched Pacific Rim.
Had you had you never watched it before
or
No, I've watched it many times, but it's
such a good play.
Oh, it holds up so well.
Oh, exceptional.
You know what I watched? What did you
watch?
Transformers 1.
Oh my. Same energy.
Wait, I know.
Entirely.
I know, dude. I I that that movie
actually kind of blew me. It was way
better than I thought it was going.
Oh, dude. Transformers one is that
that's the good. They should have
stopped there.
Yeah, we've got an exhaust down. Cyclone
to answer it though. And there's a
decoy. It's not exactly the target you
want to engage onto. Crocco does have
the crescent guard though as Yahoo is
just going to get inside the circle and
see whether he can get something done.
And the answer is he absolutely can
before he dies. Closer now looking for
some angles here as Tibis is going
ballistic. He picks up a double kill.
And this is why you do not underestimate
the big burning bear. Burn bear burn as
Sponge and Yahoo go down. Nicely done
there by the Bros in the extended fight
as it is an early skirmish. I thought
with the power of Cyclone, maybe they
could have uh could have gotten
something going, but it is the extended
chase there onto Crocco that I think
ends up costing them their lives as as
you highlight those damage shots for
Clos is going to be feeling really good
in that one. I don't think they have
kill threat here, but maybe they get a
summoner or two.
Yeah, they're going to get the barrier
out from Teddy does make it underneath
the turret. There is a nice little
bullet time to soften up hype
momentarily as the teleport will bring
back into the lane.
Still took a big chunk though. That's a
BF sword as well for Teddy. Obviously
building towards that BT. Uh no, and I
need to clarify. I'm not talking about
the first Transformer movie.
Oh, I'm talking about Transformer 1,
which is a separate animation film that
is really good.
Oh, yeah. With
I thought you were talking about Shy of
Boo.
No, no, no, no. I'm talking about like I
want to say Chris Hemsworth. Wonderful
film. Would highly recommend.
Oh, there you go.
Uh so again here, one of the big things
with Zenzo is that if you actually want
to kill him, you do have to commit. But
it means that both Sponge
and Yahoo flash over a wall while Annie
is just going completely unchecked. So
uh closer just gets multiple rotations
off. Tippers is burning. So I think they
just let I think you just take the hit.
Let Crocco flash and then don't try to
overchase as we have another fight on
our hands.
Yeah, another bear is ready to come out
as well. We're making it rain in the
river which is a little bit unnecessary.
It's already pretty wet. That's all
right. Flash comes in from closer.
throws down the bear, gets a brilliant
incinerate to make sure that Yahoo is
dead before he can really do anything.
Teddy now in trouble as the rockets are
raining
and Hype is looking to chase them down.
The decoy not going to be doing any of
much as Teddy is going to spend his
first little stint in the death chamber
here after his trip back to the LCK
after 90 days. And now some more grubs
likely to go over to the Bros if they do
want to take them because they've
already gotten two. That is guaranteed
objective from that one. And if you were
expecting burn like us might be getting
a little little caught off guard as
closer, he was the only one from the
previous scrimmage that held on to his
flash just goes for the flash play,
finds two Andu and without that damage
of the Aurora, this fight is just over
before it begins. Nice chase there.
Proco even I think got a wind up auto on
the clone.
Oh, yeah. Beautifully done. this guy
right here. I also really love flash
incinerate instead of flash tibbers
because he only had those two targets
that he could go for. And then make sure
like guarantee that you get the CC down
and then throw a bear on top. You know,
you've already made sure that you've got
the CC and then you commit the big cool
down.
That's a 9minute malignance there for
Closer.
My goodness, we are going to be seeing
even more bears
having a pretty good time here. Here's
Closer in the mid lane as Paulo just
lying and wait allowing Closer to play
as aggressively as he would like.
There's a few other movies I watched on
the play but it's so hard to keep track.
I watch the accountant again.
Me and Valdez watched it.
Oh, the the accountant is like a really
good plane.
It's a great play.
Never watched that normally.
No,
but it's it's really good for planes.
I didn't know that there's an
accountant, too.
And I I learned that. I don't know. I
don't know whether I'm going to take
that risk now that I'm not in a plane.
No, no, no. You do that on a that
whenever your next plane is
I feel like you know like the Denzel
Washington movie like the equalizer. I
feel like that would be an incredible
like series of films to watch on a plane
as well.
It would just watch watching him
revenging all over the place. Kind of
like Taken. I reckon Taken fits into
that sort of uh thing as well. And any
Jason Stathithm movie.
I am excited for the new Naked Gun
movie. Actually, I I I hope that they
I think Liam Niss might be able to do it
cuz it's hard cuz you're following up
after one of the greatest.
I mean, Leslie Nelson is probably one of
the funniest human beings to ever exist.
I'm with you.
And I don't even think like I'm not even
a huge Naked Gun fan. It's wrongfully
accused. If you haven't seen Wrongfully
Accused, just go and watch it. It is the
dumbest film to ever exist. And I almost
hurt myself laughing so much when I
watched it for the first time.
That's impressive.
It's extraordin I think it also holds up
because it's like it's very old, but
it's still just so absurd that it's f
it's it's brilliant. Absolutely
brilliant. If you haven't seen that one,
so your homework is watchfully accused
with Transformer 1.
Transformer 1.
Pacific Rim, but you've already seen
Pacific Rim. Let's be real.
Yeah. Yeah. I mean, everyone's already
seen Pacific Rim.
And if not, just watch. Don't watch Two
by Mistake. Yeah, very important.
Oh, yeah. Yeah. No, that doesn't exist.
That also didn't exist on the plane. I
did, I admit, look for it cuz I was
like, "Wow, that was a great film. I
could just go and watch the second one
now."
Thankfully, didn't actually do that. Um,
but the other thing you got to do is
Ocarina of Rhyme. Make sure that you're
listening to some of that. Uh, some of
We are We are really
We got a lot of homework. There's a lot
to be done. uh don't do it now because
we have some video games that we are,
you know, uh in in in the in the middle
of um that you you may not have realized
kind of like us. Uh yeah, Morgan
catching waves and you can see having a
look as far as the benefactors of all of
this has been hyping closer. It's where
all the money has gone. It feels pretty
good
and it makes these fights hard to play
out as well because you need to ensure
that this and he is taken out uh
basically immediately
otherwise you are going to be in a very
very tough position. The amount of
damage that close is going to be able to
do is a big deal. The the lead isn't
that crazy though.
I just remembered another film. Do you
like Dracula movies?
Uh sure. We actually went and watched
Noseratu together, didn't we? We did.
Another one that might be a little bit
more serious. Is this as serious as
well? Yahoo. Taking a bit more serious
than Noseratu.
Yeah, a little bit more serious is uh
Dracula Dead and Loving It. Another
Leslie Nelson film.
Does not you should definitely watch
like most serious Atlas.
Very good. very probably the best and
most uh historically accurate um
they really are just kind of running
away with the game uh right in front of
our eyes.
They really are. Hype doing a great job
here towards the bottom side really
putting that Trinity Force through its
paces. 35 health on Tibers still
pushing. Look at that denial of 50 gold.
Never mind. He's just going to give the
50 gold over to Yahoo. That's crazy,
man.
Okay. Well, he did that. That's just to
try and deter him from stopping the
back.
Oh, you know what else I watched? What
did you Mia?
Oh, wow.
Yeah,
I don't know whether I'd advocate for
that one necessarily. Although,
do you know what? The vibes were great.
Yeah, that's the thing. And I actually
heard that the vibes on set were also
great cuz like I think it was like an
interview with Pierce Broman that I
watched at some point where like
my favorite
him and the other singer.
Yeah, him and the other guys are just
like, "Oh, we were just having a good
time. We just got to be bimbos. That he
literally said that. It was just
I'm not surprised.
It's just brilliant. And so I think I
could watch that movie and be even
happier watching it this time without
context.
Knowing that everyone is actually just
vibing. They're not just
brilliant. All right, Teddy taking a
little bit of damage here in the mid
lane as Polo being a bodyguard to hype.
Just doing so much work,
man. Maybe that's a rewatch. That could
be a rewatch coming up. It's just it's
just fun, right? You just know you're
going to have a good time.
And all right, Polo getting some deep
vision down. Don't really have too much
to fight for outside of this Herald
that's coming up in 10 seconds time. And
Sponge. Oh dear, that's two for the
price of one on that pulverized. But the
cyclone is going to return the favor.
But never mind. There are just too many
bros and just not enough TRX in this
area. Although Sponge is lasting a long
time. And And he will just send them
back home. But that is a big cool down
that they will not have to stop this
herald from going down. So Shelly will
belong to the Bros. There's nothing that
DRX can do about it.
I kind of want to see a replay. How did
Sponge get so desync from the rest of
his team? I feel like the Chase lost it
forever. It feels like the rest of his
team just either he was too far forward
or the rest of his team should have been
there to back him up earlier because you
know that Herold is going to be the main
objective on the minds of the Bros.
All right, Crocker just will be taking
that one down.
That was enough. keepers verdict a very
big tool actually for DRX in this
composition and as soon as that ends
cyclone are down what else are you going
to do you know it's just not a whole lot
of options that you will have and
composition from ahead just seems
impossible to play into as well
it's it's really I I think either of
these comps if you get a lead because
there are so short range we we talk
about this a lot I think at least for
bro you have some combat mechanics in
the raw power of your front line as you
get later into the game for DRX I don't
really think that's the case.
Yeah, outside of like a great old from
Undeil, you can't always create a
numbers advantage. So, that's something,
but there's a bit of a tough situation
and they're probably going to have to
fight. They don't want to give over too
many dragons. Thing that I'm loving is
that they're keeping up the pressure as
maybe this is a bridge too fast.
Deadpass presence. He's going to be able
to pull Crocco away. He does have to
flash, but now Morgan makes his way in
and he is a bit of a monster. Rich is
dashing around but not able to find too
much of an angle. And this was all
without closer. Now he turns up. Bear at
the ready and the bros are ready to team
fight. There is no cyclone and that
keeper's verdict is still a little while
away these early levels.
So they do have to be a little bit
careful. There's the flash in. They look
for the angle on ridge. He does flash
himself away as Yahoo going to be able
to buy some space between worlds. DRX
though still not quite able to get
themselves in there. Step presence is
good. Bullet time even better to soften
up the cow. And once again, Tibis is
going to donate 50 gold this time over
to Rich. In goes, can he find it? Yes,
he just gets headbutted out though as
Polo will get slammed into the wall. And
Bro just kind of playing with their food
for so long that the food bit back.
I want your food to bite you. But
somehow bro on the receiving end of that
as it felt like they had a lot of
windows there to actually commit but
kind of keep kept going for these half
engages and DRX shrug off a lot of that
damage as we take uh
okay I thought we were going to get into
we take the river take a look
as the timing is a little better to just
kill rich and that should be the end of
it but it's this overextension into
Teddy when he or into on rider when
Teddy is completely safe. That kind of
ends up cooking them cuz it means Paulo
and He are both taken relatively low.
Then Paulo has to use his that times out
and they just they get the cyclone and
the keeper's verdict. Back off cool down
and they have them exactly when they
need them.
And it's a big win for DRX. Gets them
the dragon. Get them a kill as well and
ensure that this game. We know this is a
free gamer though, right? So,
uh, every game this year between these
two teams, I think has been, uh, free as
riching Morgan.
Well, once he has cleaver, I think he
actually does kind of cook him. He does
still does a good amount of damage, but
actually killing him, I think, is still
something else entirely.
Yeah, Rich given the good old thumbs up
there as he was at least got to do some
exercise as he wandered down the lane.
Morgan just going to be able to catch
this. Shouldn't be too much of a worry.
But if that is how the bros are going to
be out are going to be piloting these
team fights, could be a little bit of a
worry because that was some
indecisiveness. Crocco also deciding to
go into the one guy that you know has a
very good answer for Adacious Charge is
not exactly optimal. So they're going to
have to turn that one around if they
want to make something happen here as
hype does hit that two item spike. Man,
that is a very accelerated cork th000
gold in the lead against Teddy for now.
And it looks even worse because it's one
item and you know two little swords
against the uh manam imammune and the
trinity force already completed here for
hype does have both of his summoners
now. So this corki going to be a big
part of any fights that are coming up
and I think the teams have shut us up
chronicler I don't think it's time to be
talking about Leslie Nelson movies right
now. Well I mean right now we definitely
can cuz there's not going to be a fight
for the next 3 minutes. Yeah, but I mean
there's stake to be set. Stakes stake
setting.
Still that's just another reference to
the vampire movie, my man. I I'm just
saying.
Damn, he got me.
Yeah,
I haven't I haven't thought about that
one by me.
I honestly haven't thought about dead
and loving it for such a long time. I
really need to watch that again.
I love how you frame it as well as a
more serious vampire movie than
Noseradu, which was as realistic as a
vampire movie really could be. It's very
true.
Well, we are just starting Oticon.
Okay, bro. This is never not working.
We are proactive here today.
Uh-huh. Clos are going to get a little
bit of cannon gold and then move on
back. We are backing away from the
Articon.
That is a good call. I don't think we
should be doing Artacon into the um MF
Wukong and Aurora. I feel like that's
not a good call. And they don't. So, I
I'm loving that.
Yeah. All right. Well, Yahoo is just
going to be able to clear out some
vision. Mhm. So, some resets will ensue.
Not too much to worry about. So, keeping
it within touching distance, our DRX,
it's under a 2,000 gold lead, at least
for the moment. And here at 21 minutes,
that is not too much of a big deal. They
also have that extra dragon. It's a
chem. Um, of course, orcs not working
today, so not paying too much attention.
We did get a chem soul in our last game
as well.
When we was paying attention, we got
like 15 mountains, so I I'm glad that at
least a little bit.
The mega mountain day was odd. There was
no Oh, it it carried over. I think there
extra mountain as well.
Yeah. Yeah. Like two or three more. It
was crazy. Damn, that's weird.
I know. It was. We've never really been
inundated with mountains. It's only ever
been chemex and clouds.
All right. And his really got a good W
finger. He just knows when to press that
button. But bro also really like using
all of their dashing abilities into the
Poppy,
which you you know I ideally you
wouldn't do, but he is the one that has
to face check, right? He is the target
that's being presented the majority of
the time. So very very good that he can
just press W when he needs to.
Tier
for Hype still not fully uh fully
stacked. Only has a few left to go.
Imagine he's running around asking my my
kingdom for a tier. Yeah, please let me
hit some stuff. He's got a last whisper
now as well. My goodness. This uh Corki
pretty accelerated. Same thing can be
said for Teddy, but he doesn't have the
extra item that has been put up here for
hype.
Can't believe you just I I I'm really
trying to get you off the rails again.
My
Oh, no. I'm I'm locked back.
My kingdom for a tier. Come on, Atlas.
So obvious.
What do you mean? Oh, tears of the
kingdom. Aha, I'm there with you now.
But no, it's too late. I don't want to
talk about it anymore.
You said you said kingdom. I was
thinking of Kingdom of Heaven. You
remember that? Um
I do remember that movie. That's where
the meme comes from, right? Like the the
guy going like what Duro did the maybe
to shut up. I'm pretty sure it is.
Edward Norton in the surprise role that
no one knew it was him perhaps. I don't
quite remember.
Maybe. I do remember Duro doing that,
but I thought that that was more just a
Duro thing.
Oh no. I think it was just a doro thing,
but I know it's also a me as a drake
gets taken and we go two to two. Yeah.
So, it's evening out the dragons. We're
making sure that we get as many chem as
we possibly can have.
So, there are, you know, there's the
possibility of another three we can lock
in for everyone. And's going to turn up
towards his top side. Decides not to
give his position away as still a
target. Still something that they're all
going to have to consider. 1,000 gold as
a lead for Bro means basically nothing
at this stage. And oh my goodness, like
how many five more stacks something
there? There it is. Hype manages to lock
it down. Minds a few cheeky autos.
That's going to be able to get that
evolution. A lot of extra damage now
available here for the Corki as Morgan
is just getting hit by Rich. Man, it
just takes a lot of effort, doesn't it,
to get through this scion. Yeah, he's
he's definitely will be able to now in
the long run because he has Eclipse as
well as cleaver as bro. I think they're
just going to keep doing these fake outs
and keep seeing if the BRX response is
good.
Yeah,
maybe they I think he back off if they
if Rich TPS cuz obviously Morgan can
join with his but now they've stalled
for so I think they can just take this.
Well, the teleport is going to come in
but it feels a little bit late here.
Crocco in perfect position to rotate
over from Sponge. But they're holding on
to him. They do want to be able to burst
this one down. And Crocco is almost
dead. The public execution comes down,
but it misses and the cyclone comes in.
The knockups are good, but that one's
even better as the bullet time does help
secure the kill onto the jungler. And
there is the steel. DRX, they managed to
deny the Bros. And the Bros just wanting
to get themselves out of here. Poly
decides instead though that he wants to
go back in. And perhaps to get
themselves out of there was a better
choice as down goes the Annie as well.
Morgan and Hype just wondering what the
heck just happened because it all went
wrong. Bit of a split call there for
Bro. I think you can fully commit to the
team fight, make it work, or you can
fully commit to taking out a you can
make that work. Instead, they kind of do
both. And as a result, neither because I
want you to look. Crocco is up. Crocco,
my man, you don't have resistances. You
can't do that. Has to maybe wouldn't
have gotten hit, but I think the flash
makes sense cuz if Rich hits you, you do
end up dying. And then Rich is in the
back line. He can obviously deal with
these people.
But this all comes down to them being
completely shredded unnecessarily.
Atlas.
Yeah. And Paulo like going back in
because he knew that he was dead. But
you could see like a little bit of
movement there from closer to get back
in as well. I think he was probably also
guaranteed dead. But DRX, they just find
their way in, bro. Open the door. And
DRX say why. Thank you.
Teddy, I think his ults have been on
point.
Yeah, really good.
Actually been having a good impact here.
It's been a good champion for him in in
his career as well to this Fortune. It's
always He's always been one of these
guys that we do tend to trust on it.
So, good to see that he still has the
angles.
And now we've got a very honest game of
League of Legends on our hands. But from
the other direction, right, we were
talking about Alfro have the slight
lead. Now it's TRX that have the slight
lead, but they also have Articon buff on
top of it as Sponge is taking some
damage from Crocco. Crocco is just
looking for his way through.
Blast will get spun out to safety.
It's not about what you fight for, it's
about fighting.
I've never heard that said about bro
ever before. Atlas,
we are we are I I was a little worried
with the start, but we are currently
sitting at nine kills at 26 and 1/2
minutes. So,
it's not exactly the most bloodthirsty.
It feels more action-packed than it
otherwise could be, though.
like DRX the obviously they've already
got themselves back into a golden but
even if they were down like one 2k gold
at this point I don't think it matters I
think it's just going to be the fights
cuz what's going to happen in either of
these fights is a team is going to fully
blow all their cooldowns on a member
whether they die or you overextend and
lose
as that CP is a dead giveaway that this
is happening
well there are a lot of pings in the
area here for DRX's going to walk over
this ward and find things out as the
Baron's down to 50%. It's not exactly a
massive amount, but Andal, remember,
does have to keep his verdict.
They got the old. They can get rid of
them. Morgan going to be able to blast
his way out. Mega cones abound for the
disengage.
So, Apollo really wants to back. Will
got spotted here. TRX, they can slow
play this. They already got a lot of
health and out Apollo. Wow, Teddy really
taking matters into his own hands, but I
don't know about that one.
No, that I do. Wasn't great. Um,
I think it's fine if you're not looking
to fight, but Drake is up in 30 seconds.
That old from Teddy I think is a big
mistake. I actually think that might
have been bettering in the fight that's
about to come up. Also, hi has hit free
items, so I think he really wants to
fight. Closer also has a stopwatch or
rather arm guard, but can freeze time.
They're starting it up again as Oh, DRX.
This one might work,
bro. Are we are we even going to like
walk over there? We don't have any way
to check this.
No, it's it's it's definitely gone.
It's just gone. Yeah.
Down to 5,000. The dragon has spawned.
Polo, I think, has an idea of what's
going on here, but he just can't face
check. And so the Baron's just going to
get secured here by DRX under the nose
of the bros. And yeah, they might be
able to get a dragon, but it's a
consolation chem. And that doesn't ever
feel good. And so DRX have really just
taken this game back. If it was soul, I
think it would have been fine. But it's
not even soul. It's soul point. Atlas.
Yeah. You know what, bro? I don't care.
It's fine. Just give Nash did. This is
so weird, though, isn't it? Because like
they did. That did happen. Watch that
happen.
And also, this team is is like mostly
old sandbox, right? It's not even really
bro anymore, but it's still the same
Bro. It's still We can do things in the
early game to create a lead. And then we
stop doing stuff,
you know,
and then you the enemy just takes all
the stuff.
Atlas, the funniest part. It is It's as
you're saying, it's the same with every
or KT. It doesn't matter how many points
you change. It's just KT.
Yep.
Um I can't believe I'm saying this, but
DK, it's just it's just TK.
Although they did bring barrel back.
There's examples of this in every
region. You know, there's Fnatic uh in
the LC. There is TS in the LPL.
It's true.
Sometimes it's just the vibes.
There used to be a lot in the uh in the
LTA/LCS, but I mean TSM hasn't been
around for a while.
I know. It's a shame.
I do think the team changed quite a lot
when it went from Rainman to Dyrus.
I would say
cuz Dyus Who is your favorite like OGT?
For me, it's Oddwan. Yeah, I love the J.
Oh, Owan's fantastic. Yeah, I think it's
I think it's like he's almost the
objective right choice. I always like
Chaox as well.
That's right. Yeah. Who does manage to
take down this turret? We are extending
this Rebel Baron power play really,
really far.
We really are hitting a variety of
topics as well. I think this bot lane
turret might have to give it up, bro.
We'll see if they really want to play
for a heavy contest with this uh super
or empowered rather double cannon. I
don't know if they can really do that
much. They do have five members in the
area. The ambassador's rotating around
as well, but there goes down. They're
going to look for Andel who goes down
very low. It's a late steadfast
presence. But now between Wills, a
massive knock up though as Morgan finds
the angle, but the cyclone is just too
good. And yes, Morgan might be
surviving, but unfortunately he's lost
his Annie and his Corki is a little too
low, so he's just going to get cut down
where he stands. Oh no, bros. That was a
backbreaking fight. And TRX utilize
their Baron sneak. It turns into a 6,000
Rebel Baron power play. And the game
might just be over right here. Might
just look for the end. It's been a
Sponge and Rich
duology in these fights. The two of them
just finding the back line again and
again. And even though Teddy gets his
all interrupted, I don't think it really
matters as Rich dancing around deathless
on this Ambessa. Yeah, having a great
time. And we know like Rich actually had
some pretty good performances as Pul
going to hit a couple in the backline
there as Yahoo does die. And in fact, a
couple of people die to Hype who does a
fair bit of damage, but it does not
matter. This nexus is still going to go
down if Teddy has anything to say about
it. And he does. He says, "Bring it,
Bros. We'll take you in game one." And
we'll see whether the Bros can do it
again. Last time around, they did manage
to bounce back, but uh this this was a
rough one because they had it and then
they just kind of let it slip.
It is the classic example of I and I
don't I don't think the game was won
early on but they were in a commanding
lead and and then they threw it out of
and then they never really got control
back.
Yeah,
as a Sponge fan I am joyous. I am happy.
Thinky had a great game on the Wukong.
Teddy actually a clean MF performance as
well. Not the easiest game to play MF.
They also kept their heads in it, right?
Like this was a team that were slowly
but surely losing their grip on the game
and they said, "No, we got to do
something. We got to make our way back
in." Intelligent play around vision
control and just caught bro napping.
Caught them thinking that perhaps it was
time for a reset. It was not. It was
time to do Baron yet again
and they committed to the play. Made it
work. You can have a look at it in the
gold graph there. And as soon as they
had that lead, it was all over. There's
that man on your screen, the sponge.
And I think that Wukong is really,
really strong. That he played a
fantastic Wukong game.
And to be able to take it away from the
Bros after that level of control was
very impressive. Time for us to go to a
short break. When we get back, the space
going to break that one down. We'll have
game number two. See you soon.
[Music]
Heat up
here.
[Music]
[Applause]
Heat. Heat.
[Music]
At
least
The time has come to prune the tree.
Much has changed and I do not understand
why. Not truly
set upon them.
The eye sees. The fist crushes.
Heat. Heat.
[Music]
I mustn't take a single breath for
granted.
[Music]
I feel
[Applause]
[Music]
Hello and welcome back to the LCK space.
I am Valdez, still joined by Wolf and
Wad. And that was DRX taking down Dh
game number one up against Bro. It was a
pretty close back and forth game. It
felt like Bro was in the lead for quite
a while, but then a couple of major
mistakes in the mid to late game kind of
led to their demise. Guys, what went
wrong for Bro there?
Bro's early game has been pretty clean
most of this year, right? I mean,
they're Kespa Cup champions. They did
they did take that title, but since the
very beginning of January, this team has
been able to generate pretty significant
leads against even top teams. It's what
happens in the Midame trying to leverage
that lead where sometimes they trip,
they stumble, they fall. That's what
happened here where they had a lot of
control. They tried to use Oticon as a
stepping stone and uh you know they kind
of you know when you step from stone to
stone they they kind of fell in the
river.
Yeah. I mean I think a lot of top tier
team finally figured out that other is
not that valuable to uh give your life
to the enemy team. Uh you just use the
artakan as a fight method. You know you
just bait them and bait their TP or even
though you lose the not over yet. I mean
it's just whatever. It's not just like a
Nasher or fourth Drake soul. So I feel
like uh I I just think that bro just
didn't uh prioritize uh uh value yet
about the Atakan. I think that was the
main part why they lost the on the
Atakan fight here.
Yeah, I I think that's definitely true.
Um, I would say that also a lot of our
top teams are recognizing the power of
Aurora and it felt like uh Krakco and
the Bros didn't really understand the
power of it and we can actually see
exactly what I mean here in highlight
number one. 24 minutes in, they're
trying to bait on the Oticon and it goes
horrifically wrong as they run straight
at the Aurora. Up until this point, I
was talking to Valdez the whole time. I
was like, "This is a great call. They're
using the pressure. They're trying to
control this tri bush trying but then
everything goes wrong when Kro decides
to like try to hold Oticon then look for
an engage when he's at zero health and
then this opens everything up because
the rest of the team has to kite back.
So Teddy is getting value with this MF
as he pushes forward. If Bro had looked
for a faster turn and played through the
choke point which half of the team was
doing instead of trying to stick onto
the Oticon like Crocco was doing before
he looked for the lackluster turn. I
still think this call is correct. It's
not because you're trying to get the
Oticon. It's because you're trying to
use the lead and the control you have
over the map to force that fight, but
the turn was just so poor. It was so
poorly executed that they just got wiped
and lost the game over it.
Yeah, I think uh whenever you play
around this objective, you have to check
the objective HP. I think the level of
the HP is the 6k. The that's the lowest.
So after that, I think you have to stop
hitting the objective and turn. But if
you're hitting more than that, then that
becomes really interesting cuz it's
lower than 6k, then enemy team can
actually just have the objective. So at
that point, you start to confuse
yourself. And I think that's the the
reason why bro kind of confused in that
point.
Yeah, I mean it can be difficult, you
know, to get all five players on the
same page and to get the exact right
turn. It was obvious that that's this
was kind of the opposite of that, the
exact not right turn. And uh immediately
DRX were just waiting with open arms to
take that one down. And they did so as
well in highlight number two which was
the ending fight of the game actually
where this Aurora all just gets massive
value in this fight. It's an attempted
flank here from Bro. They look for the
pick unfortunately onto the very very
tanky Poppy and then Wukong Aurora.
You're in the circles. You are in the
death chamber. Even this MF ultimate on
the side is tangentially relevant. The
combo here is so strong for D. I mean
just look at your scion position is not
structured team fight again your scion
is on the bot side your tank cannot just
be on your front that means the
structure of the team fight is already
destroyed if like if you get the one
kill and when you're behind just be
happy with it small victory just set for
next play but I think the overchase is
always bad whenever you are behind and I
think it was just a horrible fight at
the end
I liked bros draft I like the position
they had in this him. If they executed
better on Oticon or look for trying to
threaten Oticon and rather instead of
trying to hold it or played that topside
fight a little bit differently, we're
probably looking at a bro one zero,
right? So, you've got to keep yourself
mentally on the right page, on the right
mindset moving into game two, knowing
that game one was a winnable game.
You've still got strong drafts in the
bag. I mean, or just relax a little bit
more. Even though Atakan is up in the
map, there is still a Drake and Nasher
to go on. And I feel like uh you're not
the one who's like really feeling
rushed. You know, if enemy team is
behind, they can start the ATA is more
risky and you can actually go on the
objective and take the better fight. But
I feel like whenever bro is ahead,
they're just like, "Oh my god, we are
ahead. We have to finish the game
earlier." And now like we're panicking
cuz we can't finish the game, but you
have to relax and just chill chill a
little bit more in game. And I think
whenever they have the early game lead,
it feels good. But in the mid late game,
they just need to fix the calls and uh
the plans in in game. Yeah, I mean
that's how I feel. You know, it's just a
little thing. But yeah, just happy with
the small victory.
Yeah, also something to mention, you
know, Edgar was uh released from the
team and also they have brought in Duke.
So pretty interesting to see what he's
going to be able to do with uh Bro here
in rounds three to five of the LCK. But
we're done here on the space, guys.
Let's throw it back to Atlas and
Chronicler for the cast.
Thank you very much, Valdoast, for that
one. Absolutely fantastic breakdown
there of game number one. And do you
know what? Juke has already showed us
that he can do it. That he can turn the
ship around because DK beat them in game
one. And by Jove. After that, it did not
look close.
I had to because of the by Jove.
Yeah. I don't know why I went with the
That was that was warranted, right?
Yeah. No, fair enough.
I can't wait to see what the next game
is going to bring us. I think that we
are yet again graced with peak LCK.
Oh yeah.
And what type of peak? That's the beauty
of art. It can be anything you want it
to be.
Exactly. You got to get to the top of
the mountain before you know what that
peak is going to look like.
Have you Have you heard of the game
Peak, by the way?
Peak.
We should play it. It's like you climb a
mountain and and it's very funny.
It's like getting over it.
No, you like you climb the mountain in
it. It's like co-op. You climb a
mountain.
Oh, that actually sounds pretty cool.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, we should. We should.
That'll be good.
All right. Well, Nico is going to get
banned away yet again. Nico, Gwen, and
Varys were the bands on the blue side
last time around for the Bros. Remember,
the Bros had blue side in game one and
did not quite find the victory. So, we
might have just mirrored bands here.
Although the Varys is out of order.
might give away that we are looking at a
different choice over the Gwen or maybe
a Gwen first pick for the Lord.
Gwen first pick could be the case. I
think not having to deal with this Poppy
that seemed to be baiting them into all
sorts of frustrating fights.
Well, there was there was a lot, right?
I think that Morgan unfortunately also
didn't really have the impact on the
sign like especially looking back to
some of the replays. I think his fights
were lackluster. Obviously, the space
already went over Crocco's
decision-making. Also, I think Paulo
again, warm-up game from him on the
Alistister outside of the early game.
Uh, no, not for closer. I think closer
and hype really did all they could.
Yeah, the doing fine.
I
the more I see of them, it's again, we
need to remind everyone that the
difference between these two teams in
actual score is very minimal. And I
think it's cuz DRX do sometimes just
kind of make the right call again and
again. Yeah,
like in that game they were just falling
too far behind biting their time as Gwen
B. Is it like B1 or I don't think it
should be like
it's a bit of a pick your poison though,
isn't it? Because both the Tia and the
Azir are left off. So I expect neither
of those to be banned
and then they will pick Azir for closer
cuz he can play that.
Yeah,
that's a thing.
Although it might be good if you pick
Leah to have a better lane match up.
That might not be what they
So I I actually post nerves.
Oh god, they're just going to post buffs
to Azair. I'm like I actually think that
the
the matchup like it used to be really
favored. I don't think it still is. I
think the buffs to air which again kind
of mystified all of us at the OCK.
Yeah, given
I've already in by the way. I don't know
why they're taking so long.
What is this closer? If there is a guy
that's like no no I got to counter pick.
Look at his face. That's the man that's
like, "It's fine. I'll just pick Akali."
And then they're like, "Okay, closer. We
trust you."
I mean, honestly, he is closer. That is
something that he's very likely to do.
Tell me he wouldn't do that.
Oh, no. He would do that.
He would do that.
That might actually be the play. Oh, no.
No, no, no. You're You know what it is?
He's going to swway it. He's just going
to swain his way in. You remember that?
Is like that was his Azia counter pick
like a year ago, 2 years ago, something
like that. Yeah, I think there was a
time and place for Swain. Um, I don't
know when, but this is a no-brainer,
obviously.
Yeah, this was always going to happen.
Um, if if it's just if he just picks
Rise, I'm going to be so upset
because it's just not better.
I would like Gallo. I think Gallo into
Rumble is really good.
Gallo and Or I think are the two picks
that we've seen consistently work into
this top side menace.
What are we picking up here? eyes will
be a little lackluster.
Okay, so we're just playing R.
That is that is that is very actually
that is the most lift sandbox 2022 thing
that you could go for.
Yeah.
Uh this combo hasn't really worked
nearly as well. We do have to highlight
that.
Nope. I am uh
you're Yeah, I can hear I can hear the
bro Leaf dying in Atlas's voice, guys.
Well, no. I mean, it's not I just didn't
need them to make it way harder for
themselves, you know? That's that's all.
Okay, we're just Atrox and the Rumble.
Okay, Morgan, I kind of like that. Get
the lord on a on something that can do a
damage.
[Music]
Sponge like both Trundle and Scarnner go
so hard here by the way.
Yeah,
Sponge one of them. He is
He is more He's more of a Trundle guy, I
think. It's like out of tank play for SP
although he did spend a lot of time on
Sichuani.
Oh yeahani.
The Scarnner has been one of his better
picks in the past. But it will be the
Trundle.
I think it should have been Scarnner,
but if you're a jungler, you want to
play Trundle cuz you feel like you
actually get dead.
Yeah, Scarnner is here just feels feels
too good, doesn't it?
Oh, you're you're just like, "No, no,
no. That's that's too
How do you really feel? Tell me tell me
Atlas about this draft so far. I think
Azir is extraordinarily strong. He has
been for uh and he and he has been and
he's again and he even more so than he
was before.
Yep. It's fine. This is going to six
that we knew this coming into the day.
I don't think there's a way around it.
So, Bro is going to find a way to make
it happen.
They wouldn't deny us a game game six.
No, surely we're not. We're not. It's
not going to be a cringe fight. It's
never It's It's never And it's not going
to be Bro that fails to give us it.
Well, okay. But what if they thought
that DRX really needed this?
It's a really good point. And DX do kind
of need this.
What's the tech situation like, Atlas?
That's what I'm wondering.
Well, honestly, it's not very purple in
the chat right now. So, it might have
been that uh during this draft, they
just didn't quite uh get
they didn't hit the taxation donations
to to to reach the good picks. Uh
Tomkench is an odd ban. Maybe they were
expecting Teddy to just jinx because
Teddy has been known to jinx.
I think it could have been like Santa
Kench and then you if they if you pick
Santa Kench and
you don't have a way to dive, I think
you just lose the game. So they're going
to go what? Like chin. Lucian makes
sense. You're going to go Lucian Braum.
Lucian Braum is good.
Wouldn't mind it. Doesn't give them a
massive amount of engage, but when
you've got pillar and equalizer, I think
you're happy just to kind of fish for
pillar angles and then throw fire on
top.
I'm not going to lie. Uh they will
engage. I I don't know what Bro is going
to pick here, but there's not a lot
left. Like you can't really pivot away
from this composition.
Draven Pike goes so hard here for the
Bros.
I'm not about Polo Pike. I'm not going
to lie, you could go Jinx for like Jinx
actually I could see. I think hype has
actually been a really good Ash also
would be good follow up with the arrow.
Ezreal is a lot safer though and also
does do well into the Trundle and Azer
portion. I don't think it's great into
stealing away. So you go as as Braum to
not have to deal with that and then they
go what? Re
was banned. Oh yeah, you're right. I
them.
So it has to if they want engage it
almost.
I don't know about Leona.
Nautilus could have been
worse. Yeah.
Um Andel is giggling a lot. Maybe it's
Zach time.
I just I don't support Trundle.
I mean Leona like at least you can fish
with Al, right? It's something
doesn't feel great.
Maybe that was the master stroke. The
Bros were looking for the Braum pick for
Paulo here in this game. They have
plenty of other ways to get in there. Of
course, Crocco just presses R, throws
his whole body in. He didn't need an R
button to do that. We watched him do it
all game long in the previous one. So,
let's see whether the Bros can turn it
around. Turn it around is something that
they've been able to do in the past. And
by the past, I mean two days ago.
So bouncing back here should not be a
big surprise, but it was a a redside
victory there for DRX. Once again, the
Bros wear the same colored shorts as
they head towards the rift. We saw it
earlier on today though, Chronicler. It
doesn't really matter what side you're
on. If the vibes are on your side, you
can win. T1 showed us that as they took
away the winning streak for Gen.
Let's see how this one is going to go.
DRX fans looking pretty happy today.
Oh, what are we celebrating? I don't
know what we're celebrating.
Yeah, I don't know. I can't read.
I see a lot of hearts.
Yeah, I imag Is it Are we like Are we
getting married? What are we doing? Is
it the date? Married today?
Married today? What the heck? What? The
wedding was this morning and you're
like, "Oh, just get out of the gown, get
out of the tux, and let's just uh let's
just head to L Park."
Damn. I kind of love that.
That is swift. If that was like
Oh, so the legal the legal
ah legally married today. I was going to
say like they look surprisingly sober.
Uh from my experience in marriages a
little bit different here in Korea. I
think they they keep it a little bit
more cordial. Um as we have
I was at your wedding. I can
Yeah. Cordial. Cordial.
Can attest.
I said cordial like cordial like as in
you what you drink. Um so yeah. Uh,
that's impressive. If it's just signing
the paperwork though, that makes a lot
more sense cuz that was just you go to
the to the office
and then you sign some papers.
Then you sign some papers. That's what
you do.
But it doesn't really feel real.
It doesn't.
Cuz we both did that, right?
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I I also did it like a
year and a half late as well. Chair and
I weren't officially married till like a
year and a half after you did it the
other way around.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. We did it the
other way.
Wait, what? That's
cuz I don't I don't really need the
government to tell me whether I'm
married or not, you know?
Well, yeah, I guess. But that that is
the that I I mean I guess it depends on
how you look at it. Arguably the more
important part.
I mean, it depends. It depends what your
situation is, right? Cuz some people
like me, especially if you're in a
different country and like maybe you
need it for visa reasons and stuff like
that, but uh we didn't really need it
for any of that.
Oh, yeah. I would love a chaf as well.
Well, that's a fun one. That is a really
That's actually one of the cutest joke
drawings I've ever seen.
It's very cute.
That is adorable.
And it's all like almost like a bit of a
Renekton Choath as well, which is a very
Morgan theme, which I kind of really
enjoy.
It is the mashup.
Um, we just realized that uh there is a
pause um at this point in time.
That's fine.
We are take having a little bit of a
delay getting into the game. I only just
noticed now that it's been taking a
while after we had a very long
competition.
At least I think I'm not going to lie. I
think you're still
No, no. I think the real reason is
you're still upset about the Azir and
the the Ary and Vi.
I mean, I I had kind of forgotten about
the draft. I just didn't remember what
the champions were by this stage. Is
that a happy birthday for for Sponge?
It looks like a happy birthday for
Sponge. The 25th.
Happy birthday, Sponge.
Happy birthday, Sponge. Well, the uh 200
for DRX could certainly be coming in.
Could happen.
Unless the fans on this side have their
phones out and are in Twitch chat
donating, right? Donating the Broax.
That's what you need to get in there. As
the guy in chat is actually currently
saying, "Atlas, start the game." All
right. Sorry, mate. I'm
Atlas.
It's my bad. It's my bad. I should
probably
He's currently leaving.
Yeah, I should probably pop. Just give
me give me
All right. He is actually
I'm heading out. I'm just gonna jump
over.
He is. No, no, no, no, no. Atlas. No,
no, no, no, no. Please, please, just
What do you mean? I need to go and start
the game.
You can't jump down there. That's
dangerous.
But I also I can't walk through hands
and everything. And there's a guy right
there.
Yes, you can. Just walk to the stage and
press the button.
I'm a very live person.
Don't I
I'm quite live.
Atlas. Atlas, I know you're a tall guy,
but just you you got to stay safe. Yeah,
I think you you're dramat dramatic.
Oh, I'm overly dramatic and very caring
and worrying about your wellbeing.
Oh, did you watch um the the the K-pop
Demon Hunters movie?
No, but I've heard it's amazing.
It's pretty good.
So, yeah, cuz I I have to watch it with
my wife and she's not here yet. She's
coming to Korea soon.
So, we're watching it together.
Uh I've heard it's it's it's fun.
It's pretty good.
It's pretty good. Um, I watched it in
Korean cuz I watched it with my wife and
it was really interesting because a lot
of the songs are in English, right? And
so I'm listening to the whole thing in
Korean and the Korean like translation's
actually super good like for like the
dubbing or whatever.
Um, but then they just all of a sudden
go into English and it's like for the
songs and it's just kind of odd.
Sounds weird.
Yeah. So I think I might just watch it
again just in English. See how that
goes. But do you know what we're going
to watch now? It's a game two between
the pros and DRX and the Azer on red
side somehow. Let's get onto the rift.
[Music]
[Applause]
All right. Well, I started the game and
thank you very much for the tax there as
well. There was some Atlas start the
game tax that was put in that, by the
way, guys, that goes straight to me and
not to the bros. So, you need to also
put your bro tax in
if you just let the Atlas start the
game.
You can't do that. It's a bro game.
That's That's bro tax. No, but like they
that was not they didn't, you know, do
the right channels to get it in there.
So, it went to the wrong place. Got to
make sure
donated
me.
Yeah,
I did already. I've double road tax.
Donate what the people gave to you to
bro.
Oh, like just like behind the scenes.
Yeah.
Oh, I could do that.
Please. But I mean I I do that anyway.
Atlas. Atlas, you're a good Okay, that's
true actually. Yeah, it'll it all comes
up bro eventually.
Indeed. All roads lead to bro.
That's why they call them bros.
Still have two games left at you can't
do that to me.
Oh, one in a bit
cuz this game's already been It's
already 2 minutes over.
I mean,
I've missed you out.
Some games are already done in 15
minutes time.
I'm glad we're we're cussing together
again.
You already miss MSI.
Yeah.
No, no, it's the opposite. I love MSI,
but for me, um, handle
I mean, I think that's I think that's n
with the level up, it's not it's not
Yeah, that that was a short shot too
many. Um, no. So
really, when it comes to adrenaline and
how memorable the games are, obviously
you can't beat an international
tournament. But when it comes to pure
enjoyment,
there is just not a lot of stuff that's
as fun as just having an LCK series
where you're just hanging out with the
gang,
where you're just enjoying yourself.
It's a very different thing, isn't it?
It's not It's actually not the same. I
feel like they're very different skill
sets because for for obviously, you
know, you have to you have to be
serious. You have to remind people that
the stakes. You have to actually look at
the game.
Yeah.
And now we don't have any of that
weighing.
I mean, there are there are some there's
some stake stakes.
How does this keep happening to you? I
don't know. It's it's a day got on red
side. Okay. And I don't I just don't
know how to call.
I lost. I need you. You don't need to t
It's fine. I know Azir was really
strong, but you can't
I mean it is Ari and it is closer
Crocco.
Yeah. And I mean, this is one of
Crocco's greatest picks in the past. So
maybe still has a massive amount of
confidence on it.
But Sponge is also very happy to be the
troll king
as Xandel doesn't get stunned up because
that mystic shot misses.
Oh my god.
The angle. Yeah, Hype just going to have
to flash. But now Sponge, he can just
flash in and chomp him. Oh no. Oh no. Oh
no. The troll was under the bridge. And
he's just, as I said, he didn't even
need to flash in. He just chomped him.
And that was it. Now Polo just has to
watch as he also gets chomped and no one
even dies. It's a gorgeous, gorgeous
dive. And Rich also survives on the top
side. Crocco getting cooked. And my god,
DRX may just obliterate the Bros. They
will at least in this early game, Atlas,
cuz that's a disaster.
Early kill for Teddy.
Sponge getting the follow-up kill.
Apollo as well. experience gap secured a
full level by the way cuz that was on
the crash and this is very elementary
stuff. If you are weak sided you can't
be going up for these trades. You just
can't. This is a much harder dive. Pipe
doesn't literally just die off of a
single auto by the Trundle. They Apollo
because he doesn't have anyone to help
him stack.
Oh man, the fact that Angel survived
there as well is
so big. It's not even insult to injury.
might just be backbreaking, but we'll
see. Of course, it is very early. Bit of
hyperbole here from good old Atlas, but
we'll see how they're going to recover
as maybe this is all part of the game
plan because in one Bro had a great
start and you saw how that ended. Now,
what Juke has said is no guys, great
starts are not what we want. We want a
terrible start. That's what's going to
get us. Okay, but but how does that
relate to the law of sponge where if
Sponge pops off, he will continue to pop
off?
The spongiest meme like he just isn't
one that can actually be understood.
That's that's the way I think about it.
It it he is Lord Spong. We know what he
does
indeed.
Well, sometimes I I I don't Okay, let me
troll king and he is one and I'm a
little bit worried about that. in a game
before a game. I never know what Sponge
does. But if Sponge is winning, I do
think generally he just keeps winning.
When he's losing, I think he keeps
losing. I don't think he's a he's a
combat guy.
That's a good point.
But when he's playing from ahead, I
think he is a little dangerous. We'll
see though. Closer and Kle have a lot of
playmaking potential. And he is trying
to sneak in here.
Oh, just on the edge of vision.
Yeah, not quite able to sneak into that
brush. He doesn't have Yeah, he has to
cuz he doesn't have flash or six. So,
oh, that is costly.
Level six is at least gained here for
Morgan. Does have that world ender back
up and hype and Polo just doing the very
best to catch waves underneath this
turret as Teddy lining a whole bunch of
these piercing lights onto Polo helping
soften up this Braum.
Shots going ary and it's looking a
little bit rough still. It's not exactly
end of the world as far as CS is
concerned and things like that. He's
only down about a wave. Uh is hype. So
that is going to alleviate if he can
stay competitive.
But mid lane extraordinarily even, top
lane extraordinarily even. And it's all
just the jungle and bot lane gaps that
are really starting to protrude here.
Oh, Ko getting invaded.
Yeah, problematic as that is a really
nice winter bite to spot out exactly
where Andal is.
Still level five.
Yeah, teleport. No, not a teleport. That
is a back. That's um that's less
aggressive.
A little bit unfortunate here for the
Bros as they will lose their red buff.
Crocco.
Yeah, it's uh feels like a race to level
six as the VI and he lost.
Yeah, I got I got nothing more. He will
be able to hit it off of but like look
at the vision control. He's not going to
be able to punish this bot lane
whatsoever.
And DRX a bit of an early game master
class. We kind of questioned Unil, but
it was his early trades
that set up the dive and they got both
kills off of a very clean setup with
Unil living. Sponge and Teddy both
picking up a kill.
And now the continued invading.
Brok I think needs to make this gank
work. They need to find something on
Rich.
Guess what? Rich, he's looking for a bit
of a back angle.
Oh, yep. There you go.
That's going to spot him out. So this
ward gives them all the information that
they need. Looks like Crocco might be
able to make his way over to some grubs,
but you can see the pings are coming
through from Sponge as well. That would
not be uncontested.
And so slinking back into his jungle.
Crocco just kind of licking his wounds
at this point. Teleport is going to
bring Andel towards the top side.
And they'll clear out some vision, make
sure that these grubs are going to be as
safe as possible. Yeah, with control of
mid lane and there is no contesting
this. So DRX have so far just controlled
everything on the map. And when you're
behind with your VR rec composition, it
just kind of falls flat, right? You need
to be able to actually find a target.
Going ham is Oh, good charm.
Yeah, decent charm. But the Empress
provider is still going to connect this
time. At least the box fire and the
sorry, the spirit rush is going to be
able to get him out of the way of
Vandal.
But that's still a win for the Rex. The
RX are looking at this going, "Okay,
Ariel means there's no window." Look at
the vision control as well. like yes
that is pink but even then I'm pretty
sure they knew cuz Krocco was on the top
side. Look at the vision that's there in
this top side jungle and before it was
in the bot side. They've been tracking
Krocco from the very beginning and with
Kroco not being able to make an impact
because he's being tracked. The lanes
are really struggling as DRX the solo
laners doing a good job. bot lane we
already talked about
and it doesn't really get better from
here, right? With the Azir on the map,
the fact that Trundle scales perfectly
into the later stages. Doesn't exactly
have the greatest of subjugate targets,
but it's not really that much of a
problem if you can just control your
opposition. And in the 1 v one against
Crocco, he didn't even need a lead like
this to have a very good time. It would
be very funny if Dx like some are two
zero, but the Sier just doesn't matter.
Well, Morgan does find a world well
world ender angle and Sponge gives up on
the opportunity here. Does just throw
down a pillar and realizes that he's a
little bit too close to the turret. They
don't exactly have hard CC.
So, he's allowed to live for the minute.
Slight advantage as well as far as CS
like Morgan and Clos are at least
farming well. And you can see the money
as far as the solo lanes concerned is
fine for the bros. It's just elsewhere.
It's kind of going catastrophically
wrong.
Early drake,
triple grubs as well for DRX. So,
they're feeling great. The only thing I
am a little worried about is that when
it comes to setup, they are relying on
And they'll be in there. Without him, I
think their CC is pretty lackluster.
Yep.
You're really only looking at a shuffle
and a pillar. Now I love Trundle pillar
but
into the enemy team like how good is it
really? Yeah, it's not amazing when it's
alone, you know.
It's well that, but there's also there
is u what is it? Um dash.
Y
there is a vault breaker
obviously.
Stand beside me.
There you go.
Stand beside me or stand beside Brock.
He says stand behind Bra.
But it is stand. Well, it makes sense
cuz it wouldn't It'd be weird if the
name was
Yeah, I think we're supposed to say
Braum.
But if you're playing Braum, you can say
me.
Well, he still says Braum, though. Like,
he talks about himself in the third
person. That's kind of weird.
Do that. It is kind of weird. Atlas does
that too sometimes.
Yeah, I don't like that.
Yeah, I know. Neither do I. Okay. Um,
what does Atlas think about it?
He loves it.
Uh, second drake being contested here.
Look at the item finishes. Item done for
Sponge. Item done for Teddy as well as
Rich sitting on a Yeah, they can contest
this. I think they made the right call.
But you are VI and Ari
and you're not contesting Drakes. You're
down to
And that is going to be feats of
strength. Objectives are concerned. And
there is another mountain. We are
inundated with mountains.
Is anything more bro than beating DK and
then just getting two zero by BRX?
Nope. That is about as bro as you can
get. And do you know what it is?
It's a lack of brok.
It's just everyone lost all of their bro
tags.
The people are struggling.
They should have got all of their brok
the the the committed like uh the the
the bro predictors.
They would have been like rolling in the
cash after, you know, they they they
picked up the win against DK. Like the
channel points should be there.
Should be flowing. Oh dear.
It's fine. It's only a 1.2k gold lead. I
do think the game state is getting worse
for Bro, but let's not pretend that the
RX
It's never too late for more Broex.
There is always a way, you know, as it
it might be tough for the Lord, who I
think knows that things are getting a
little bit rough as they do move their
way in. Flash still available, but he
decides he wants to use that next time
because he was looking pretty dead. And
it's just going DRX to DRX. That is
going to be feats of strength. Some
upgraded shoes now available here. And
the Bros looking just kind of worse for
wear.
DRX making good use it looks like of the
time that they spent.
Just we've got a new one. We've got
Atlas. Stop blaming chat attacks.
I don't know where that one goes.
No, that's good.
That's a good one.
That's good.
I'm sorry. Sorry, I'll stop blaming
chat, but that was very good.
That is the core of many bro memes. He
will not chat. Don't let him get away
with it. I love this actually.
Accountability for Atlas.
Okay, I apologize. However, you still do
need to pay your bro.
No, it's you and you and Ox are both the
the kings of getting as much Brot tax as
possible. Accountability for Aux as
well.
Well, I mean, it's just you just got to
pay Broax, man. It's I'm not the
government. No, I am I'm going to
question I want to question why why are
we paying our bro tax? Why do we need to
do this?
So that the bros can stand a chance.
Well, but if I've been paying for Broax
and I'm not seeing any of that in the
pro performance,
but it would have been way worse if they
hadn't paid any protag.
Well, you got evidence of that.
No.
Well, then why are you making these
claims?
If I could travel to a different
dimension, I might be able to prove. But
I can't.
Oh, we're not even doing a little
timeline hop. We're not doing a little
multiverse. No, because everyone loses
interest. As soon as you bring in
multiverses, no one cares anymore. Okay,
we don't have time.
Nothing matters.
We don't have time to talk about the
fact that if there is no causality,
nothing matters. Atlas, there are
stakes. You said it many times.
No, we were talking about dinner,
weren't we? I said that there wasn't any
steak.
No, we were talking about vampire
stakes.
I forgot. Oh, now we're back to Leslie
and I'm feeling way better. Okay, Andel
and uh Teddy are looking for a little
bit of an angle here. I don't know why
we're we're doing some uh K River,
but uh we are going to move back to the
A ramming. We were river ramming for a
moment, which is some pretty crazy
territory.
We're going to get a Herald fight. I if
bro lose this fight, I think it's done.
They need to find good target selection.
Well, Crocco is just going in. He
flashes out of the way of the solar
flare and finds Yahoo. Closer is there
as well. They manage to land the char.
True shot barrage is going to be able to
take down the Azir. And now Morgan is
going to end TRX's world as he takes
down Andel. There goes Rich as well.
Thank you for the protag chat. You guys
did this. This is you
as the target selection
of Crocco and Closer find. Yahoo. That
man did not get to play the video game.
And the turn around
that we all knew deep down was coming as
the Herald is taken. The mid lane turret
falls and bro is back on top. And you
don't need a multiverse anymore.
Chronicler, you know that it was that
influx of purple text
that allowed this to happen.
I don't know whether that's the case,
but bro are definitely back in it now.
They in fact have a 1,00 gold lead
again. Highlight here is the turn onto
Yahoo. So really good flash from Crocker
to ensure he doesn't get taken down by
the solar flare and then an entire open.
He goes into Paulo. Oh, okay. We are
back in the action once again. Emperence
divide is on too, but it is Andal that's
going down and Paulo just walks it off.
Close is going to turn off but DRX what
happened? as Teddy is actually kind of
popping off right now. But the
relentless pursuit to try and escape
is coming on through here. There is the
culling. That'll take down the Braum.
And it is a two for two in the end.
Guys, Drake is up. I feel like we have
more pressing. DRX could have just took
just take a drake. We could have got
soul point.
No, no, no, no, no.
Just take soul point.
There was hitting enemies to do
chronicler.
Uh, as we go for the dive as there are
many, many people on this. I didn't see
that solar flare cuz I think outside of
the replay off screen that was actually
he did travel to the multiverse. He was
hitting eight trucks in the other
timeline.
That was where
exactly.
Yeah. Okay. Before they got all of the
people back that Thanos did his cliff.
Not in this timeline though as clearly
didn't find the was ambitious dive
anyway. Uh what does it mean for the
fight? Closing those have his
that dragon that we were going to fight
over before. Rock is going to go in.
They are just looking to execute the
Trundle and they do exactly that. And
he's got the Eclipse running, but
where's the follow up? Where's the
answer? It's a double for Hype as
Yahoo's now just going to get stunned up
by the Braum passive. Teddy gets ceased
and desisted. Oh, assault and battery
was so much better for doing that. Um,
but he that is kind of what happened in
the end. And now it's a free dragon over
to the bros. They have full control.
This was all part of Juke's plan.
He warned him. He said early leads,
early leads are bait are killers.
Never have a lead early and everything
will be fine.
And you know what? Proof is in the
pudding, Chronicler.
So, engage onto Sponge, who I really
think should have just subjugated at the
start of this. Maybe could have lived.
But there's also the question, why are
we that far up when we don't have an
ultimate uh on the Azero? cuz if a zero
is an ultimate, they can't make that
play cuz they try to go that deep get
taken down. And then these segmented
plays where Morgan just gets the press
Q, they can't get the ST, the Braum
passive. It's one by one by one by one.
Obviously doing a lot better there.
Now DRX still in a playable spot in this
game. But
I mean, this is still a throwable.
Uh yes, for either side, which I do
appreciate
big time.
We're going to see that this goal graph
is precisely how it looked in the last
game, but the other side
like almost exactly. It's almost poetry.
It's beautiful
as Closer was unable to kill that
minion. Um, which is a bit awkward.
Poetry needs tension. Okay, Atlas. Not
everything is perfect.
Yeah, that's true. That's true. Light
and shade and stuff like that. It's it's
shades of gray, blah blah blah. Um, not
not a certain number of them. Okay. No,
that's it's the gray area.
They didn't they didn't even go there,
Atlas.
Oh, it's not in the It's not in the
zeitgeist anymore.
He scoffed. He scoffed.
Yeah. Just scoff at you trying to just
pilot your way for yet another
nonsensical allegory that we're trying
to make work.
Have you seen that there's an Australian
dude that just does really Australian
summaries of movies?
I have not.
There's a Twilight one. It's so good.
It's very funny.
My uh the person that was the best man I
went actually made me read all the
Twilight novels.
Really?
So I actually did read all of them.
Yeah.
Is that worse or is me reading them
twice on purpose? That as Sponge is
going to get taken down very low again,
but this time the subjugate is going to
be working out through barrage wasn't
enough. Oh, the door is there to answer
the Lucian as Closer was dashing over
but doesn't quite find a target. Getting
taken a little low, but looks like DRX
doesn't want to commit with their front
line. No, Rich. Uh, okay. Well, I guess
he had flash, but no longer. Hm. Well,
he's just going to go home. That was
weird. All right.
Wait, so so you just also read all of
them voluntarily?
Yeah, I did. As my uh one of my best
friends in uh high school was like,
"These these books are great." I was
like, "All right."
They there were, but I enjoyed it. It
was fun.
Yeah, it was a bit of a romp. Uh, you
know, I like vampires as we were talking
about in the previous video.
It did give us um Robert Patterson,
which
I mean, I don't think he needed the
whole Twilight thing, you know.
Well, no, but it definitely helped.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
I think if we had have just been able to
like skip that bit though and just had
the Robert P.
No, I actually No, I actually think it
adds it adds character. It adds
character.
Oh, brilliant. Well, Derrick's doing
that start up.
How do we feel about this?
Well, we saw what it did for Row in the
last game, so I I I'm waiting with great
interest. Well, we are trueing and
barging. Bridge taking a bit of damage,
but it's Morgan in a bit of trouble.
Does find some knockups though, and
remember has a lot of healing. He goes
golden, but now closer is going to show
up. The equalizer does nothing. Teddy
trying to get out of the way of Polo,
but he should be able to get this one
done. It's a double as Teddy makes his
presence known. Ice charm will connect
but Andal back underneath that sundisk
and bro don't know about this one is
dead and sponge is still up so it's noon
now
just a two for two rich if he uh
positions his queue a little bit better
there with the arm guard I think he
could have actually cooked Morgan could
have been big cuz look at the damage
he's able to do here I think both his
old and his Q right there
timing a little better and he kills
Morgan and then Morgan to get the reset.
Uh closer also is able to get to the
rest of the fight, but it's a bit of a
mess as again these fights are so split
on either side. No one gets out of Khan.
So we look at what has actually been
used. So it's flash for Crocco, flash
for Paulo, flash for Yu as well. Uh and
R doesn't have his arm, which I think is
actually a big deal. As Ro are just
going to start it up again. I'm not so
sure about that, but there is no
equalizer right now available. and and I
might just have to get this.
I mean, there's actually there's no alts
apart from the uh the solar flare that's
coming up pretty soon. It is just gone.
So, the bros some highway robbery here
as the artic is going to be secured.
And that's a magis. Wow. Closer. Wow.
How can you be like I'm going to build a
banshees and a magis?
Well,
I feel like you've just that's like
multiple personalities.
No, no. There is a school of thought
that Magis or sorry Banshees allows you
to play more aggressively spell.
Oh, right. And that lets you hold on to
the stacks more effectively.
Well, that but also you can play more
aggressively into the opponents cuz you
can tank a skill.
True.
So like you can you can ult in more
aggressively because you're fine.
Well, we'll see whether that is going to
remain the case. So far 306 having a
very good time as Yahoo may discontinue
having a good time.
We're playing two sides of the map here.
This is risky from bro.
They are.
Yeah, I was about to say
on a dragon right now. That is going to
go down. But can they all get themselves
out?
Why did Why did we We did not need to
press the Q button.
Not going to move the wall.
He needed to kill actually needed to
kill it as soon as possible cuz he
didn't have smite. Oh,
so he did actually really want to try
and kill it even if it end up with him
dying. Two das now for Bro. They're
going to be feeling amazing about that
as well. Yeah, some uh individual
mountain das also feel pretty good with
this composition that doesn't really
have a true tank as all right in goes
the V. Doesn't quite find the V breaker
and will just get that back massage and
put into the death chamber with the
equalizer. Very well played here by DRX
to lock down the jungler, but just a
little bit of a step too far there by by
Crocco on the bottom side of the map. So
they'll lose the turret and DRX
incremental little step back into this
game. Unforced arrow there by Krokco.
Gets the drake. That was big. Uh if he'd
given his life, taken the drake, I think
it wouldn't have felt as bad, but that
was just not necessary. Just walks up,
tries to go for the Q, and just uh dies
unceremoniously. Very straightforward.
Doesn't have flash, so you can't use
your Q like that. Even if he hits it, I
don't really think you can do too much
with it. Two item spikes now being hit
across the board. There's the stopwatch
for Rich. Sterox for Morgan. Man, this
really is closer versus Teddy, isn't it?
on this Lucian.
He's been doing a good amount of gaming.
He's back.
Yeah.
Oh, wow. That's a good time to start
talking about him as well. That's a big
spike.
He is still Lucian though. So, if he
does get over by Crocco and Closer gets
on top of him, I do think he dies
indeed.
And DRX, their job is to make sure that
that exact cuz everyone else I think you
can do without like Yo, Rich, it's fine.
You don't actually need them to win a
fight. You do need Teddy. Teddy needs to
live.
And there's no males or anything like
that. So over charm hits onto Teddy. He
is dead. That's likely what the layering
of CC is going to be. Crocco goes in,
hits him with the cease and assist, and
then you just pour everything on top.
The vision denial is the main thing
because if you have multiple angles from
which you can come, then you can
actually take down Teddy. But if he
knows you're there, then you're going to
have a much tougher time. So denying as
many wards as possible is a big deal for
Bro here. So DRX doing the opposite
trying to make sure that Uniel can just
create as much vision as possible. Yeah,
about 1,000 gold here for Morgan top
side of the map. Two items to two and a
bit here from Rich. Pretty happy to have
the Oblivion orb as well. Trisha Barrage
going to pick the gap and in fact there
were four post. So that was AFL 100% six
points. Closer pushes this wave in.
deals with that at least one level lead
here for Morgan. Items aren't
necessarily looking to Atrox favor in
this match up right now. And I think
Rich is going to be kind of okay with
just picking up this wave as it heads
towards the turret.
But yeah, Teddy against the world. It's
just Jin Air all over again. Why is it
always just it all comes back to Jinire?
Good question. I don't know. Kind of
crazy.
He is also an AD carry. do think that
they have this situation happen a lot
and then they make one misstep that
arguably isn't a misstep and they just
die and it's well game's done.
Oh, Crocker clearing out some vision
here. It's DRX. Oh, once closer gets
that death gap. That is a big spike.
Oh god.
I think DRX might want to look for a
fight right now to try and deny that. He
has the 10 stacks already completed as
well. Oh, that's going to be a ton of AP
Atlas.
Yeah, hype possibly in trouble, but the
pillar are not really doing too much.
Trish shot barrage just to spin the wave
as best they can. That's an arcane shift
as in comes closer. He's spotted on
vision, but what? And is just dead. He's
just too far up. Just a mistake here
from the support out of DRX. And you
said it already. He's the only one that
can hold people in position.
Well, Baron Pit might be doing them some
favors here. That's a close and tight
corridor. Oh, look at the setup here.
Multi and Crocco looking
on the angle. Finds their way in. There
is the flash forward from Closer, but
Teddy's life and then he's taken out.
Rich also is going to be able to go
golden, but that's a sea or death type
goal. And now, Yahoo finds himself
running the wrong direction. They save
the the Azir till last and Sponge is
running for the hills. This is a Baron
if the Bros want it, but they might look
to break open the base first as the true
barrage sails by. Oh man, probably going
to be kicking himself after that one.
Wonder what happened there. It's I think
another example of DRX not all being on
the same page.
Yeah,
cuz
he needs to step up to try and secure
vision. But I hope we get a replay to
see what actually happened there. Felt
like
he both overstepped. But if the rest of
the team at least provides some safety,
maybe that could have been something. We
did see though the problem for Teddy as
Okay, guys. This game is
It's um
This game is done.
It's not looking too good. That's a nice
solo flare, though. Polo comes on over
just to see what's going on.
Yeah, but the game is done.
It is. And it's so weird that it's an
exact mirror of what we saw in game one.
But the other side. Um okay, we're
rushing a Baron as Soul Point is looking
to be picked up here by the Bros.
YOLO.
Yeah.
Oh. Oh,
but hang on. They do a lot of damage to
Baron.
They might be able to take this.
Have that teleport to come in from
Morgan.
Angle true barrage to lay on through. It
is going to be rich that locks down the
baron for TRX. Teddy has been dove on
though. He does manage to take down
Crocco, but Morgan's there to end his
world. Yahoo now trying to get out of
the way. And the Emperor's Divide
doesn't really do anything.
Unfortunately, if you divide by zero,
you're just going to find yourself in
the death chamber. And there is the win
for the although I guess croc died and
closer lost a whole bunch of
stats. Wait wait wait wait wait.
This is a huge trade up. They got soul
point and Nash. Okay. Yeah. And it
looked like we were just looking at the
bit of the fight the bro won and I'm
like oh it's all great but it's not.
Okay.
The DRX macro.
Yeah. I don't know how that even works
but let's have a look at it again. So,
this was just a straight flip.
Pure 50/50. That might end up deciding
the game.
Uh, goes down to 150, by the way.
Um, not sure how that happened. And then
Teddy does take down Krock, but more
importantly,
close or dice. Was Hype just not there?
No, he he based.
Uh-huh. And he he had to cuz he had no
health.
Yeah. Uh, but that did mean that they
they were down a member. H Yeah,
quizzical. Yes, it was certainly a turn
of events. It's also an even bigger
deal, right? Because that's eight stacks
off the forbidden book for closer and so
it's going to have to find another
me back to the red. I want to see that
gold craft go up and down.
It's not quite a heart monitor unless
you have a very very slow amount of BPM.
But we are getting back towards a beat
on the other side.
Their siege is good. they can set up.
Need to actually get to the turret
though.
And a team fight when it works
looks pretty good for DRX as well as
let's see whether some more of these
picks can actually Oh my god. Dear Rich
taking so much damage. Closer having to
use the odd just to avoid the culling.
But once again, Andal is in no man's
land. Emperor's Divide just to buy some
space. And it might have actually done
so as Teddy down so low. Still trying to
kite. Still trying to do damage as
Crocco. He can't get there. Oh my god,
Teddy, you monster. But he's left the
rest of his team. And they are going to
fall down. Rich with the teleport in and
then the run away. And wait, was this
another DX straight up? I don't really
know
where the rich did he base.
I thought he was dead before. What
happened? What?
I don't know.
Show Atlas. This game's This game is
getting to me. What is happening? Why
Why are these events transpiring? I'm
I'm watching it and trying to yell about
it when it's happening and I still have
no idea. I have to admit to you.
I think we need another replay. Okay, so
the poke is really good here from Bro
and Poke actually finding the angle on
Rich was really good. So Rich runs away.
So Rich runs away and then I I legit
think if he just goes in here and toast
them, I think they just all die. But he
has empower So the he has empowered
Baron recall so he thinks he can get out
and then get back in. Yeah,
but then he doesn't. And if Teddy dies
there, that's game. I'm not even jo
That's That's game over right there.
But it's not. He doesn't die.
So, we get another fight. This game is
still not done.
And Closer just won a team fight, but
he'd already sold his book.
A
feels terrible, doesn't it?
That's bad.
Wait, guys. There's no objective.
Why are we in river?
You got to fight for the river.
No. Push the side lanes.
No, no, no, no.
So, Yahoo, despite being two and seven,
is about to finish his death camp.
This is a game, Atlas.
Oh, it really is. This is This is one of
the most games that I've
Do you know what this is?
What is this?
This is Rise, baby.
Oh, heck yeah.
Wasn't it cool? Yesterday we got two
Rise Rise series, one after the other.
That was amazing. We It was a real
treat.
I thought you were You were You were
hyping up KT.
I think Rise is the better group.
GenT1, that's nothing. Yeah, it's not
compared to this.
I don't even understand this. It's so
far ahead of me that I just don't even
get it. I'm
so glad we're back at the LCK and we get
to witness this League of Legends.
Exactly.
That's Challengers, baby. Why wasn't Bro
at MSI? Ah, because they'd make everyone
else look too silly. That's why they're
not ready for Bro on the international
stage.
Maybe one day. Well, they they you know,
theoretically it's possible. Oh, he's
going to show him the door. Pretty good
about that.
Morgan, Morgan, Morgan, Morgan.
It's the Pinser attack. There's the
flash in right on top of Yahoo. But it's
it's the Lucian they have to take down
and they absolutely do that. The Empress
Divide on to three, but what is that
going to do? The answer is nothing at
all as Hype hits two with the ulti on
the back end. Sponge gets eliminated. Is
that a clean ace? Is that a clean ace
for the pros? It absolutely is. This is
Anvil for the first time this series
goes down last and the Bros will move on
to game three.
Not even close, baby. As Lord Morgan
with the taxes in his hand, heavy with
gold finds the flank. Crocco gets on top
of Teddy. Teddy did not get to play the
game by the way as we highlighted that
Vari combo ends up being the difference
maker.
That was ridiculous. The Lord has never
had a performance like this on Aatrox in
my recent memory. I I just honestly
haven't seen it. This is often times a
pick that he's not quite found success
on, especially for closing out games.
That flank angle absolutely beautiful.
And DRX just crumbled.
Oh my goodness.
We are learning. We are learning many
things. We are learning that early leads
are bait. We are learning that Azir is
overrated
and maybe we are learning that Broax
does in fact matter.
Broax does matter and I
Okay, I need I need evidence but we're
we're getting evidence. We're gathering
it right now.
This is the thing. What you did is you
just pitted the power of Broax against
Azir and it just shows Broax is more
powerful than how good this champion is.
I think it was just Azir or sorry uh
Vari just dunking on the only Honestly,
it was a bit of a reminder because we
did see like
there's been many examples of V looking
a bit muted,
but then sometimes she can just
she can just press R on someone and that
someone is really important and when
they're dead, there's no way to win the
team fight.
Oh golly gee, we get another one of
these chronicler. Time for us to take a
shot. The space going to break it down
and we'll be back for game number three.
See you there.
Heat up
[Music]
here.
Heat.
[Music]
Heat. Heat.
Turn
how
Oh, the wind.
[Music]
Fore
speech.
[Music]
Hey,
hey,
hey.
Hey hey
[Music]
hey.
Heat.
[Music]
[Applause]
Are you
[Music]
[Applause]
Hello and welcome back to the space.
We're here after game number two where
Bro was finally able to take it down. It
was a very close affair being very back
and forth towards the end with some of
the Azir and Lucian damage from the side
of DRX. Wasn't enough to get them across
the line. Bro do tie it up and now we go
all the way. Gentlemen, what happened in
that game number two? I thought Bro had
once again a draft where they can
control the early game. They'll have to
make some tough decisions in the mid to
late and they should be able to pull it
off, right? They get ahead early, right?
They did not get ahead early. Uh in
fact, it was a little bit problematic.
We were scared that the Azir was going
to get out of control. The very big hole
in the bottom lane with illusion was a
bit of a problem, but eventually the
comp, yes, was quite simple to execute
and bro buttons. Yeah, I was kind of
confused that uh Vi and Ari didn't make
the play by themselves in the early game
because they're known as early game
king. They could actually make some
plays on the side lane and help your
laners to win the pressure. But I feel
like it was kind of late at the moment.
But in the in the we going to see the
first highlight, but it was actually
huge enough to bounce back because uh DX
was kind of trusting themselves too much
in the early game. Uh and their team
comp was not about that one against Ari
and Vi.
Yeah, we should definitely talk about
the draft and uh just see what was going
on in this one because the VI was picked
first and then the re followup from
closer. It just feels like traditional
crocco closer duo, right?
The main issue I had for DRX before they
got to the last phase of the picks,
right, was their lack of engage. Like
they sure they have his ear and they
have pillar, but Ezreal gets locked in
first. They take the Lucian instead for
some reason instead of taking the Ezreal
themselves. Then they pick Leona cuz
like well we really need some type of
engage. But into this draft, if you're
not super coordinated or if you fall
behind, the Leona dies slowly but dies
repeatedly as we unfortunately did see
for Andil in this game. I mean, it keeps
happening whenever junglers are playing
Trundle. They know they're stronger, but
it's really hard to target someone in
the fight. So, uh I think teams are
starting to confuse more whenever they
are playing Trundle. And they uh bro,
they really have the easy comp. they can
just target one one champion and just uh
just dive into it. And I think that's
what happened in this game mainly.
Yeah, definitely did. We should talk a
little bit about the game. We had a
highlight here for the side of Bro 15
minutes in this was this was the first
fight where it felt like okay, they're
playing to their composition. They have
Vi. They're going to press their
buttons. They did it well.
I have serious issues with how DRX
approached this fight. So super
halfhazard here from Teddy. There's no
setup. like ult Palo and this flanking
Azir where Bro already knew he was
topside is such an easy target to
collapse on and they just turn away from
the enemy Lucian and go well that's an
Azir that's the only way we lose this
fight he doesn't get to Emperor's Divide
he's CCed and taken down DRX threw the
game here basically in terms of the lead
they had by just trying to force a fight
where they had no right to do if the
Azir is with the rest of the team on the
other side they could use the Azir to
peel and look for some additional damage
or if They collapse towards illusion a
little bit fast or sorry towards the
Azir a little bit faster. Maybe they can
make that happen. But it's such an easy
call. The second they see the Azir
physically like with their eyes to just
use their first V ultimate of the game
and take him out.
Yeah, as you mentioned, the right
approach with the Trundle jungle is just
hit the front line with your Trundle and
you have your DPS on your back, but Azer
was on the front in front of a Ari and
Vi, which makes no sense here.
Certainly didn't uh did put him in the
death chamber. Now we're going to jump
very far into the future about 19
minutes later 34 minutes into this game.
The last fight that Bro were able to
take down and end this game on.
I mean Bro this time around they didn't
throw in the objective. They just gave
up the objective but they kept the
pressure and that's why they were ahead
in uh many moment and here it was great
TP flank from Morgan and at this point
they were just super ahead in the game.
So all they need to do is jump into the
target and demolish them. I mean Yahoo
played it as best as he could. I I think
really I mean he was able to zone and
then get away and set up for a big peel
ultimate, but the fight was won before
that happened and he was behind so much
of this game once he lost control early.
So he couldn't actually do big damage.
And in that fight, you know, especially
with how quickly those types of fights
can break out when a flank like that
happens from Morgan, if you're in zonas
during the fight, you're not doing any
of that late game as damage. So, it
doesn't really matter what items you
have. It doesn't really matter how good
your scaling is if you're just sitting
golden while the rest of your team falls
apart. I mean, the big difference
between game one and game two is Bro
didn't actually int for objective. Even
though you miss the Nasher, even though
you didn't have the lead on the Drake
stacks, they don't care control about
the map control. I mean, just take care
about the map control and vision
control. They just take the better fight
and objective didn't mean anything if
you're winning the fight.
Yep. Not by the end of that game. Well,
we're done here on the space for now.
Now, let's go back to the casters for
the final game of the night.
Thank you so much, Valdez. And it's a
little bit sad that it is the final game
because think about it. If this was a
best of five, we could have three more.
I can only dream
of what conversational topics we would
hit in a best of five between Bro and
DRX. I actually think I'm going to bring
this up with the LCK commission. What if
we did it so that like cuz we have like
five rounds, right? Why don't we make it
so that round three is just best of
fives?
Well, you know, we are getting playins
and like I think only the only the 10th
team is not in
that's ninth and 10th, right?
I'm going to have to check. Might be
ninth and 10th. Either way, I think it's
better with nine. That sounds more fun.
That being said, it'd be harder to find
the matchups unless you run it gauntlet
style, which we have done in the past. I
need to just do a bit of a refresh on on
the on the bracket and what it's going
to look like cuz things have all
changed.
And now let's see how things change in
this draft because we are fearless. And
honestly,
that is the word of the night. These
teams, both of them, fearless
probably should have been a bit more
fearful in both of these games certain
points.
But let's see how it is going to go here
in game number three when it is all on
the line. The Bros, they've done this
before. They did it two days ago. They
took down DK in a reverse sweep best of
three style. You are correct by the way.
I think it's the um
it it's number one, two, and three. So 9
and 10 are out. Y
So that means that we probably won't be
see cuz I think one of these two teams
it's probably going to be in ninth.
Might be BNK.
It could theoretically still be DK. Uh
depending on how collapsed you truly
think they are.
You'd have to colossally collapse, I
think.
Well, no. They're like 10 points ahead
of everyone else. Yeah. Like we're not
talking just a normal collapse. We're
talking we're talking big big collapse.
And we do have uh just confirmation that
uh 9th and 10th are both out
as we just learned. Good to know that I
at least remembered that.
And once you're in planes, you can do
whatever you can dream of. You know, you
can make it all the way.
Exactly.
It is possible. You could go on a run,
Atlas.
Oh, the Brun. Imagine it.
The Brun. Oh my goodness. Oh, that
reminds me of that really cute TV show
with the car called Brum. Do you
remember?
What is the recent greatest? Is it Is it
Well, it's DRX, actually. Never mind.
Like, what is the greatest run? Like, is
it home? No, it's DRX.
It's just DRX.
It's just DRX. Yeah, never mind. Huh.
Kind of.
It's kind of frustrating, isn't it? Cuz
that'll never be topped and so it's just
always DRX from now on.
Well, it's cuz they won. I think
otherwise Hanwa might have actually get
if it if they both ended in the same
place. I think the Hanwa run might have
still been crazier.
True. But
the 2021, but again, I'm not trying to
argue this cuz it is DRX. We both know
this
for a fact as we are. You know, normally
this early rail pryo I'm not a fan, but
Alistar is out and it is Palo. So I
actually I'm down with it. I respect it.
I like it as the rise is picked up here
for Yahoo. What is closer going to play
into it? I'm not sure about first pick
rise. Doesn't make me feel fantastic,
but
it did win in uh
that's true in the previous series.
There's the Cassiopia and that was not
what was picked
by Chovi in our last series. So this
time the snake lady. We got horse pants
and snake lady. It's very, very cool
stuff as Sponge and Yahoo. What are we
going to be locking away here to augment
this composition? Jungle Pool is looking
a little thin, especially after the
Nocturn and Pantheon were both banned
away.
We'll see where Sponge is going to go as
the Rakan is a consideration likely the
Zire to follow. Teddy is big advocate
for Zia. Always has been. Still, they
could go with something else. This could
be just them making sure they have some
engage.
I think Aaya does run into Jinx.
Could see that come through. I like this
a lot actually.
Yeah,
Charvin combined with Vakan really
strong. Also takes away a lot of the
strong AD carries that you want to go at
this point in the game. Right. Lucian's
out. Ezreal's out. Can go Zia, but
you'll still be stuck.
Yep.
can't exactly fly over that wall play
here
cuz you want something that can kind of
deal.
You could know.
So you could actually, funnily enough,
you could go Renekton, go an AD m
jungler and just go Ziggs. I'm not even
joking.
True.
Like Zigs into like if he ult you just
ult yourself and then uh Satchel and
then he dies.
Yep.
I could see it. I I wouldn't hate it
actually more I think about it. see
where the hype does want to go there.
And then what's the AD jungle that you
do decide to pick alongside it? Is it
like a Viego or a Zed? I guess Zed's a
bit flavor of the month at the moment.
I wouldn't mind Zed. What else do we
still have open? Pantheon's out. Knock
out.
Fury. Haven't seen the Fury in a while.
Yeah, I think the Fury is kind of bad.
Probably a Bri.
They They actually make the Okay, let's
They actually make the read like this a
lot. The Zban I think is very warranted.
like it.
This jungle pool is going to get well
and truly
it is.
There's going to be something that we're
not thinking of right now that's like
super obvious.
Oh god.
What? Wait, what?
It's Lee. Oh my god, you're right. Can't
believe we're not thinking the most
arguably the most iconic jungler ever.
Is it not that we should be considering
creating carries though? Because like
maybe it's a Kaiser. You could
theoretically Kai your way out of a
cataclysm.
You could Kaisa. Yeah, I think Kaiser
works. But I do think playing Kaisen to
work. Okay. Oh my god.
Well, they're banning the Lee as well.
I I am really happy that I mentioned
both Zed and Lee and then they both got
banned.
I I do kind of that that makes me feel
that makes me feel good. That was nice.
That's It was nice. Take take the win.
There you go. Yeah, it's good. Well, now
what does uh what does Crocco play
though? That's the real question.
Maybe you just slam Ziggs here and give
yourself more time to think about it.
could do it that way.
Let's see. It's Crocco that we're
focusing on at the moment. And oh god,
it's my it's my train of thought. Oh no.
I liked yours a lot better, but instead
we have got the croc and the cat. And
it's a managerie. We've got horse, we've
got snake, we've got the crocodile, and
we got the kitty cat. So what animal can
be picked for the bottom lane?
What are we playing here as hype? You
can't go Ziggs anymore. Like I I really
no absolutely
there's there's no shot.
So what do you go cuz everything else
that's good runs into the Jarvin
problem. Do you know Teddy has played
the most civer in a single game out of
any other player on the planet?
Yes, I am aware.
I also noted killed Faker like 90
minutes in.
Did he really? What was he playing?
He was Kazix, wasn't it? It was and it
was it was into the Cassadin and it was
a very cool moment cuz it was the very
end of the game. Anyway, um we have now
the uh
going to slam like Ash or something and
just be unhappy
or just say
high side. Yeah, that makes sense.
Oh no. So like they weren't listening
when you were I guess they were
listening when you were talking about
the Lee and the Zed and so then they
banned that away.
Well, it's like but it makes sense cuz
like what?
Yeah. No, what else are you going to
play?
Are you going to play like Olaf? That's
not that's not a champion. Taran showed
us that unfortunately.
Yeah.
Like I think Nefair is kind of rough.
I'm sure again I'm sure there's stuff
that we can think of if you just sit
there and aren't casting uh one or two
obvious AD junglers that maybe were not
like Talon. Talon's kind of fun. I don't
hate Talon actually.
Owner would have picked Talon.
Oh no. And well Cuz would have picked
Viego. Okay, but that's bad. FGO is
actually bad though. I feel like Talon
actually in this spot that's like I
could see it. Talon Zigs I think you
feel better.
I'm worried for bro.
It depends how much they can play around
top side. I think that this is this all
comes down to how much Morgan can just
crush this lane with Crocco's help.
Does Kroko have his card? We don't know
this actually cuz right now I don't
think anyone besides Kenyon has the
card.
Yeah. U Peanut had it for a little bit
but he lost it.
He he definitely he does. He's no longer
in possession. Yeah, he he kind of
forgot to re-up the uh the license and
and lost it, unfortunately.
Lucid had it once upon a time. That was
nice.
Well, you've got a pretty comfy looking
draft here out of DRX moving into this
game number three and the Bros are
experimenting. There's certainly going
to be some laning prowess that they
might be able to find. See how it does
go under the rift.
[Applause]
[Music]
All right. Do really like the vibe in
here today. Both sides of L Park
erupting as these fan chants ring
through and it is late, right? It is
like almost quart 10. It's getting to
the point where it's like I'm I'm sorry.
We're going to have to take a cab cuz
we're we're not we're not going to have
the train to get home.
And the energy in this room is still
electrifying.
Many.
There is a problem though because I was
talking about it and we we've got horse,
snake, cat, crocodile, and lady and
Kaiser.
Well, Re is also a girl, right? So, I I
know she is metal horse pet.
Oh, it's not it's not actually a horse
though. I know, but you can you can get
with like I mean Azir is also not
Is it Isn't Isn't
okay is a pigeon.
Okay, fair enough. Yeah, but doesn't
Kaisa isn't the thing isn't it like a
venom situation? Isn't the thing alive?
Oh, yeah. But it's not really It's like
it's a void creature, but it is alive.
We were in a bit of like a farmyard type
vibe or at least a zoo.
Yeah. What would you have picked though?
Cogmore, cuz then you can be pug and
then you're a doggo. Well, Corki uh was
banned cuz it was fearless, right?
What about 80 carry Nasses cuz then he
could have a dog. 80 carry Renekton.
Sorry, not Renekton. Rengar,
you are losing me. Atlas, these are just
the animals that you could have picked.
No,
it would have been double cat if it's if
it's
Well, Zia was not it, but Zia was fine.
Yeah, they had to crash down here
towards the bottom side as Paulo does
find a nice little stun onto handle who
finds nothing with the grand entrance.
So, it's decent. But Teddy is still full
health and he's just bouncing these
Beyblades all over the lane. And the
Bros realize they're going to need a few
more bandages here in this bottom lane.
Also, hype going for Ghost. Not going
for uh
Andy more defense if they use it. Yeah,
they got a good amount of damage down,
but unless they get damage down on Teddy
as well, it's a bit rough. I do think
that early on Kais has way more damage
thanks to her passive and her Q than
Civer does. Lethal Tempo as well here
for hype mid lane match up closer known
as a very mechanically minded mid laner.
There's a reason right if you get make
your name on champions like Aurelia and
Akali.
Yeah.
Um those are really mechanic champions
first and for as
yeah if that passive gets perks he would
have been in a bit of a rough spot but I
guess he's fine. And the thing is like
Endor just makes himself a target and
then while they're busy trying to kill
him,
Teddy is just hitting them with buttons.
Boomerang Blade comes down. He's just
walking at them. He's just walking at
them. Crocco is here looking for a bit
of an angle. But remember, I mean,
Spongeb
to be so incredibly careful. Crocco just
going to look for the crab. And Hype
needs to be really careful. These little
pizzas are really getting scary. I know
that's not the skin he's using. In fact,
Teddy using a very weird skin. It's like
pack civer or like you just don't pick a
skin. They know about this gang by the
way. So, I think it's a good call from
Crocco to dip. Not run the risk. Would
have been a time waste if he did.
I'm not sure. I do know that um
I did see Krocco go for the best skin,
which is nice.
Is it the Canyon skin?
It's the Canyon skin. Yeah. And there's
also Renekton with uh Renektoy which is
also the best.
Oh yeah, Morgan. Morgan always to be
trusted uh to use the best Renekton skin
every single time.
Thank you. Oh, look at that.
Glorious.
Looking good as per usual.
Crocco is just going to wrap around, get
some traps in, and then wait for his
camps. Just uh suffering from success a
little bit when it comes to clearing
things out a little bit too quickly. Not
going to be going overly aggressive or
anything like that. Looking for counter
gang, counter jungling this stage of the
game. So the pathing a little measured a
little game three here.
Oh, this is a long one, Atlas.
Oh yeah, we are we are not going anytime
soon. Don't you worry.
That means our viewers are secured.
Guaranteed, some might say.
Cannon was just missed there byus.
I didn't want to talk about it.
Um, but guaranteed pure entertainment
for at least the next 30 minutes.
Yep. And uh that is a huge advantage
that Teddy now has in this lane. You can
see he's behind in farm but ahead in
gold. The power of the cannon do remain
on the other end. It's cold season for
hype.
All right. So just uh saying we don't
really mind what happens in the lane.
This is also one of the games where I I
think DRX feel better about their
scaling, but it's not like Bros is bad,
you know, like between the Kai'Sa and
the the Kaisa Re and Casio.
Yep.
You're always going to have good
threats. Their front back is a lot
clunkier than the RX. I think the RX
comp is a lot more straightforward to
play out. I do think that Yeah, if if
Bro mess up the the initial salvo,
right, they can't get on top of Teddy.
Teddy just kills everyone. And I think
they just don't have the range to deal
with Civo.
Well, yeah, but I do think the the
Kaiser to me in late game is just so
insanely insanely strong if you can just
get on top of the enemy cuz your burst
is just
kind of out there. But as you say, they
do need to actually be cleaning their
setups, which bro have been. Sometimes
I think they know they can do it.
Sometimes they decide not to do it.
Oh, it's all up it's all choice.
Yeah. Well,
they believe in the broth whenever they
lose. It's just their choice.
They just they get the statement back
like how much tax is actually being
accured. If there's not enough,
then you know, let's just run it down.
If there is enough, they perfectly set
up. They find the angles. They fight
back from any deficit and they bring us
to a three game series. Hollow
finds a shattering strike onto Teddy's
spell shield and will just now vacate
the area. Got a bit of a back coming on
through there as the void seeker does
find that one melee minion
and the ghost back off cool down the
heal the same thing. Everything
equalized but
it is just a bit of a potential lane
swap angle. Never mind just going for a
reset. So not going to be swapping these
lanes at this point in time.
It's brewing brew.
It's game three Atlas.
We do be brewing.
That is the case. Morgan up here on this
top side though alone for now. Rich is
just passing by. Didn't actually use
teleport. Neither did Morgan as he went
back and got some uh steel caps.
And yeah, we are just very calmly
pingponging the waves back and forth.
You want to hear my smoothie story from
Please tell me the smoothie story.
Uh so it was me and uh and Mr. Daniel
Draos and it was the I think it was the
day of of finals.
Mhm. That was the day you kind of looked
like uh looked like a vampire, right?
So, what I was going for was uh Florence
Pew and Thunderbolts, but instead it
looked like evil Peter Parker from
Spider-Man 3.
It definitely did give off those vibes.
Yeah, it was it was good. It was fun. I
I I always enjoyed doing the the type of
stuff just uh you know,
keep it interesting.
Why Yeah, why not, right? Might as well.
We're on camera. Fun to play around with
a little bit. I didn't think it looked
particularly uh again skill issue on my
end. Makeup did a wonderful job. Uh but
on that day, we got a there was this
place called uh I forgot what the name
was, but it was basically like, you
know, like a healthy food store and they
did smoothies.
Yeah. Yeah.
And I got a really nice smoothie. And up
until that point, I only got like the
bowls, you know, like an acai bowl with
just a lot of fruit.
Yeah. Those stuff I I'm holding off a
little bit to see if we get action. I
don't think we'll get action. I think
we're very much burn brewing. And it
looks like we're solid.
Yeah. Teddy actually didn't get the memo
that we're not doing this.
No, no, no. He he does. He does. It's
fine.
He just sat there for a while longer
than he didn't need to. Yeah, not at
all. Follow with two pieces of B.
So I got my smoothie, but up to that
point I only got the balls. Draco kept
saying mama. I'm telling you, these
smoothies are amazing, you know, in
there. You could like slam extra fiber
in there, extra protein. There was just
a lot of lot of I think I got a mango
one towards the end. It was wonderful.
So uh I'm I'm trying to drink my
smoothie.
Uhhuh. And uh I'm like, man, this is
really good. And then at some point,
like the stroll stops working. I'm like,
what's happening?
Why why am I not getting my smoothie?
And I I asked Dragons, he's like, no,
I've never had this issue. Like, maybe
blow on it a little bit. So, I try to
blow
just a little bit on the stroll.
Oh god.
And I don't know if you guess what
happened next.
How much of it went all over your face
and how much went all over your front?
So I actually thanks to my cat. Oh,
there might bit of a dive here towards
the bottom side and that is just a dead
Sante
as Rich hands up in frustration
and I don't know. Yeah, it's so I that's
how I felt actually right there. Uh
because my entire face and my shoes I
actually didn't get on my shirt were
covered in smoothie.
Damn.
Yeah, it was it was a mess.
It was the perfect time to get to the
end of the story right as Rich got
smoothie all over his face as well. I
know
under the bottom lane out of turret.
We're going to have a look at it one
more time.
It makes sense that you'd feel safe cuz
you're Casante.
But you just these minions, man.
Yeah. So, so the combination of the
minions and also why are you you are on
the weak side, my friend. Just sit
there. The wave was coming for you. That
was that was why the hands were up. That
was an unforced error.
Yeah. And it's also one of these times
as well where you're against a Renekton.
I think you're feeling the pressure as
well to not let him get a big lead in
the early game. And you did that.
So I guess you don't really have care
that much, right?
But but he did.
Now he's CS down.
Yeah, cuz he just died and lost like two
waves.
And also Morgan doesn't seem to have
been put that far behind by the lane
swap either. He was in a 1v2 scenario
for quite some time.
So the only win for uh DRX is that Polo
got the kill. That's it.
Yeah. Well, that's a that's a positive.
still going to be getting to that
redemption a little bit earlier if
that's what he does decide to go for.
I did finish the rest of the smoothie,
by the way, and it was really nice.
I mean, mango smoothies are just good.
Yeah. Yeah. But it was it it was
gruesome. It wasn't great.
Tell you what really like made my life
better. Discovering avocado smoothies.
Oh, yeah. You've told me about this.
Avocado smoothies. Just the best place.
Yeah. My wife always tries to sell me an
avocado juice, which I think is just an
avocado smoothie.
Yeah. I don't know. It's like strawberry
juice. And like, isn't that just a
smooshed strawberry?
No, I think they're a lot more juicy
than
than avocados, but I think it's it's the
same, right?
Yeah. Bit of a weird situation.
You Australians do love avocados. I have
been told
we we are. I mean, avocado toast. Why no
one owns a house? All of our money on
avocado toast. It's absolutely true.
Certainly.
As Rich and Morgan facing off, Rich
actually still holding his own as we can
see, trying to pull things back. Does
have the Bramble vest at least.
But I think Morgan just pretty happy
with how this game has gone. Haven't
seen too much of the uh Crocco Morgan
combo,
but still relatively early days, I
guess. Although 12 minutes probably
about the time where you will have
wanted to have your crocodile and cat
lady in a somewhat uh relative vicinity.
Wait, he's going AD.
Wait, what?
Okay. Oh, maybe. Well, actually, it
might be like the Shyvana build where
you go Shoin into like Leandre. That's
kind of fun. I kind of like that.
Going to work here for Crocco as in goes
Sponge. Magnets to try and turn this
though as Petrifying Gaze doesn't quite
get the stuns and down goes Polo. The
spears are sort of flying all waywood
and closer is just dead. TRX, they
answer back beautifully here, but I
don't quite know what the plan was there
by the Bros.
I am uncertain what the plan though was
there. As you're saying, Atlas, I feel
like they blew everything into Oh. Oh,
well, Type is possibly also dead. Grand
entrance going to connect this time, but
he makes it underneath the turret
utilizing the flash.
Oh, that's big. If he dies as well, it
would have been a complete disaster.
Now, it's still not great, but
a bit of a disaster.
It's It's a It's Yeah. Well, can you
have a mouth disaster? I feel like then
it's just like an inconvenience, right?
Yeah, I guess so. But it is a big
inconvenience. Like we're right on the
verge between Mal Disaster because
why are we all ining? We don't need to
all in on the sponge here. Maybe they
thought they'd find a killer instinct to
get hype in there. We can't do that.
Well, if in doubt, kill rich seems to be
the plan here as there is the Crocco and
Morgan show that we were asking for. And
that's a 1.5k gold lead for Morgan's
crocodile, guys. And look, there are
leads on Renex we've seen in the past.
This is not any regular lead. This is a
guy who has an emote in the game
of this champion.
And we'll see what he's going to be able
to do. Black Cleaver is now completed as
Rich went all out, but then he was all
out of options or something.
I don't even know if he wins the one v
one is the worst part.
Oh, Rich, we've seen this before. This
man has had really good performances
marred by sometimes kind of giving into
the tail.
Yeah.
And now that that first kill
was not good, but I think you can come
back from that. The second one is I
think a lot more costly. We might be
seeing the third one. Although the niti
is a little bit far away and there's a
recan coming down to offer some
assistance. Yeah. Who up here towards
the top side?
Closer.
He is going to be really big in like 15
minutes cuz it looks like he's going for
Archangels next.
Yeah, he's doing the rise build. He's up
against Rise. Just copy the build.
You also really like having a bunch of
extra mana on Cassopia. I
guess I agree, but I do also think
you're not going to be doing any damage.
No.
And Bryce has utility
and you do not. Well, if you're old, but
like how often do we actually see that
as utility? Well, it looks like Purple
is actually going the You have the
Myasma. That's pretty good.
Yeah, it's it's fine, but I don't think
it warrants the champions. They're going
to contest. Oh, let's see whether they
can actually find the angle as the spear
is just avoided here by DRX. Teleport
back in from closer though as he's
looking for the angle. Fro needs to land
some of these, but he's not really
hitting them. And there goes the drake.
Void seeker going to connect onto Rich
and it's going to be a hex tech soul
this game as well. That's massive. Down
to 50% here as Yahoo does spot out where
the Renekton is.
One to one in Drakes. Two to two in
kills. That's how I like my rise group
matches. Atlas.
Oh yeah. Legend group could never.
All right. Uh Spear doesn't find
anything. Void doesn't find anything.
The Rift Herald is just going to be
secured here by DRX. Both still retain a
2,000 gold lead off the back end of
this. It's kind of crazy that they're
able to get that far ahead. Of course,
most of it is on the crocodile. And it's
largely because they've just taken more
farm. As you can see, mid lane pretty
even, AD carry pretty even. There's a
catastrophically massive gap between
Rich and Morgan right now. Sh. If we
don't talk about it too much, it's not
real.
Oh, but it is.
No, it is.
And I've talked about it a lot.
You do love talking about Morgan.
I I just I just tend to talk.
Wait, and actually mainly about Morgan.
I was about to say all goes back to 2021
Atlas.
Mhm. The Morgan Camille. I still have
all of the trading cards. Every single
Morgan trading card.
Oh, you know, I'm sitting on a on an
auntie card.
Oh, heck.
Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah.
I've got my uh I've got an effort card
as well. I think I have like nine of
them. Looking forward to
I also have Pace, which obviously I'm
very happy about.
Yeah, that's a goodie.
Bunch of Zas cards. It's nice.
I got a Faker. I don't know whether it
was a like a holographic Faker like the
foil.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I got a couple of
foils. I just can't remember. I only
know that I got all of them.
I definitely got Pas in foil. That was
awesome. All right. Bit of a grand
entrance here from uh from Andel, but
it's Polo that decides to go back in
with the crash now. Cataclysm going to
come on through. Crocco just pounces his
way out. They do get the exhaust, so
there's that. But Polo can replace that
one pretty quickly and does so
immediately, in fact.
as we don't have an objective right now.
So these ults being thrown out not super
consequential. They are kind of starving
Sponge out of resources though which I
do like.
Yep.
Uh Morgan and Rich fighting one another.
There is the Black Cleaver first
completed here by Morgan, but thorn mail
still working out here for Rich.
I like the Black Cleaver first though.
And you can actually trade against
Casante and not go for too many autos.
So, it's not one of those situations
like if you just use E and Q, right, for
the trades.
Yep.
You won't be taking
the healing reduction until you actually
order. So, you can kind of trade around
that.
Hype here just trying to catch these
waves when they approach. Level 11s for
both of our AD carries. Never mind.
Level 12 for Teddy
who's doing a great job. Just continuing
to be Civer, right? Wants to be getting
to three items as soon as possible. Oh,
he knows he is the saver guy.
We have off a tool about
may have you do. Yeah,
but going to be a little while. Isn't
going to go for infinity edge second or
anything like that. Can kind of do that
and get away with it, but who wants some
attack speed in the build,
especially in this game.
Oh yeah.
So, how many people in chat do you think
are making the Casio Piano Boots joke?
Oh, yeah. That's a good point. Let's
check. There's always one.
I can't see. If not, if not Twitch chat,
you're letting us down. You know, you
have one job. Well, you don't. You get
There's just a bunch of people standing
up for Rich and what he's trying to
achieve. I appreciate that. He is a good
dude by all accounts.
All right. Well, Crocco going to be
taking this crab. And the Bros retaining
control of the map. They are slowly
getting further and further ahead, which
most of that gold is just on the
crocodile. Um, but let's not kid
ourselves. A very fed Renekton with a
next drake coming up. Uh, is a pretty
big deal as Paulo gets the blue.
So going for a Zeke. Haven't seen that
in a while.
That's an odd move.
Two items done for Teddy now. Not quite
there yet for hype, but he is probably
going to look to get that on his cuz did
cash out the call on the next wave.
Maybe he needs the base cuz he needs to
get a second item before this drake
contest comes through. He does have a
few moments uh in order to do it. So if
he does go back now,
yeah, there's the skates actually fine.
Uh does he have the money though?
Well, that's the main thing. Needs a
quick cloak and a complete the uh
recipe. So maybe not. He did buy
relatively recently.
That's that's big.
Apollo tping in.
Um he does have his merk treads now
complete.
Remember
the next kill, that's what secures feats
of strength as well.
Any sort of pick is going to be even
more meaningful for either team
as it's going to be upgrading their
shoes. Closer's shoes not going to be
upgraded, but Cassiopia still gets a bit
upgraded. It's okay.
Teddy is so big, I think, with the two
item spike on the AD carry.
Oh,
sometimes you just want to press R.
Yeah, I think he was trying to predict
Sponge's EQ and then he just didn't.
Yeah, that was a bit weird. Well, Closer
is going to stand his ground here.
Myasma does go down as Andiel not going
to be dashing off that one, but he still
takes a lot of damage. Crocco getting
out of there because he does the same
thing. Primal Surge might be able to
keep him around though. The sustain here
for the Bros. is going to be a little
bit better.
Both top laners are backing looking to
TP in. This could be the fight that
decides to game. Yeah, Morgan very scary
on this crocodile as we know, but it
looks like
bro might be giving this up. Let's see
how this one's going to go. The teleport
comes in and Morgan with the rest of his
team and he's just walking forward. He's
like, "Guys, I am huge and I will be
able to take these guys down." Sponge
gets out of the pit. Crocco gets in.
There's the magnet storm and they've
caught two out of position. Down goes
the rise. Yeah, he didn't get the memo
that they were backing away and they
secure the dragon. The pros are looking
to try and do it again. That's speeds of
warfare as well locked down and they get
the second drake for themselves.
Might just be that might be looking for
as well.
Is this a bridge too far? The answer is
probably not because there's no rise for
another 20 seconds.
There's no Teddy. He's walking way over
from mid lane. I don't think they have
to damage.
Yeah, he doesn't have on the hunt
available as there's a little knock back
onto Morgan. They're going to look for
the turn angle. Cataclysm onto closer
who's standing his ground. Teddy gets
stunned up, but he's
doing a pretty good job standing his
ground. There's the dash around from the
Casante, but he just doesn't have any
money. Punch highway robbery as Polu
comes on over, but he's not able to stop
him. Teddy will go down as the slices
and dices come in, but is such a big
prize. And Yahoo, he's going to turn
back up. The triple knock up from
Sponge. They take down the Kaiser and
it's TRX that are able to get it done.
Morgan will go down and I have a feeling
that that emote is going to be
necessary. The shaky hands for the
Renekton out of frustration here for the
Bros unless they can get some sort of
psycho turn. I don't know about that one
as out goes Crocco and he's not even
able to get his raptors I don't think.
Man, it was so good when they took the
dragon and that was when we needed to
cut the video.
I'm a I'm a bit perplexed. I'm a bit at
a loss for words there Atlas because
that game should have been dunzo and I
want to highlight what happens here is
bro I think kind of get lost in the
sauce because what happens is we have a
complete turn if they just help closer
they win the fight.
Yeah.
If they just kill rich
immediately they win the fight. But the
fact that DRX get to keep the leash, get
the TP in,
get the autoacon as well as the fight
win might end up deciding the game. Now,
I want to make very clear that game is
not done. Uh, this was big for DRX, but
they were losing.
Gold lead, I think, is still about 1 and
a2k for bro.
Yeah. Yeah, something like that. Buton
is a lot, right? Is actually incredibly
high value. Basically, it's even is what
we're saying.
Um,
Poly died.
Poly died again.
Okay.
Not ideal.
Uh, Crocco is making rifts. He's looking
to make another summoner's rift.
Yahoo. Got another kill.
Yeah, he's five and one.
Yep.
That's a Wow,
it's a big rise.
Yeah. I also I just don't quite remember
when that happened.
Oh, he's been involved with six out of
the seven kills.
Yeah, he's having a great game.
as Oh, Apollo.
Oh dear.
Just um
very straightforward. Was caught in a
place on the map that he wasn't allowed
to be.
Just trying to clear vision as Morgan
might have to take matters into his own
hands. Can he get the plasma stack for
Hype?
Now he's going to try as Ridge goes all
out and then he's all out of options
unfortunately. And Hype comes on over.
That is going to be another one picked
up. He now has his Infinity Edge done.
So this Kaiser now able to fight on a
little bit more even footing. Teddy is
going to make it a little bit uneven
after he finishes his Infinity Edge, but
it's taking a little while.
And it is even a slight gold advantage
here for Hype as well.
Actually, we're in Rift Maker. Did
Krokco, so kind of cool.
It's a It's a build. He's building some
items,
making some stuff happen.
Curious as to what's happening next as
far as that build is concerned. Maybe it
is going to be Leandre's coming in
afterwards. Just pretend to be Rumble
after this.
Might be kind of the way to do it
at this point. Just go redemption, bro.
Just embrace the redemption Olaf energy.
Honestly,
you're going for like I'm not even
joking. Like redemption into the DRX
comp actually goes really hard.
Just rabbit on so that your your primal
surge just does so much more healing.
Yeah, but it's not team wipe, right?
No, it's not. It's nice. But maybe you
don't need your team to live. You just
need Morgan. Well, I would say you just
need hype actually. Um, but I do like
your Morgan propaganda.
No, I am uh I'm committed.
You are. So,
the game is basically even, especially
taking the two pound upper dragon. I
think the RX have a slight scaling
advantage, but that does really fall
apart if like Teddy is ever out of
position, right? Cuz then
ignore that minus one cuz it was Morgan,
so it doesn't count. He didn't need that
money.
Dad, are you familiar with the term
biased cost?
Yes.
Yes. Are you sure?
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I know. Because I'm
biased towards Morgan.
Okay. Just making sure. Yeah. Well, that
was that was
I think it's I think it's different when
you're biased towards a player rather
than a team.
Well, it's also again I've said this
many times, but we're never called out
for bias. So, I think you're also easy.
I think you're also allowed like two,
right?
So, because it's barrel and Morgan.
Yeah.
And death. But that is, you know,
retired, right?
Yeah. Yeah. He's in military at the
moment.
I don't mind. Lucid Crocco. Oh, I guess
you did sort of forfeit your time. Oh,
flag and drag into the realm war. That's
pretty cute. As DRX just going to look
for a little bit of a baron steel.
I think it's gone.
I think the Bros know that this is
happening, but can they actually do
anything about it? That's the question.
Too late.
Yeah, probably going to get held out of
the pit here as Andrew just buying space
and the spear is not going to land
highway robbery. They'll be able to
steal away the purple buff.
That's the rise value. There it is
right there. And that's why you can't
give up vision control around that area
even for a moment.
Well, they knew, right? And actually
think Kroco could have made it. Just
didn't have the time. They're going to
get soul point, but soul point for Nash.
That's not worth it. Soul nob brainer.
Now they got to hold on tight and pray
that they get the opportunity to get
themselves to chem to the hex soul
somehow.
It's going to be the big one, but Sponge
and Yahoo getting to work on this inner
turret. That is going to extend the gold
lead here for DRX as they move to about
Yeah. 3k Rebel Baron power play here.
And Crocco possibly caught out of
position unless it's a cunning ruse.
Rich making his way over Hype. We know
that he's in danger. Does he know?
That's the real question as there's
Yahoo flashing on top. The flash out
immediately there from Hype as well.
Shattering Strike. Not something that
Rich really cares about as TRX keep all
these Barons alive. Look for a bit of a
reset.
I know what the other one was. It was
pace.
Ah, there it is.
Yeah, there you go. Easy.
Well,
I actually have a lot now that I think
about it.
Yeah, there's a few.
And I'm sure it's not just Morgan and
Barrel for me as well
as Yahoo as you highlight picks up the
Rabidons was already a complete menace.
Machine gunning down everyone in his uh
in his sight.
Morgan should be finishing his third
item.
This is a huge swing though. The gold
was pretty firmly in Bro's favor.
That said, Bro can actually just sit and
not do anything for the next like 8 and
1/2 minutes.
They can, right? Because they they're
sitting at top point. DRX is nowhere
near.
The the real issue again is what do you
actually scale towards
and it really is just Casio and Hype.
It's a bit cute. On the hunt does come
down. That's a good charm on a closer.
But they don't really get any real
damage on the hunt now on cool down. In
fact, both bottom laners using their
buttons.
Oh god. Okay. Both top laners going to
join the backside of this fight as
Morgan. He wants out. He's got splicing.
He's dying and he's uh he's Yeah, he's
just he's just getting out of the way.
Man, I thought that was going to be so
much more exciting and cool than it was.
That's okay. It's a tense situation
here.
There is no objective. These teams are
just But obviously DX trying to get out
of the Rebel Baron power play which was
fine sponge.
Yeah, doesn't quite find the flag and
drag there as Kro is able to pounce his
way out. Yahoo is so scary though. They
do back out of the way of this rise.
Even the ricochets, man. Oh, Teddy is
really starting to hurt
and late game is where this man thrives.
You can see the nerves. They know how
important this match is really big deal.
When a highlight again, bottom two are
out. DNF, they're not technically locked
yet, but they are in obviously a very
deep hole right now, but it's probably
going to be one of these two teams in
ninth place. Yeah,
it's them or BNK most likely. So getting
a direct win over your opponents is a
really big deal. And for Bion
really their a lot of their wins funnily
enough came against teams on the other
side.
Legend group not against their direct
compatriots
here in the rise group for DRX. What a
big one it would be. Means that they
equalize the score.
This is kind of crazy though cuz the
Baron has now worn off. Yes, they
eliminated all the inner turrets. They
got themselves a decent gold lead, but
it's only decent. It's only 3k.
Yep.
We have another fight that's going to
happen in a minute and a half
approximately on this Hexte dragon
and it's going to lead directly into a
Baron immediately afterwards. It depends
how much milling about we're going to do
to see whether both of these objectives
are up at the same time or not.
But man, this has gotten very tense,
very very close when it did feel at
different separate moments each team
would run away with it. felt like that
Baron play was a huge back breaker. It
turns out, you know, Bro were able to
weather the storm. They didn't throw
away anymore. The main thing is the map
control cuz once you have that Baron
containing or keeping map control is a
lot easier as we can see here,
right? Broer still hasn't really been
able to fully retake.
There's also this rise problem.
Yeah. Well, I mean, Yo has been a
problem the entire game, right? Like the
lead is getting kind of ridiculous. Um,
but what I want to really highlight is
that because of this, I think bro just
gives this next drake. I actually don't
think you can test cuz I think that if
you don't, you're going to be able to
get to a fourmon hype to a four item on
closer and those are big break points.
Getting void staff I think is a big
deal. Obviously for your Renekton, for
your Ni, it doesn't feel that great, but
if you lose the game or if you flip the
game here and you don't get the dragon
might just be the end of it. And for
Bro, I think the target selection is a
lot harder. They need to somehow find a
flank with Morgan. If he can't get into
the enemy backline, I don't think he can
win the fight.
And it's so frustrating as well because
they need to kill both Yahoo and Teddy
immediately at the very beginning of the
fight.
Spell shield going to get popped here.
But the bros, they are looking for it.
They want to fight for this. 5 seconds.
And Crocco getting dove on here by Ando.
The dragon has now spawned. Oh goodness.
Are we flipping for Hexte soul?
Oh yeah, bro. Want to for sure. Well,
they're going to start this one up. Oh
my goodness. Taking so much damage.
Morgan is just going to be Hex getting
Nova. Rich will follow him. But
Quickness gets into the backline. But
where is the follow up as Morgan flashes
over and Rich uses it as a way to taxi
his way forward. They take down the
Javan. The killer instinct. Oh no, he
didn't really want to do that. But
fortunately, they did have a crocodile,
but it may not be enough. Closer is
still alive. Yahoo is so big. And in
goes Crocco. And I just don't think
he'll have any assistance here. And
Yahoo has to do it alone. He has to be
the hero, but he's on the Myasma. And
he's taken by Crocco. And they have the
hex tech soul.
I didn't even see the dragon go down.
This is absolute cinema and I love it.
Mayhem Atlas.
I I I I I don't even know what happened.
I We're going to try and do our best.
Look at Morgan, man. He's like, I've
been run prisoned. Teddy doesn't have
spell shield.
Takes care of two people. Crocco is just
ensuring they get the smite. Gets it at
111. And even if this fight doesn't go
their way, just that I think was enough
as long as they don't decisively lose it
to be a win, right? Cuz Hexo I think is
the most broken sword in the game. But
then here the heal value is actually
crazy. Therefore, Crocco
Yeah. Croc like Closer had a pocket
healer. It was like watching like WoW
arena,
you know, and they just didn't kill.
He was wobbing and weaving. He was
getting that line of sight. And in the
meantime, Sponge is just dead.
Okay, welcome back to live, ladies and
gentlemen. The jungler is now down and
the bros
Oh, there must have been an influx. It
must have been you guys yet again. The
purple in the chat has now transferred
into the game and is now a buff
surrounding the bros as they march
towards DRX.
Pay to win in my LCK.
Oh, absolutely. And we love to see it.
Capitalism, baby. As All right, the Bros
now just diving. They know they can see
it. And they've got hex tech. It is so
disgusting. Down goes everything. Hype
is collecting a triple kill. And Teddy
turns up just like Donald Glover with
the pizza. It's a quadra under the
inhibitor turret. Inhibitor to follow
here. And the bros, they are done with
this. They want to go home.
It's about 11 p.m. and yeah, out of the
death chamber and straight back in there
once again. Could have potentially been
a pentacill there for hype, but instead
it's Crocker that locks it down and the
Bros do it again. Backto back reverse
sweeps here in their first week of this
round. They're looking good.
Lot of excitement,
a lot of hype
performances from hype as well on this
Kai'Sa. Not the easiest pick to execute,
but I'm looking at that mid jungle duo
again. I'm looking at in the previous
game. It was for me mostly closer on
that. In this game, I think Crocco
actually made the Ni work. I think he
keeps his pass. There was a crocodile.
I think it was a weird game as well.
It was. Yeah,
it was. There wasn't a lot of spears
landing, but the way that he got around
team fights, especially later in the
game, he was useful.
And uh that's not something a lot of
nitalies can say.
And then um as highlighted,
uh Morgan,
oh yeah,
flawless performance here on the
connection. I think he did have a bit of
more of an up and down in the series as
a whole.
I think his scion was also robbed of a
victory there in that game.
Uh I don't think his I think his
pretty flawless. It was not great. His
son wasn't He got a lot of value out of
the zombie. Not a lot of people get a
lot of value out of the zombie.
It really He didn't hit it all, Atlas.
It was It was rough.
He did hit one fourman after everyone
else on his team. How did he
He also hit He did the one where he went
into the turret and his charge
explosion.
Yeah. So, the entertainment value is
extraordinarily high out of his side,
let's say.
Yeah. And uh
on this on the flip side, a bit of a
heartbreaker for DRX. They got very
close. Yahoo actually having a monstrous
performance on the rise.
Oh yeah,
but the timing wasn't quite there. And I
think when you look at team fighting,
it has to be the Jarvin, it has to be
the Casante, and it has to be the
Raakan, right? And those three need to
work in cohesion. And I think early on
we saw it, but as the game progressed,
we kind of lost that.
And the thing that's really hard as well
is that it was a bit of a top gap
situation, right? A bit. and uh
zero and six.
This is also and I want to step away
from my you know overblown Morgan
fandom. He is not the best top laner in
the league
that crocodile.
He is on his croc his atrox also um had
a pretty game-winning flank towards the
end of that second game as well. But I
mean Rich just got absolutely bodied in
this game.
He did.
We'll see. I think PM I think uh anyone
on the top side really makes sense. I
think Morgan given his uh as you
highlight I think his particularly his
Renekton performance but even the flank
on the Hox was nice uh closer is a
no-brainer. I think this game he really
struggled, but I think in the other two
games he was really good. And then
Crocco for me consistently over the
series. I think just did a great job
with his early impact.
And a weird
I still have no idea what happened there
with Sponge
and maybe he thought they were on the
Baron.
Yeah, of course they didn't vision,
right? So he needs to check for Baron.
So he just at that point the game is
lost. So it doesn't they lost Hex Soul.
So it was just kind of over already.
Man, what an incredible journey we went
on tonight though in this series. Even
in our first series, right, Genji losing
their first series after 27 in a row.
And then we got this. The bros showing
that they have more tenacity
than someone that built merc treads and
and and and got feeds and strengths
and got sterox and all sorts and got
zephr from a patch long ago.
Look at look at the vibes.
Yeah, man. It's beautiful. Look at that.
The bro cliff.
They showed them the island and then
they threw them off and they drowned in
the
trench right there out there. It really
is. Really is. You got to be careful of
tsunamis with a with a with a trench
like that.
Yeah. This final game at closer. Not not
the
Yeah,
the best cas I don't think p was a was a
was a tick in the mid box.
No, I did not go for that.
This one pretty intelligent. 301
actually on the niti towards the end. I
think that the vi target selection saved
them the game in game number two.
Well, you you come on. We talked about
B. You know why he went for?
It was Morgan, right?
It was Crocco.
Oh, right.
Yeah.
Oh, you you almost you you almost got me
there. I thought maybe you you'd done
the right vote, but
I had to be serious that you know
Crocco's he's a good player, but it's
just no Morgan. The Morgan's flanks on
the the
Isn't it nice that in the past when we
casted we would have to have these
players on opposite sides and now we
just both get to enjoy.
I know. It's pretty good. It's like it's
kind of just like Sandbox and Bro got
smooshed together, which as our known
bro antie here at the LCK
is really difficult. So now with the
fact that DGO skipped a bro day to go
and support, you know, to go to the T1.
Don't put that pressure. Don't put that
pressure on me.
So now like we need someone to be the
bro fan because Don's gone.
It's not me.
It's Crocco. Well, I
I am still president of the Crocco fan
club and that will remain the case.
Not going anywhere.
Mhm.
But Crocco, it's not the Broco fan club.
Okay. Crocco
specifically.
I think the Broco fan club actually has
a really nice ring.
That actually sounds amazing, doesn't
it?
Yeah.
Consider it. I'll see what I can do. I
will raise a petition or something.
I'll raise the issue, you know, with the
board and we'll see what we can do.
Yep. We'll raise the bro tax in the
meantime. Time for us to head over to
the interview with Kroco though.
Thank you very much guys. This is dear
for the POM interview translation joined
by Kroco on the side of OK savings
thanks.
Thank you.
It's just the beginning of round three
and you've already achieved your second
win and PG pom in a row. How do you
feel?
You know, I think we all played out
really well overall.
You know,
our other teammates were saying, "Oh,
you're getting the PM again." And
they're just poking fun at me. But I
think we had such a great atmosphere
because we all knew that we do did
really well. All of us did quite well
today.
And today
marks new history for you guys. So every
time you faced DRX this year, it went to
a three game series which all ended up
going to DRX's way. So with today being
the day you shut them down, what do you
think was the key to today's victory?
[Music]
I feel like despite us being behind, I
think we just kept a really good mental
fortitude and were able to communicate
pretty positive. but positively within
the team.
That all ties back to you guys having a
great team spirit and atmosphere. And in
game two, it was so important to get a
pick on the enemy Lucian and you were
able to execute so well. So, how are you
able to make those decisions in the
pinch?
You know, Lucian has to be the weakest
against Vari comp. So I think our game
plan was honestly we had to strategize
around just getting the pick on Lucian
the entire game.
And in game three for your niti you got
a shoin and rift maker as your core
items. So what made you build them? Now,
rather than really focusing on the items
strength, I was just I just noticed that
one of our opponents during our scrim
were using these item builds and it
looked really good. So, I just tried
copying it,
but honestly, today it didn't seem too
good. So, I think I might have to put it
away for a bit until I see a better
angle next time.
And game three was so close that it was
impossible to predict who would win. So
what do you think was the game deciding
moment? Honestly, the soul dragon fight
and probably our team fighting at the
very end. I think that had the most
influence on ending the game.
And I feel like overall I feel like even
if we start out behind, we're able to
stay solid and bite out towards the end
until the end to close it out our way
and
of course there is a famous line from
you which is the jungle roll is all
about sharp decision making and intense
mind games. So did you have any moment
that stood out for you today?
I think for the VI game, I think I was
able to dodge and juke the enemy skill
shots and go in at the right time to get
a pick during those team fights. So, I
think that's what really
stands out in terms of outplaying my
opponent today.
Now that you start out round three
strong, what goals does okay savings
bank have?
I think we really want to focus on
improving our performance and obviously
our results and outcome
and improve our standings and I think
that's just the best that we can do from
our position
and that makes your next match against
BNK PRX so important. So what would you
like to say about those?
You know, I think we have a really good
feeling.
We had always been losing against TX and
BNK FX. So, I think this is the moment
that we can actually turn it all around
and create a good momentum. And that's
the end of the interview with Kroco. And
back to the space. Thank you.
Thank you so much, dear, for that
awesome translation. We made it to the
end and Bro was able to take the victory
just barely. It was very close down to
the wire, but then they kind of stomped
that last fight. So, very welld deserved
by the Bros for picking it up tonight.
Any any thoughts on that last game,
gentlemen? Any
Please don't build Niti like that.
Who was the scrim terrorist? Who did it?
Who's the guy
who infected Kro's brain?
I think we need to rebuild the player.
I think next time we we have to
Don't say that, Vald.
All right. Well, we did have to vote for
some palms. Um, you know, there were a
lot of thoughts about who was going to
be the palm for the side of
DRX and then they had to go for bro at
the end. Um, Soup and TZ once again kind
of uh not on the same page with us here.
Understandable. Uh, Vass going for
Morgan.
What do you guys think about that?
It's okay.
Atrox. Yeah,
jungle mid is is probably the way to go
just because
uh closer controlled the Arivi game and
then
I mean in fact they had
it was he played Casio and that's very
fun which might be why Soup and Giz
voted. Not sure about that
probably. So we're going to take a look
at some of the comments as well and see
what people thought about this one.
Crocco dialed in. Yeah, it's like cuz
he's a crocodile
crocodile. He's crocodiled in,
you know.
Yeah.
Nobody says dialed in anymore when it
says focused up, locked in, whatever.
But like if you want to make the pun
work,
you could have done like crocodiled in a
while crocodile. Take it like even one
step further.
Anyways, let's take a look at the next
comment.
All right. All right. Even though you
blamed the item build, his item build
actually saved him at the last moment
when when you remember Rise got the
triple kill in the D.
Yeah, the third item seekers arm guard.
He could actually jump left and right
because of his item build cuz he was a
lot tankier than uh any other build, you
know, that saved the team.
Um, but I don't want to see the item
build once again. That was so bad.
That's why he has a fan club. Yells
chronicler from the uh caster desk.
Thankfully his uh yeah Kroco the one
jump athlete.
See
um kind of makes sense. You know
throw the spear and then you have the
increased jump range.
No no no that that item build doesn't
care about the spear. All about all what
he matter is just jumping into the enemy
team. And
let's not give any credence to this
build. Come on. Um, the star of Rise are
the junglers. Like that.
Okay. Yeah. Cool. Yeah. Yeah. Makes
sense. All right. All right. Anything
else? Anything else from the Korean
side? Array of light in a dizzying game.
Sure. Cloud Templar. Keeping it real.
I want to hear if there's anything that
that's said about mid. Any um closer
voters?
Uh,
you just want to blame.
No, I just I'm just curious what they
have to say. If if the All right. There
he is. Right. KR cast. Yeah. Surpass me.
Okay, Pony.
All right, Pony.
So, how do you rate?
How do you rate?
I mean, he did get the last laugh, so I
suppose he didn't get surpassed.
Um, he did in the gold and in the damage
that was done in the game, but not in
game two where he just crushed him and
the zero was like one and five and the
revi worked out. Simple, easy to execute
composition. Yeah. Best individual year.
Yeah.
Yeah. Closers. You know, if you're
voting for like best individual year,
then I understand those pawn votes.
Otherwise, yeah. No, no more Cassiopia.
Let's take a look at the standings here
uh after that game because these two
teams were kind of close. You know, Bro
was ahead and now they're going to take
one step farther further into the lead
and DRX will remain in fourth place of
the Rise Group, which is technically
ninth. It's a 20 week for Bro.
They're now their next opponent is BNK
who they're tied with in wins. They get
that eighth win. They jump up to second
place. So, they're coming for D+ who
they already beat. Bro, could be the
key.
That's huge. Well, I mean, I have I
mean, I I have a huge disappointment for
today's game from DRX cuz the last game
was definitely wable, but uh I could see
Reach was tilting and he was like just
straight up dying four times in a row
even though the game was wable. So, I
feel like if DRX can fix that mental
issue, they have the fundamentals. Yeah,
we were watching and you pointed out he
got his teleport cancelled like what was
it 4 minutes into the game
and he was actually that moment his
mental was out the windows game was
getting late
plates after that for free. Yeah. Oh, he
was very far behind. So tomorrow Wolf
and I are going to be casting this. It's
been a late day. It's an early morning
tomorrow with the earlier start. DK up
against BNK. That should be pretty fun
especially because DK are coming off of
a loss to Bro. And then we got Homal
Life Sports up against KT. I would say
currently KT are probably heavily
favored for that one. Should be
interesting.
Yeah, the second match up is a lot
sassy.
Yeah, I really like that second match
up. I think my match of the week to be
honest.
We did see Han Life play that one close
game against Genji, but otherwise have
been looking really out of sorts. KT
Rollster.
Really looking forward to seeing what
this this team is going to show us after
a rocky start to the week from them. I
think we had higher expectations, but it
should be a really fun one. I mean,
personally, I think HLE's game win plan
is like somewhat gone for now. So, I
just want to see how they can bounce
back with their team.
Yeah, KT the perfect team to just strike
when the enemy is weakest. And I think
they might be able to do it tomorrow,
but you'll have to wait until tomorrow
to see. That's it for us, guys. Thank
you so much for watching, and we'll see
you tomorrow.
[Music]
Heat.
Hey. Hey. Hey.
Heat
[Music]
up here.
Don't you
[Music]
These health bars are so low. Diabo
dancing around this fight and manages to
take out all of them.
[Music]
What doesn't kill me
makes me stronger.
[Music]
[Applause]
Heat.